<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Iniunctions giuen by the Reuerend Father in Christ John by Gods prouidence, Bishop of Sarisburie [sic], aswel to the cleargie, as to the churche wardens and enquirers of euerye seueral parish, aswel of his peculiar as general iurisdiction within and of the diocesse of Sarum to be obserued and kept of euery of them in their offices and callings, as to them shal appertaine, for the aduauncement of Gods honor, thincrease of vertue, and good order to be continued within his sayd diocesse, and the same to be enquired of and put in vse by all the Archdeacons, commissaries, and other officers excercising ecclesiastical iurisdiction vnder the sayde Bishop according to the limittes of their seueral offices and iurisdictions, in their synodes, visitations, inquiries, and courts.</title>
      <author>Church of England. Diocese of Salisbury. Bishop (1559-1571 : Jewel)</author>
      <author>Jewel, John, 1522-1571.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[16] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">Henry Denham</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Richard Iackson</persName>, and are to be sold in <placeName>Gutter Lane at the signe of the red Lion</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1569. February. 22.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Signatures: A-B&#8308;.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Pepys Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Richard Iackson</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Henry Denham</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Gutter Lane at the signe of the red Lion</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
