<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The Romish Fisher caught and held in his owne net. Or, A true relation of the Protestant conference and popish difference A iustification of the one, and refutation of the other. In matter of fact. faith. By Daniel Featly, Doctor in Diuinity.</title>
      <author>Featley, Daniel, 1582-1645.</author>
      <author>Featley, Daniel, 1582-1645. Fisher catched in his owne net. aut</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[24], 46, [106], 176; [12], 50, 49-191 [i.e. 190], [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">H[umphrey] L[ownes</persName> and <persName type="printer">William Stansby]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Robert Milbourne</persName>, and are to bee sold at <placeName>the great south-dore of Pauls</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1624.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>An official account of the Protestant-Catholic controversies, especially of the conference held 27 June 1623 between Featley and Francis White and the Jesuits John Fisher and John Sweet.</note>
      <note>Title page in red and black; the words "fact. faith." are bracketed together.</note>
      <note>"Stansby pr[inted]. [par.]1-G1 of pt. 2; app[arently]. all the rest is by Lownes"--STC.</note>
      <note>Signatures: [par.]&#8308; *&#8308; A-G&#8308; H*-N*&#8308; O*&#8308; (-O*4) O**&#8308; P*-Z*&#8308; 2A-2S&#8308; 2T&#178; ; [par.]&#8308; *&#178;  A-F&#8308; G&#185; H-2B&#8308;. The first leaf is blank. "It seems possible that at least quires H-P of pt. 2 were originally intended to follow G4 of pt. 1"--STC.</note>
      <note>The first part is an expansion of "The Fisher catched in his owne net", and includes an answer to: A.C.  An answer to a pamphlet, intituled: The Fisher catched in his owne net.</note>
      <note>"An appendix to the Fishers net" has separate dated title page, pagination and register; within this, "A true relation of that which passed in a conference, at the end of Pater-noster-Rowe, called Amen: touching transubstantiation" has separate dated title page, but pagination and register are continuous. This contains a reply to: Sweet, John.  A defence of the Appendix.</note>
      <note>P. 190 misnumbered 191.</note>
      <note>Leaf L*1 is a cancel; first word in the penultimate line of L*1v is "profession". Variant: cancellandum L*1; first word in the penultimate line of L*1v is "the".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Robert Milbourne</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>H[umphrey] L[ownes</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>William Stansby]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the great south-dore of Pauls</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
