<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>An historical collection, of the most memorable accidents, and tragicall massacres of France, vnder the raignes of Henry. 2. Francis. 2. Charles. 9. Henry. 3. Henry. 4. now liuing Conteining all the troubles therein happened, during the said kings times, vntill this present yeare, 1598. Wherein we may behold the wonderfull and straunge alterations of our age. Translated out of French into English.</title>
      <title>Recueil des choses m&#233;morables avenues en France sous le r&#232;gne de Henri II, Fran&#231;ois II, Charles IX, Henri III, et Henri IV. English</title>
      <author>Serres, Jean de, 1540?-1598.</author>
      <author>Matthieu, Pierre, 1563-1621. Histoire des derniers troubles de France. English. aut</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[12], 310, 292, [4] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">Thomas Creede</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1598.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of: Serres, Jean de.  Recueil des choses m&#233;morables avenues en France sous le r&#232;gne de Henri II, Fran&#231;ois II, Charles IX, Henri III, et Henri IV.</note>
      <note>The words "Henry. 2. .. now liuing." are bracketed together on the title page.</note>
      <note>The first leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>"The first booke of the historie of the last troubles of France, vnder the raignes of Henry the third, and Henry the fourth now liuing" (caption title) begins new pagination on 2A1r. It is a translation of: Matthieu, Pierre.  Histoire des derniers troubles de France.</note>
      <note>"A true discourse concerning the deliuerie of Brittaine, in the yeare 1598", [4] p. at end.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Thomas Creede</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
