<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Tvvo spare keyes to the Iesuites cabinet&#183; dropped accidentally by some Father of that societie and fallen into the hands of a Protestant. The first wherof, discovers their domestick doctrines for education of their novices. The second, openeth their atheisticall practises touching the present warres of Germany. Projected by them in the yeare 1608. and now so farre as their power could stretch, effected, till the comming of the most victorious King of Sweden into Germany. Both serving as a most necessary warning for these present times.</title>
         <title>Colloquium Jesuiticum. English</title>
         <author>Francke, Christian, b. 1549.</author>
         <author>Freake, William.</author>
         <author>Camilton, John. De studiis Jesuitarum abstrusioribus. English.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 36, 39-62 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">B[ernard] A[lsop]</persName> and <persName type="printer">T[homas] F[awcet]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">George Giebes</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop at the Flower de Luce</placeName>, by <persName type="printer">the little south-doore of St. Pauls Church</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1632.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>The first part and possibly part of the second are translations from "Colloquium Jesuiticum" by Christian Francke. The second part, however, is a translation of "De studiis Jesuitarum abstrusioribus", attributed to Joannes Cambilhon.</note>
         <note>Translated by William Freake.</note>
         <note>A reissue of "The doctrines and practises of the societie of Jesuites", with the preliminaries of both books cancelled, and cancel general title page.</note>
         <note>Printers' names from STC.</note>
         <note>Identified as STC 14538 on UMI microfilm.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>George Giebes</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>B[ernard] A[lsop]</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>T[homas] F[awcet]</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>the little south-doore of St. Pauls Church</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>his shop at the Flower de Luce</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
