<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The gouernement of all estates, wherein is contayned the perfect way to an honest life gathered out of many learned authors, a boke right profitable for all estates, but especiallie for the trayning [and] bringing vp of the yonger sort: written in Latin by that excellent learned man Andreus Hesse, translated into Englishe.</title>
      <author>Schottennius, Hermannus.</author>
      <author>Baarland, Adriaan van, 1486-1538. aut</author>
      <author>Bourman, Nicholas.</author>
      <author>Hermann IV, Landgrave of Hesse and Archbishop of Cologne, d. 1508, attributed name. aut</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[256] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">Henry Denham</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Hacket</persName>, and are to be solde at <placeName>his shop in Lumbart streate</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date>[1566]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Signed at end by translator: N. Boorman.</note>
      <note>"Howe a man may attaine to the chiefe pointes of Christianitie, or deduction of a Christian life" by Adriaan van Baarland has caption title on M8r.</note>
      <note>The modern attribution to Archbishop Herman IV is erroneous; in the preface the authors of the 2 sections are identified as Hermannus Hessus (i.e H. Schottenius, called Hessus) and Adrianus (i.e H.C.) Barlandus. In the first section excerpts from Latin poets are rendered in English verse--STC.</note>
      <note>Colophon varies: undated or dated. In this copy the colophon is undated.</note>
      <note>Last leaf blank?.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A&#8308; B-Q R&#8308;.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Hacket</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Henry Denham</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop in Lumbart streate</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
