<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The auncient historie, of the destruction of Troy Conteining the founders and foundation of the said citie, with the causes and maner of the first and second spoiles and sackings thereof, by Hercules and his followers: and the third and last vtter desolation and ruine, effected by Menelaus and all the notable worthies of Greece. Here also are mentioned the rising and flourishing of sundrie kings with their realmes: as also of the decai and ouerthrow of diuers others. Besides many admirable, and most rare exployts of chiualrie and martiall prowesse effected by valorous knightes with incredible euents, compassed for, and through the loue of ladies. Translated out of French into English, by W. Caxton.</title>
         <title>Recueil des histoires de Troie. English</title>
         <author>Lef&#232;vre, Raoul, fl. 1460.</author>
         <author>Caxton, William, ca. 1422-1491.</author>
         <author>Phiston, William.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <editionStmt>
         <edition>Newly corrected, and the English much amended, by William Fiston.</edition>
      </editionStmt>
      <extent>[6], 604, [4] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Thomas Creede</persName> [and <persName type="printer">Valentine Simmes]</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1596 [i.e. 1597]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>By Raoul Lefv&#768;re.</note>
         <note>Printer's name from separate title page to Book 3.</note>
         <note>A translation, by William Caxton, of: Recueil des histoires de Troye.</note>
         <note>In three books.</note>
         <note>Book 2 has a separate title page, with same imprint as general title page, reading: Here beginneth the second booke of the collection of the histories of Troy. ..</note>
         <note>Book 3 has a separate title page (with imprint reading: "Imprinted in London by Valentine Simmes. 1597"), which reads: In these two books precedent, we haue (by the helpe of God) treated of the two first destructions of Troy, with the noble acts and deeds of the strong and puissant Hercules, .. And also how he slew the king Laomedon, .. And afterward, how for the rauishment of the dame Helene, wife of king Menelaus of greece, the said citie was totally destroied, ..</note>
         <note>Pagination and signatures continuous.</note>
         <note>Pages 243, 599, 601 and 603-04 misnumbered 233, 123, 127 and 127-28.</note>
         <note>Some print show-through, and some pages stained.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="printer"><persName>Thomas Creede</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>Valentine Simmes]</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
