<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A treatise concerning the defence of the honour of the right high, mightie and noble Princesse, Marie Queene of Scotland, and Douager of France with a declaration, as wel of her right, title, and interest, to the succession of the croune of England: as that the regiment of women is conformable to the lawe of God and nature. Made by Morgan Philippes, Bachelar of Diuinitie, An. 1570.</title>
      <title>Defence of the honour of the right highe, mightye and noble Princesse Marie Quene of Scotlande and dowager of France</title>
      <author>Leslie, John, 1527-1596.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[1], 50, [1], 67, [1], 30, [1] leaves   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Apud <persName type="printer">Gualterum Morberium</persName> [and <persName type="printer">J. Fowler]</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Leodii [and Louvain] :</pubPlace>
      <date>1571.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Morgan Philippes = John Leslie.</note>
      <note>An enlarged edition of: A defence of the honour of the right highe, mightye and noble Princesse Marie Quene of Scotlande and dowager of France.</note>
      <note>In three parts, each with a separately dated title page, pagination, and register. Title page to part 1 as above; title page to part 2 reads: A treatise touching the right, title, and interest of the mightie and noble Princesse Marie; title page to part 3 reads: A treatise vvherin is declared, that the regiment of vvomen is conformable to the lavve of God and nature.</note>
      <note>The three title pages are cancels and are the only portions printed by Morberius--STC.</note>
      <note>With a final errata leaf.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Gualterum Morberium</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>J. Fowler]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
