<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A true and experimentall discourse, upon the beginning, proceeding, and victorious event of this last siege of Breda With the antiquity and annexing of it, to the house of Nassaw, and the many alterations it hath suffered by armes, and armies, within these threescore yeares. Together with the prudent plots, projects, and policies of warre: the assailants and defendants matchlesse man-hood, in managing martiall affaires: the misery and manner of souldiers living, their pinching want, and fatall accidents: strange weapons and instruments used by both parties in severall conflicts. Lastly, their concluded articles, with circumstances and ordering of the siege and victory. Being pleasant to peruse, and profitable to observe. Written by him who was an eye witnesse of the siege. William Lithgow.</title>
         <author>Lithgow, William, 1582-1645?</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8], 55, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">I. Okes</persName> for <persName type="publisher">I. Rothwel</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop in Pauls Church-yard at the signe of the Sunne</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1637.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>The first leaf is blank.</note>
         <note>Running title reads: A true experimentall discourse upon the happy recovery of Breda.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>I. Rothwel</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>I. Okes</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>his shop in Pauls Church-yard at the signe of the Sunne</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
