<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Theses Martinianae that is, certaine demonstratiue conclusions, sette downe and collected (as it should seeme) by that famous and renowmed clarke, the reuerend Martin Marprelate the great: seruing as a manifest and sufficient confutation of al that euer the Colledge of Catercaps with their whole band of clergie-priests, haue, or canbring [sic] for the defence of their ambitious and antichristian prelacie. Published and set foorthe as an after-birth of the noble gentleman himselfe, by a prety stripling of his, Martin Iunior, and dedicated by him to his good neame and nuncka, Maister Iohn Kankerbury: hovv the yongman [sic] came by them, the reader shall vunderstande sufficiently in the epilogue. In the meane time, vvhosoeuer can bring mee acquainted vvith my father, Ile bee bounde hee shall not loose his labour.</title>
      <author>Marprelate, Martin, pseud.</author>
      <author>Throckmorton, Job, 1545-1601, attributed name.</author>
      <author>Penry, John, 1559-1593, attributed name.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[32] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed [by <persName type="printer">John Hodgkins]</persName> by the assignes of <persName type="assigns">Martin Iunior, without any priuiledge of the Catercaps</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Wolston, Warks.] :</pubPlace>
      <date>[22 July 1589]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Martin Junior = Martin Marprelate, who has been identified with John Penry and, more probably, with Job Throckmorton.</note>
      <note>Often referred to as "Martin Junior".</note>
      <note>Place of publication and printer's name from STC. Dated at end: Iuly 22. 1589.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A-D&#8308;.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="assigns">
      <persName>Martin Iunior, without any priuiledge of the Catercaps</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>John Hodgkins]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
