<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A monument of remembrance erected in Albion, in honor of the magnificent departure from Britannie, and honorable receiuing in Germany, namely at Heidelberge, of the two most noble princes Fredericke, first prince of the imperiall bloud, sprung from glorious Charlemaigne, Count Palatine of Rhine, Duke of Bauier, Elector and Arch-sewer of the holy Romane Empire, and Knight of the renowned order of the Garter. &amp; Elizabeth Infanta of Albion, Princess Palatine, and Dutchesse of Bauier, the onely daughter of our most gratious and soueraigne Lord Charles-Iames, and of his most noble and vertuous wife, Queene Anne. Both of them being almost in one and the same degree lineall descent from 25 emperours of the east and west, of Romanes, Greekes, and Germans, and from 30 kings of diuers countries. By Iames Maxvvel.</title>
         <author>Maxwell, James, b. 1581.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[56] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Nicholas Okes</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">Henry Bell</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop within Bishops-gate</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1613.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Mostly in verse.</note>
         <note>The words "Fredericke .. Garter." and "Elizabeth .. Queene Anne." are bracketed in two columnms, separated by the ampersand.</note>
         <note>Signatures: A&#8308; a&#8308; B-F&#8308;.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Henry Bell</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>Nicholas Okes</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>his shop within Bishops-gate</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
