<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>An itinerary vvritten by Fynes Moryson Gent. First in the Latine tongue, and then translated by him into English: containing his ten yeeres trauell through the tvvelue dominions of Germany, Bohmerland, Sweitzerland, Netherland, Denmarke, Poland, Jtaly, Turky, France, England, Scotland, and Ireland. Diuided into III parts. The I. part. Containeth a iournall through all the said twelue dominions: shewing particularly the number of miles, the soyle of the country, the situation of cities, the descriptions of them, with all monuments in each place worth the seeing, as also the rates of hiring coaches or horses from place to place, with each daies expences for diet, horse-meate, and the like. The II. part. Containeth the rebellion of Hugh, Earle of Tyrone, and the appeasing thereof: written also in forme of a iournall. The III. part. Containeth a discourse vpon seuerall heads, through all the said seuerall dominions.</title>
      <author>Moryson, Fynes, 1566-1630.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[16], 84, 83-106, 109-295, [1], 301, [1], 292, [2] p. : ill. (woodcuts)  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Iohn Beale</persName>, dwelling in <placeName>Aldersgate street</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1617.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Two-page title, [par.]2v and [par.]3r.</note>
      <note>The first leaf is blank except for signature-mark "[par.]"; the last leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>In three parts, each with separate pagination; register is continuous.</note>
      <note>The contents of the parts on the second page of title is printed in roman. Variant: second page of title is a cancel, with the description of parts in italic.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      <note>Imperfect: first part of title, leaf [par.]2 lacking.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Iohn Beale</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Aldersgate street</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
