<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The picture of a papist: or, A relation of the damnable heresies, detestable qualities, and diabolicall practises of sundry hereticks in former ages, and of the papists in this age Where in is plainly shewed, that there is scarse any heresie which the auncient Church knew, and withal condemned to the pit of hell, which the Romish Church hath not raked vp againe, and propounded to the world with new varnish and fresh colours. Together with a discourse of the late treason, and of the late execution of some of the traitors ... Written to stop the mouthes of those, that complaine of rigour, and scandalize the state of cruelty, in their iust seueritie. Whereunto is annexed a certain treatise, intituled Pagano-pagismus: wherein is prooued by irrefragable demonstrations, that papisme is flat paganisme: and that the papists doe resemble the very pagans, in aboue seuenscore seuerall things.</title>
      <author>Ormerod, Oliver, 1580?-1626.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8], 83, 90-137, 168-203, 264-275, [1]; 56, 47-62 p. : ill. (woodcuts)  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed [by <persName type="printer">R. Bradock]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Nathaniel Fosbrooke</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop, at the west end of Paules</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1606.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Dedication signed: Oliuer Ormerod.</note>
      <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
      <note>"Pagano-papismus" (caption title) has separate register and pagination.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Nathaniel Fosbrooke</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>R. Bradock]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop, at the west end of Paules</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
