<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A true and plaine declaration of the horrible treasons, practised by William Parry the traitor, against the Queenes Maiestie The maner of his arraignment, conuiction and execution, together with the copies of sundry letters of his and others, tending to diuers purposes, for the proofes of his treasons. Also an addition not impertinent thereunto, containing a short collection of his birth, education and course of life. Moreouer, a fewe obseruations gathered of his owne wordes and wrytings, for the farther manifestation of his most disloyal, deuilish and desperate purpose.</title>
      <author>Parry, William, d. 1585.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 53, [1], 7, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">C. B[arker]</persName> Cum priuilegio,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
      <date>[1585]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Printer's name and publication date from STC.</note>
      <note>"A prayer for all kings, princes, countreyes and people, which doe professe the Gospel" (caption title) begins new pagination; register is continuous.</note>
      <note>In this state, title page line 7 ends "of his"; English letter on D2r begins "Monsignor, the Holines".</note>
      <note>Identified as STC 19341 on UMI microfilm reel 1325.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery and Cambridge University Library.</note>
      <note>Appears at reel 515 (Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery copy) and at reel 1325 (Cambridge University Library copy).</note>
      <note>Reel 1325: title page mutilated.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>C. B[arker]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
