<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A commemoration of the right noble and vertuous ladye, Margrit Duglasis good grace, Countis of Lennox daughter to the renowmed and most excellent Princesse Margrit, Queene of Scotland, espowsed to King Iames the fourth, of that name ... wherin is rehearsed hir godly life, her constancy and perfit pacience, in time of infortune her godly end, [and] last farewel, taken of al noble estates at the howre of her death. The ninth day of March. 1577. At her house of Hackney in the countie of Midlesex: and now lyeth enterred the thyrd of April, in the chappel of King Henry the seauenth her worthy grandfather. 1578. And anno. 20. of our soueraigne lady Qu&#233;ene Elizabeth, by Gods permission of England, Fraunce and Irelande Qu&#233;ene, [and]c.</title>
      <author>Phillips, John, fl. 1570-1591.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[32] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">Iohn Charlewood</persName>, dwelling in <placeName>Barbycan, at the signe of the halfe Eagle</placeName> and Key,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date>[1578]]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>By John Phillips, whose name appears on A2r.</note>
      <note>In verse.</note>
      <note>Printer's name and place of publication from colophon; publication date from STC.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A-D&#8308;.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: A freendly farewell geuen to honorable and vertuous ladies.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of a photostat of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Iohn Charlewood</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Barbycan, at the signe of the halfe Eagle</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
