<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The vvonderfull discouerie of witches in the countie of Lancaster VVith the arraignement and triall of nineteene notorious witches, at the assizes and general gaole deliuerie, holden at the castle of Lancaster, vpon Munday, the seuenteenth of August last, 1612. Before Sir Iames Altham, and Sir Edward Bromley, Knights; barons of his Maiesties Court of Exchequer: and iustices of assize, oyer and terminor, and generall gaole deliuerie in the circuit of the north parts. Together with the arraignement and triall of Iennet Preston, at the assizes holden at the castle of Yorke, the seuen and twentieth day of Iulie last past, with her execution for the murther of Master Lister by witchcraft. Published and set forth by commandement of his Maiesties iustices of assize in the north parts. By Thomas Potts Esquier.</title>
         <author>Potts, Thomas, fl. 1612-1618.</author>
         <author>Bromley, Edward, Sir.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[188] p. : ill. (woodcut)  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">W. Stansby</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Iohn Barnes</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop neare Holborne Conduit</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1613.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Editor's note signed: Edward Bromley.</note>
         <note>Signatures: pi&#8308; (-pi1) A-Z&#8308; (-Z4).</note>
         <note>Errata on A4r. Variant: last line of title reads "By T.P. Esquire."; A4r is blank.</note>
         <note>"The arraignement and triall of Iennet Preston" has separate title page dated 1612; register is continuous.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in University of Illinois (Urbana-Champaign Campus). Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Iohn Barnes</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>W. Stansby</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>his shop neare Holborne Conduit</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
