<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A godly treatise containing and deciding certaine questions, mooued of late in London and other places, touching the ministerie, sacraments, and Church Whereunto one proposition more is added. After the ende of this booke you shall finde a defence of such points as M. Penry hath dealt against: and a confutation of many grosse errours broched in M. Penries last treatise. Written by Robert Some Doctor of Diuinitie.</title>
         <author>Some, Robert, 1542-1609.</author>
         <author>Penry, John, 1559-1593. Defence of that which hath bin written in the questions of the ignorant ministerie, and the communicating with them.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[4], 36, [12], 53-200 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>By <persName type="printer">G[eorge] B[ishop] deputie to Christopher Barker</persName>, printer to <persName type="patron">the Queenes most excellent Maiestie</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1588.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A reply to: Penry, John.  An exhortation unto the governours and people of her Majesties countrie of Wales, to labour earnestly to have the preaching of the Gospell planted among them.</note>
         <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
         <note>"A defence of such points in R. Somes last treatise, as M. Penry hath dealt against" has separate dated title page; pagination and register are continuous. It reprints and replies to: Penry, John.  A defence of that which hath bin written in the questions of the ignorant ministerie, and the communicating with them.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Union Theological Seminary (New York, N.Y.). Library.</note>
         <note>Some print faded; some pages stained.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="patron"><persName>the Queenes most excellent Maiestie</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>G[eorge] B[ishop] deputie to Christopher Barker</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
