<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A bevvayling of the peace of Germany. Or, A discourse touching the Peace of Prague, no lesse unhappily than unjustly concluded at Prague in Bohemia, the 30. of May, 1635 Wherein the subtilties and practises of the Austrians, the weakenesse of the Saxons, the dangers of the protestants, and the justnesse of the warre, deservedly set on foot by the French and Swedes, are most evidently declared. Written in Latine by Iustus Asterius, otherwise Stella, a Germane, now one of the advocates in the Court of Parliament of Paris, and historiographer to the French King. Faithfully translated out of the Latine copie. Whereunto is prefixed a briefe summarie of the treaty of peace concluded at Prague, as aforesaid, &amp;c. Published by authority.</title>
         <title>Deploratio pacis Germanic&#230;. English</title>
         <author>Stella, Johannes.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[4], 28, [18], 129, 110-111, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">I[ohn] L[egat</persName> and <persName type="printer">Eliot's Court Press]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">I. H[unscott]</persName> and are to be sold in <placeName>Pauls Church-yard, at the signe of the golden Lyon [</placeName>by <persName type="printer">P. Stephens</persName> and <persName type="publisher">C. Meredith]</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1637.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A translation of: Stella, Johannes.  Deploratio pacis Germanic&#230;.</note>
         <note>Printers', publisher's, and booksellers' names from STC; "Eliot's Court Press pr[inted]. a-f&#8308;".</note>
         <note>The first leaf contains addenda and errata.</note>
         <note>&#178; A1 is a cancel (printed as f4); recto catchword is "at". Variant: A1 is cancellandum; catchword is "their".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Folger Shakespeare Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>C. Meredith]</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>I. H[unscott]</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>Eliot's Court Press]</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>I[ohn] L[egat</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>P. Stephens</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>Pauls Church-yard, at the signe of the golden Lyon [</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
