<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A collection of certaine learned discourses, written by that famous man of memory Zachary Ursine; doctor and professor of divinitie in the noble and flourishing schools of Neustad. For explication of divers difficult points, laide downe by that author in his catechisme. Lately put in print in Latin by the last labour of D. David Parry: and now newlie translated into English, by I.H. for the benefit and behoofe of our Christian country-man</title>
      <author>Ursinus, Zacharias, 1534-1583.</author>
      <author>I. H., fl. 1600.</author>
      <author>Pareus, David, 1548-1622. aut</author>
      <author>Junius, Franciscus, 1545-1602. aut</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8], 341 [i.e. 327], [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Ioseph Barnes</persName>, and are to be solde [by <persName type="bookseller">J. Broome</persName>, <persName type="bookseller">London]</persName> in <placeName>Pauls Church-yard at the signe of the Bible</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>At Oxford :</pubPlace>
      <date>1600.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Publisher from STC.</note>
      <note>Pages 180-91 and 236-37 missing in number only; 130, 131 and 177 misnumbered 132, 130 and 18.</note>
      <note>Includes "A funerale oration of D. Frances Junius, Professor of Divinity in the famous schoole of Neustade; vpon the death of D. Zachary Ursine, a most worthy man and vigilant Doctor of Divinity in the saide schoole of Neustade".</note>
      <note>Errata on verso of X4, final page.</note>
      <note>Also published under title: Certaine learned and excellent discourses: treating and discussing diures hard and difficult points of Christian religion.--NUC Pre 1956.</note>
      <note>Some print faded.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>J. Broome</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>London]</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Ioseph Barnes</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Pauls Church-yard at the signe of the Bible</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
