<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Concerning the excommunication of the Venetians a discourse against C&#230;sar Baronius Cardinall of the Church of Rome In which the true nature and vse of excommunication is briefly and cleerly demonstrated, both by testimonies of Holy Scripture, and from the old records of Christs Church. Written in Latine by Nicolas Vignier, and translated into English after the copie printed at Samur 1606. Whereunto is added the Bull of Pope Paulus the Fift, against the Duke, Senate and Commonwealth of Venice: with the protestation of the sayd Duke and Senate. As also an apologie of Frier Paul of the order of Serui in Venice.</title>
         <title>De Venetorum excommunicatione, adversus Caesarem Baronium. English</title>
         <author>Vignier, Nicolas.</author>
         <author>Sarpi, Paolo, 1552-1623. Apologia per le oppositioni fatte dall'illustrissimo &amp; reverendissimo signor cardinale Bellarminio alli trattati, et risolutioni di Gio. Gersone. English.</author>
         <author>Baronio, Cesare, 1538-1607. Duo vota. English.</author>
         <author>Catholic Church. Pope (1605-1621 : Paul V)</author>
         <author>Venice (Republic : to 1797). Doge (1606-1612 : Donato)</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 49, [1], 23, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">M[elchisidec] B[radwood]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">C[uthbert] B[urby]</persName> and are to be sold in <placeName>Pauls Church-yard at the signe of the White-swan</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1607.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A translation of: De Venetorum excommunicatione, adversus Caesarem Baronium.</note>
         <note>Printer's and publisher's names from STC.</note>
         <note>Includes a translation of and reply to: Baronio, Cesare. Duo vota.</note>
         <note>"The bull of Pope Paulus the Fift, against the common wealth and Senate of Venice" (caption title) begins new pagination on G3r.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>C[uthbert] B[urby]</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>M[elchisidec] B[radwood]</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>Pauls Church-yard at the signe of the White-swan</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
