<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The Englishemans treasure, or treasor for Englishmen vvith the true anatomye of mans body, compiled by that excellent chirurgion Maister Thomas Vicary Esquier Sergeant Chirurgion to King Henry the 8. to King Edward the 6. to Queene Mary. and to our soueraigne lady Queene Elizabeth. And also cheefe chirurgion to S. Bartholomewes hospitall. Whereunto are annexed many secrets appertaining to chirurgery, with diuers excellent approued remedies for all diseases the which are in man or woman, with emplasters of speciall cure with other potions and drinkes approued in phisike. Also the rare treasor of the English bathes, written by William Turner, Doctor in Phisicke. Gathered and set forth for the benefit of his friendes and countrimen in England by William Bremer practitioner in phisicke and chirurgery.</title>
         <title>Profitable treatise of the anatomie of mans body</title>
         <author>Vicary, Thomas, d. 1561.</author>
         <author>Turner, William, d. 1568. New herball. Part 2. Selections. aut</author>
         <author>Bremer, William.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[12], 60+ p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Imprinted by <persName type="printer">Iohn VVindet</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Iohn Perin</persName> dwelling in <placeName>Paules Church-yard at the signe of the Angell</placeName>, and are there to be sold,</publisher><pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1586.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A reprint, with additions, of: Vicary, Thomas.  A profitable treatise of the anatomie of mans body.</note>
         <note>Includes extracts from "A booke of the nature and properties, of the bathes in England", part 2 of "The seconde parte of William Turners herball".</note>
         <note>The first leaf is blank except for signature-mark "A.j.".</note>
         <note>Running title reads: A treasure for English men.</note>
         <note>Copy catalogued is incomplete.</note>
         <note>Lacking all after p. 60.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Iohn Perin</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>Iohn VVindet</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>Paules Church-yard at the signe of the Angell</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
