<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The waie home to Christ and truth leadinge from Antichrist and errour, made and set furth in the Latine tongue, by that famous and great clearke Vincent, French man borne, aboue .xi. hundred yeres paste, for the comforte of all true Christian men, against the most pernitious and detestable crafte of heretikes, which in his tyme by all subtell wayes, deuised to obscure and deface the doctrine and religion of the vniuersall churche. And now the same worke is englished, and by the Quenes highnes authorised to be sette furthe for the reliefe fo diuers Englishe menne, which yet stande in doubte, whether they may goe to heauen in the peace and vnitie of Christes vniuersall churche, or to hell in the dissention and confusion of heretikes</title>
         <title>Pro catholicae fidei antiquitate libellus. English</title>
         <author>Vincent, of L&#233;rins, Saint, d. ca. 450.</author>
         <author>Proctor, John, 1521?-1584.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[228] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>By <persName type="printer">Robert Caly</persName> within <placeName>the precincte of the late dissolued house of the graye freers, now conuerted to an hospitall, called Christes Hospitall</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>[Imprynted at London :</pubPlace>
         <date>the .xxii. daye of October. 1554]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A translation, by John Proctor, of: Saint Vincent of L&#233;rins.  Pro catholicae fidei antiquitate libellus.</note>
         <note>Imprint from colophon.</note>
         <note>With a final colophon leaf.</note>
         <note>Signatures: A-O P&#178; .</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Folger Shakespeare Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="printer"><persName>Robert Caly</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the precincte of the late dissolued house of the graye freers, now conuerted to an hospitall, called Christes Hospitall</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
