<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Novem. 24 Num. 7. The weekely newes containing these particulars. The surprising of tvvo tovvnes by the Prince of Oranges forces, and the manner of their taking, vvith the seuerall pasages of Spinolas armie lying before Breda, and our campe at Rosendale: as also the death of the Earl of Southampton and his sonne at Bergan-vp-Zomme. The taking of many places in the Grisons countrey by the French kings forces. Likewise the entertainment of many thousands of men by the State of Venice; vnder the command of Colonlel Ouentuant once one of Count Mansfields chiefe commanders. The Hollanders fortunately meeting with one of the King of Spaines plate ships comming from the West-Indies the which in a short time they ouercame and tooke: with a great victorie obtained by the Duke of Tuscans gallies, against the pirats of Argles. The disagreement which is like to happen betweene the emperour and Bethlem Gabor, and the Turke and the Emperour ...</title>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 20 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">W. I[ones]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Archer</persName> and are to be sold in <placeName>Popes head Ally, ouer against the signe of the Horse-shooe</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1624.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Print faded and show-through; some pages stained.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Thomas Archer</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>W. I[ones]</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>Popes head Ally, ouer against the signe of the Horse-shooe</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
