<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Sir Phillip Sidney, his honorable life, his valiant death, and true vertues A perfect myrror for the followers both of Mars and Mercury, who (in the right hardie breaking vpon the enemie, by a few of the English, being for the most part gentlemen of honor and name) receiued his deathes wound, nere vnto Sutphen the 22. of September last past, dyed at Aruam the 16. of October following: and with much honor and all possible mone, was solemnely buried in Paules the 16. of February 1586. By G.W. gent. Whereunto is adioyned, one other briefe commemoration of the vniuersall lamentation, the neuer dying praise, and most sollemne funerall of the sayd right hardie and noble knight. By B.W. Esquire. Dedicated, to the right Honorable the Earle of Warwicke, by his Lordships faithfull seruant George Whetstones.</title>
      <author>Whetstone, George, 1544?-1587?</author>
      <author>B. W. (Bernard Whetstone) aut</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[22] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>[By <persName type="printer">T. Orwin]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Cadman</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date>[1587]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>B.W. = Bernard Whetstone.</note>
      <note>In verse.</note>
      <note>Printer's name and publication date from STC.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A-C&#8308; (-A1).</note>
      <note>Running title reads: The life, death, and vertues of Sir Phillip Sidney Knight.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of a photostat of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Cadman</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>T. Orwin]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
