<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Propositions made by Monsieur Vander Hurst at the assembly of the Generall States of the Vnited Prouinces vpon the 13. of Ianuarie, 1608 With the answer of the sayd Generall States giuen vnto the sayd Monsieur Vander Hurst, touching the said propositions. And also a declaration made and sent by the said States Generall vnto all the prouinces and townes vnder their gouernment, touching peace to be made: printed 1608. The finall answer made by the said Generall States of the Vnited Prouinces vnto the Commissioners for the King of Spaine and the Archduke, assembled in the Hague, concerning peace to be made, 1608.</title>
      <title>Propositie vanden Heere vander Horst, ghedaen ende ghepresenteert ter vergaderinge vande ... Staten der Vereenighde Nederlanden den xiiien. Januarii 1607. English</title>
      <author>Wittenhorst, Walraven van, d. 1623.</author>
      <author>United Provinces of the Netherlands. Staten Generaal.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 18, [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed [by <persName type="printer">Melchisidec Bradwood]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Philip Harison</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop in Corn-hill ouer-against the Exchange</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1609.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of: Wittenhorst, Walraven van. Propositie vanden Heere vander Horst, ghedaen ende ghepresenteert ter vergaderinge vande .. Staten der Vereenighde Nederlanden den xiiien. Januarii 1607.</note>
      <note>The speech was actually given in 1607; see Knuttel 1360, 1529a.</note>
      <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
      <note>The first leaf is blank except for signature-mark "A"; the last leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in Yale University. Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Philip Harison</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Melchisidec Bradwood]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop in Corn-hill ouer-against the Exchange</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
