<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The true difference betweene Christian subiection and unchristian rebellion wherein the princes lawfull power to commaund for trueth, and indepriuable right to beare the sword are defended against the Popes censures and the Iesuits sophismes vttered in their apologie and defence of English Catholikes: with a demonstration that the thinges refourmed in the Church of England by the lawes of this realme are truely Catholike, notwithstanding the vaine shew made to the contrary in their late Rhemish Testament: by Thomas Bilson warden of Winchester. Perused and allowed publike authoritie.</title>
         <author>Bilson, Thomas, 1546 or 7-1616.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[24], 430, [2]; 686, [10] pages   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Ioseph Barnes</persName> printer to <persName type="patron">the Vniuersitie</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>At Oxford :</pubPlace>
         <date>MDXXCV. [1585]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A reply to William Allen's "An apologie and true declaration of the institution and endevours of the two English colleges" and "A true, sincere, and modest defence of English Catholiques that suffer for their faith both at home and abrode".</note>
         <note>In three parts, the third with separate pagination and register.</note>
         <note>The first leaf is blank except for signature-mark "*1".</note>
         <note>At least quire 3X is in two settings; 2X1r line 1 ends (1) "of" or (2) "Car".</note>
         <note>With five final contents leaves.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="patron"><persName>the Vniuersitie</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>Ioseph Barnes</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
