<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A defence of the olde, and true profession of Christianitie against the new, and counterfaite secte of Iesuites, or fellowship of Iesus: Written in Latine by P. Boquine a Frenchman, borne in Borges, &amp; Professor of Diuinitie, in the Vniuersitie of Heidelberge: Translated into Englishe by T. G. Whereby maye bee perceiued, howe falslye the Iesuites vsurpe the name of Iesus, and how farre off they are, from the thing signified thereby, and what their profession, and purpose is in truth: otherwise then they beare the worlde in hande.</title>
         <title>Assertio veteris ac veri Christianismi adversus novum et fictum Iesuitismum seu Societatem Iesu. English</title>
         <author>Boquin, Pierre, d. 1582.</author>
         <author>T. G., fl. 1581.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[32], 165, [3] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Imprinted by <persName type="printer">Iohn Wolf</persName>, and <persName type="printer">Henry Kirkham</persName>, and are to be solde at <placeName>the little North dore of Paules at the signe of the Blacke Boy</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>[1581]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A translation of Boquin, Pierre.  Assertio veteris ac veri Christianismi adversus novum et fictum Iesuitismum seu Societatem Iesu.</note>
         <note>First two and last leaves blank?.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
         <note>Year of publication from STC.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="printer"><persName>Henry Kirkham</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>Iohn Wolf</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the little North dore of Paules at the signe of the Blacke Boy</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
