<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The complaynt of veritie, made by Iohn Bradford. An exhortacion of Mathewe Rogers, vnto his children. The complaynt of Raufe Allerton and others, being prisoners in Lolers tower, &amp; wrytten with their bloud, how god was their comforte. A songe of Caine and Abell. The saieng of maister Houper, that he wrote the night before he suffered, vppon a wall with a cole, in the newe In, at Gloceter, and his saiyng at his deathe</title>
         <author>Bradford, John, 1510?-1555.</author>
         <author>Rogers, Matthew. Instruction of a father to his children.</author>
         <author>Allerton, Ralph. A lamentable complaynt of the afflicted, unto god our onely healper.</author>
         <author>Allerton, Ralph. A briefe rehersal of parte of the aucthours trouble, entituled God is my comforte.</author>
         <author>Allerton, Ralph. Songe of the poore prisoners in Lolers tower.</author>
         <author>Hooper, John, d. 1555. Wordes of Maister Houper at his death.</author>
         <author>Hooper, John, d. 1555. These are the wordes that Maister John Houper wrote on the wall with a cole, in the newe inne in Gloceter, the night before he suffered.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[32] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>John Day? for <persName type="publisher">Owen Rogers?]</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
         <date>Anno Domini. 1559.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Includes Bradford, John.  The complaynt of veritie; Rogers, Matthew.  The instruction of a father to his children; Allerton, Ralph.  A lamentable complaynt of the afflicted, vnto god our onely healper; Allerton, Ralph. A briefe rehersal of parte of the aucthours trouble, entituled God is my comforte; Allerton, Ralph (and others).  The songe of the poore prisoners in Lolers tower; Hooper, John.  The wordes of Maister Houper at his death; and Hooper, John.  These are the wordes that Maister John Houper wrote on the wall with a cole, in the newe inne in Gloceter, the night before he suffered.</note>
         <note>Printer and vendor suggested by STC.</note>
         <note>Signatures: A-B.</note>
         <note>All in verse except "The wordes of Maister Houper at his death".</note>
         <note>B6 verso heading: "Houper"--STC.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Owen Rogers?]</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
