<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Two godly and learned sermons, made by that famous and woorthy instrument in Gods church, M. Iohn Caluin. Which sermons were long since translated out of Latine into English, by M. Robert Horne late Byshop of Winchester, at what time he suffered exile from his country, for the testimony of a good conscience, as his apology in the beginning of the booke will witnes. And because these sermons haue long lyen hidden in silence, and many godly and religious persons, haue beene very desirous of them: at theyr earnest request they are nowe published by A.M.</title>
         <title>Quatre sermons. English. Selections</title>
         <author>Calvin, Jean, 1509-1564.</author>
         <author>Horne, Robertc1519?-1580.</author>
         <author>Munday, Anthony, 1553-1633.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[152] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed [by <persName type="printer">John Charlewood]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Henry Car</persName>, and are to be sold in <placeName>Paules Churchyard, ouer against the signe of the blasing starre</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
         <date>[1584]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A translation by Robert Horne of two sermons from: Quatre sermons. Edited by Anthony Munday.</note>
         <note>A.M. = Anthony Munday.</note>
         <note>Publication date from title page verso; printer's name from STC.</note>
         <note>Includes Horne's apology (leaves B1-D5).</note>
         <note>Caption title (leaf B1 recto) reads: The apologie of Maister Robert Horne, late Bishop of VVinchester ..</note>
         <note>Signatures: A&#8308; B-K.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Cambridge University Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Henry Car</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>John Charlewood]</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>Paules Churchyard, ouer against the signe of the blasing starre</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
