<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Virginia's God be thanked, or A sermon of thanksgiving for the happie successe of the affayres in Virginia this last yeare. Preached by Patrick Copland at Bow-Church in Cheapside, before the Honorable Virginia Company, on Thursday, the 18. of Aprill 1622. And now published by the commandement of the said honorable Company. Hereunto are adjoyned some epistles, written first in Latine (and now Englished) in the East Indies by Peter Pope, an Indian youth, borne in the bay of Bengala, who was first taught and converted by the said P.C. And after baptized by Master Iohn Wood, Dr in Divinitie, in a famous assembly before the Right Worshipfull, the East India Company, at S. Denis in Fan-Church streete in London, December 22. 1616</title>
         <author>Copland, Patrick, ca. 1570-ca. 1655.</author>
         <author>Pope, Peter, fl. 1622.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[6], 36, [8] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">I[ohn] D[awson]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">William Sheffard</persName> and <persName type="publisher">Iohn Bellamie</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop at the two Grey-hounds in Corne-hill, neere the Royall Exchange</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1622.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
         <note>The epistles by Peter Pope, with caption title "To the most illustrious knight, Sir Thomas Smith ..", have separate register. They include the Latin originals.</note>
         <note>The last leaf is blank.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Iohn Bellamie</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>William Sheffard</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>I[ohn] D[awson]</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>his shop at the two Grey-hounds in Corne-hill, neere the Royall Exchange</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
