<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A treatise of the Fift General Councel held at Constantinople, anno 553. under Iustinian the Emperor, in the time of Pope Vigilius. The occasion being those tria capitula, which for many yeares troubled the whole Church. VVherein is proved that the Popes apostolicall constitution and definitive sentence, in matter of faith, was condemned as hereticall by the Synod. And the exceeding frauds of Cardinall Baronius and Binius are clearely discovered. By Rich: Crakanthorp Dr. in Divinity, and chapleine in ordinary to his late Majestie King Iames. Opus posthumum. Published and set forth by his brother Geo: Crakanthorp, according to a perfect copy found written under the authors owne hand</title>
         <title>Vigilius dormitans</title>
         <author>Crakanthorpe, Richard, 1567-1624.</author>
         <author>Crakanthorpe, George, b. 1586 or 7.</author>
         <author>Crakanthorpe, Richard, 1567-1624. Justinian the Emperor defended, against Cardinal Baronius.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[24], 506, [10] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed [by <persName type="printer">Miles Flesher]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">R[obert] M[ilbourne] 1634. And part of the impression made over, to be vented</persName> for <persName type="publisher">the benefit of the children of Iohn Minshew, deceased</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>[1634]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A reissue, with cancel title page, of: Vigilius dormitans.</note>
         <note>Printer's and publisher's names from STC.</note>
         <note>The first leaf is blank.</note>
         <note>Includes index.</note>
         <note>Chapter 20 was published separately in 1616 as "Justinian the Emperor defended, against Cardinal Baronius".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>R[obert] M[ilbourne] 1634. And part of the impression made over, to be vented</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>the benefit of the children of Iohn Minshew, deceased</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>Miles Flesher]</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
