<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A plaine path-vvay to plantations that is, a discourse in generall, concerning the plantation of our English people in other countries. Wherein is declared, that the attempts or actions, in themselues are very good and laudable, necessary also for our country of England. Doubts thereabout are answered: and some meanes are shewed, by which the same may, in better sort then hitherto, be prosecuted and effected. Written for the perswading and stirring vp of the people of this land, chiefly the poorer and common sort to affect and effect these attempts better then yet they doe. With certaine motiues for a present plantation in New-found land aboue the rest. Made in the manner of a conference, and diuided into three parts, for the more plainnesse, ease, and delight to the reader. By Richard Eburne of Hengstridge in the countie of Somerset.</title>
         <author>Eburne, Richard.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[20], 80, [2], 89-120, [2] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">G[eorge] P[urslowe]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Iohn Marriot</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
         <date>1624.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
         <note>Parts 2 and 3 have separate title pages; pagination and register are continuous.</note>
         <note>The last leaf is blank.</note>
         <note>Running title reads: The path-way to plantations ..</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Iohn Marriot</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>G[eorge] P[urslowe]</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
