<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The warnings of the Lord to the men of this generation particularly, to those in power, who are lately past away, ere they so passed; and to them that remain, who are* ready to passe except they speedily repent. As they were given forth in sundry letters, and sent to Oliver Cromwel, Richard his son, late Protectors. The Parrliament [sic] succeeding. The council of officers of the Army. The Council of State. A Member of the Parliament and Council of State, and Committee of Safety. The general council of the officers of the Army a citizen of London, and one of the commissioners of the militia there. By his servant George Bishop. Who is moved of the Lord (now) to publish them, ... Whereunto is added, The burden of Dumah upon occasion of this query, sent in a letter by one related to the Army, viz. - Watchman! What of the night? Watchman! What of the night?</title>
         <author>Bishop, George, d. 1668.</author>
         <author>Cromwell, Oliver, 1599-1658, recipient.</author>
         <author>Cromwell, Richard, 1626-1712, recipient.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 44 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">M. Inman</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>the Three Bibles in Pauls Church-yard</placeName>, and by <persName type="bookseller">Richard Moon</persName>, bookseller in <placeName>Windstreet in Bristol</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1660.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>The asterisk in title refers to printed marginal note: 17th. of the 10th. mon. 1659. The words "Oliver Cromwell, .. his son," are joined by a right brace with the words "late Protectors." to right; the words "Oliver Cromwel, .. militia there." are joined by a left bracket.</note>
         <note>Copy stained with heavy print show-through.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="printer"><persName>M. Inman</persName></person><person type="bookseller"><persName>Richard Moon</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>Windstreet in Bristol</placeName></place><place type="location"><placeName>the Three Bibles in Pauls Church-yard</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
