<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>New experiments physico-mechanical, touching the air</title>
         <title>New experiments physico-mechanical, touching the spring of the air, and its effects</title>
         <author>Boyle, Robert, 1627-1691.</author>
         <author>Sharrock, Robert, 1630-1684.</author>
         <author>Boyle, Robert, 1627-1691. Defence of the doctrine touching the spring and weight of the air.</author>
         <author>Boyle, Robert, 1627-1691. Examen of Mr. T. Hobbes his Dialogus physicus de natur&#226; a&#235;ris.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <editionStmt>
         <edition>The third edition : whereunto is added a defence of the author's explication of the experiments, against the objections of Franciscus Linus and, Thomas Hobbs.</edition>
      </editionStmt>
      <extent>[16], 203, [12], 117, [8], 102, [2] p., 2 leaves of plates (1 folded) ;  21 cm. </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Miles Flesher</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Richard Davis</persName>, bookseller in <placeName>Oxford</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1682]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Title taken from half-title. Each of the three works has special t. p. and separate paging; the third has separate signatures.</note>
         <note>Contains the first formulation of Boyle's law.</note>
         <note>"A catalogue of all the philosophical works published by our author": p. [1]-[2] at end.</note>
         <note>Edited by Robert Sharrock.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in Huntington Library.</note>
         <note>New experiments physico-mechanical, touching the spring of the air, and its effects, made, for the most part, in a new pnuematical [sic] engine : written by way of letter to the Right Honorable Charles Lord Vicount of Dungarvan, eldest son to the Earl of Corke / by the Honorable Robert Boyle Esq. -- A defence of the doctrine touching the spring and weight of the air, propos'd by Mr. R. Boyle in his New physico-mechanical experiments, against the objections of Franciscus Linus : wherewith the objector's funicular hypothesis is also examin'd / by the author of those experiments -- An examen of Mr. T. Hobbs his Dialogus physicus de natur&#226; a&#235;ris, as far as it concerns Mr. Boyle's book of New experiments touching the spring of the air, &amp;c. : with an appendix touching Mr. Hobbs's doctrine of fluidity and firmness / by the author of those experiments.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Richard Davis</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>Miles Flesher</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>Oxford</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
