<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Two treatises the one medical, Of the gout and its nature more narrowly search'd into than hitherto, together with a new way of discharging the same / by Herman Busschof ; the other partly chirurgical, partly medical containing Some observations and practices relating both to some extraordinary cases of women in travel, and to some other uncommon cases of diseases in both sexes by Henry Van Roonhuysen ... ; Englished out of Dutch by a careful hand.</title>
      <author>Busschof, Hermann. Of the gout.</author>
      <author>Busschof, Hermann. Of the gout and its nature more narrowly search'd into than hitherto, together with a new way of discharging the same.</author>
      <author>Busschof, Hermann. Gout more narrowly searcht and found out, together with the certain cure thereof.</author>
      <author>Busschof, Hermann. Podagra, nader als oyt nagevorst enytgevonden.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[12], 136, [6], 208, [4] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">H. C.</persName> and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Moses Pitts</persName> ...,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1676.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Imperfect: Medico-chirurgical observations is lacking on film.</note>
      <note>First treatise is a translation of: Podagra, nader als oyt nagevorst enuytgevonden.</note>
      <note>First treatise has a running title: Of the gout.</note>
      <note>First treatise title variation: The gout more narrowly searcht and found out, together with the certain cure thereof.</note>
      <note>Second treatise has a separate t.p.: Medico-chirurgical observations / by Henry Van Ronhuyse.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in Bodleian Library.</note>
      <note>The gout more narrowly searcht and found out, together with the certain cure thereof / Hermann Busschof -- Some observations and practices relating both to some extraordinary cases of women in travel, and to some other uncommon cases of diseases in both sexes / Henry Van Roonhuyse.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Moses Pitts</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>H. C.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
