<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The admirable and glorious appearance of the eternal God, in his glorious power, in and through a child of the age of betwixt eight and nine years, upon her dying bed, opening her mouth to speak forth his praise, and extol his reverent holy name and power: a short relation whereof, together with her exercise throughout her sickness, is hereafter collected, or so much thereof as was by us certainly remembred.</title>
      <author>Camm, Thomas, 1641-1707.</author>
      <author>Camm, Anne, 1627-1705. aut</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>8 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">John Bringhurst</persName> at <placeName>the sign of the Book</placeName> and Three Black-Birds in <placeName>Leaden-Hall-Mutton-Market</placeName>, <placeName>(who formerly lived at <placeName>the sign of the Book</placeName> in Grace-Church-street.</placeName>),</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1684]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Signed at end: Camsgill in Westmoreland, the 12th of the 8th moneth, 1682. Thomas Camme, and Anne Camme. Father and mother of the said Sarah Camme.</note>
      <note>Caption title.</note>
      <note>Imprint from colophon.</note>
      <note>Recounts the last words of Thomas and Anne Camm's daughter, Sarah, who "dyed in the ninth year of her age, wanting about eleven dayes of nine years, being the 18th day of the 7th moneth, in the year 1682".</note>
      <note>Identified as Wing A585A on UMI microfilm set "Early English books, 1641-1700", reel 2204.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the Friends House Library, London (reel 1863) and the Haverford College Library (reel 2204).</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>John Bringhurst</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>(who formerly lived at the sign of the Book in Grace-Church-street.</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Leaden-Hall-Mutton-Market</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the sign of the Book</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
