<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Truth defended. or, A triple answer to the late triumvirates opposition in their three pamphlets viz. Mr. Baxter's review, Mr. Wills his censure, Mr. Whiston's postscript to his essay, &amp;c. With Mr. Hutchinson's letter to Mr. Baxter a little before his death. And a postscript in answer to Mr. William Walker's modest plea for infants baptism. By Tho. DeLaune.</title>
         <author>De Laune, Thomas, d. 1685.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[14+]; 21, [7], 24, [2], 34, [2]; 31, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">the author</persName>, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Francis Smith</persName> at <placeName>the Elephant</placeName> and Castle near <placeName>the Royal Exchange</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>[S.l.] :</pubPlace>
         <date>1677.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A reply to Whiston, Joseph.  An essay to revive the primitive doctrine; Wills, Obed.  Vindic&#230; vindiciarum; and Baxter, Richard. Review of the state of Christian's infants.</note>
         <note>"A brief survey and confutation of Mr. Joseph Whistons books of baptism", "A just reproof to the clamorous cavils of Mr. Obed Wills, the turbulent appealer", and "Mr. Richard Baxter's review of the state of Christian infants, examined" have separate dated title pages; register is continuous. The "Postscript in answer to Mr. Walker's modest plea" has caption title and register is separate.</note>
         <note>Text continuous despite pagination.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>the author</persName></person><person type="bookseller"><persName>Francis Smith</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the Elephant</placeName></place><place type="location"><placeName>the Royal Exchange</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
