<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A Fifth collection of papers relating to the present juncture of affairs in England</title>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 24, 8, 33-34 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Rich. Janeway</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London,</pubPlace>
         <date>1688.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Fifth in a series of twelve collections issued in 1688 under the general title: A collection of papers relating to the present juncture of affairs in England; and reissued in 1689 under title: A compleat collection of papers, in twelve parts, relating to the great revolutions in England and Scotland.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
         <note>Includes bibliographical references.</note>
         <note>(from t.p.) I. The hard case of Protestant subjects under the dominion of a popish Prince -- II. An answer to a late pamphlet, entitled, A short scheme of the usurpations of the Crown of England, &amp;c. -- III. An humble and hearty address to all English Protestants in the army / published by Mr. Johnson in the year 1686 -- IV. Several reasons against the establishment of a standing army, and dissolving the militia -- V. A discourse of magistracy, of prerogative by divine right, of obedience, and of the laws -- VI. The definition of a tyrant, by Abr. Cowley : with several queries thereupon proposed to the lawyers -- VII. A letter to the King inducing him to adhere to the Protestant religion -- VIII. Ten seasonable queries, proposed by an English gentleman at Amsterdam to his friends in England.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="bookseller"><persName>Rich. Janeway</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
