<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>An account of several new inventions and improvements now necessary for England, in a discourse by way of letter to the Earl of Marlborough, relating to building of our English shipping, planting of oaken timber in the forrests, apportioning of publick taxes, the conservacy of all our royal rivers, in particular that of the Thames, the surveys of the Thames, &amp;c. : Herewith is also published at large The proceedings relating to mill'd-lead-sheathing, and the excellency and cheapness of mill'd-Lead in preference to cast sheet-lead for all other purposes whatsoever. : Also A treatise of naval philosophy, / written by Sir Will. Petty. ; The whole is submitted to the consideration of our English patriots in Parliament assembled.</title>
      <author>T. H. (Thomas Hale)</author>
      <author>Petty, William, Sir, 1623-1687. A treatise of naval philosophy.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[12], CXXV, [16], 132 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">James Astwood</persName>, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Ralph Simpson</persName> at <placeName>the Harp in St. Paul's Churchyard.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date>MDCXCI [1691].</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"An account of several new inventions" signed at end: T.H.</note>
      <note>"A treatise of naval philosophy" has separate pagination.</note>
      <note>2559:5a lacks "A table of some of the principal matters contained in the following letter to the Earl of Marlborough" (p. [2-12] of 1403:23).</note>
      <note>"A survey of the encroachments of the river Thames" follows p. 132 of 1403:23. It follows p. [16] of 2559:5a.</note>
      <note>1403:23 is a reproduction of original in the University of Illinois (Urbana-Champaign Campus). Library.</note>
      <note>2559:5a is a reproduction of original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
      <note>2559:5a bound with: Advertisem[ent] To all who have Occasion to make Use of Sheet-Lead. London : Printed for T.H. ..., [1690].</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>James Astwood</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Ralph Simpson</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Harp in St. Paul's Churchyard.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
