<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Short and plaine animadversions on some passages in Mr. Dels sermon first preached before the Honourable House of Commons on Novemb. 25. 1646. But since printed without their order Setting forth the many dangerous and destructive assertions therein both to church and state, the covenant, and the reformation so much desired. Together, with an answer to an unlicensed pamphlet annext to the sermon, entituled, A reply to Master Loves contradictions. By Christopher Love minister of Anne Aldersgate, London. The second edition. Imprimatur Ja. Cranford. Decemb. 17. 1646.</title>
         <author>Love, Christopher, 1618-1651.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <editionStmt>
         <edition>The second edition.</edition>
      </editionStmt>
      <extent>[6], 33, [1], 33-44 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">R. Cotes</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">Iohn Bellamie</persName> at <placeName>the three Golden Lions in Cornhill, neer the Royall Exchange</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1647.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A reply to: Dell, William.  Right reformation.</note>
         <note>"A short answer to an unlicensed pamphlet, entituled, A reply to the chiefe contradictions of Master Love's sermon" has caption title on E3r; register and pagination are continous.</note>
         <note>Text and register are continuous despite pagination.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Cambridge University Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Iohn Bellamie</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>R. Cotes</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the three Golden Lions in Cornhill, neer the Royall Exchange</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
