<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A trumpet sounded out of the wilderness of America which may serve as a warning to the government and people of England to beware of Quakerisme. Wherein is shewed the great contradictions of the Quakers, both in their former and later writings. Also how they deny Jesus of Nazareth to be the Christ. And how in Pensilvania and there-away, where they have the government in their own hands, they hire and encourage men to fight; and how they persecute, fine, imprison, and take away goods for conscience sake. Notwithstanding they formerly exclaimed against the government of England, &amp;c. for the same things. Setting forth likewise there base temporizing with whatever government is uppermost, &amp;c. By Daniel Leeds.</title>
         <author>Leeds, Daniel, 1652-1720.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[14], 151, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">William Bradford</persName> at <placeName>the Bible in New-York;</placeName> and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">B. Aylmer</persName> at <placeName>the Three Pidgeons in Cornhill</placeName>, and <persName type="bookseller">C. Brome</persName> at <placeName>the Gun at the west-end of St. Paul's London</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
         <date>1699.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A reissue, with cancel title page, of the 1697 New York edition printed by Bradford.</note>
         <note>"1699 t.p. probably printed in London"--Bristol.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="printer"><persName>William Bradford</persName></person><person type="bookseller"><persName>B. Aylmer</persName></person><person type="bookseller"><persName>C. Brome</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the Bible in New-York;</placeName></place><place type="location"><placeName>the Gun at the west-end of St. Paul's London</placeName></place><place type="location"><placeName>the Three Pidgeons in Cornhill</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
