<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Matters of great consequence, and worthy of note to all England first the royall embassage from the Prince of Orange, to the well affected subjects of England : secondly, a message from a committee of both Houses of Parliament, to the Spanish embassador to make stay of the ships at Dunkerk, which were intended for the supply of the rebels in Ireland : thirdly, the true and humble petition of the Lords and Commons now assembled in Parliament, to the Kings most Excellent Majesty : concerning the Lord Kimbolton, M. Hollis, and the rest of the gentlemen that were accused of high treason : fourthly, an order of the House of the Lords for suppressing of the Arch-bishop of Armaghs sermon, which was falsely put upon him : fiftly, articles against Sir Edward Herbert Knight, His Majesties attorney generall, by the House of Commons : sixtly, an ordinance from His Majesty, and both Houses of Parliament, for the ordering of the militia of the kingdome of England, and also of the dominion of Wales : lastly, the names of all the lievtenants of every country, which are approved by the Kings Majesty.</title>
         <author>Ussher, James, 1581-1656.</author>
         <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed at <placeName>London</placeName>, for <persName type="publisher">F. Coules</persName> and <persName type="publisher">Tho. Bankes</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1641.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Illustrated t.p.</note>
         <note>Imperfect: edges cropped.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in Thomason Collection, British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>F. Coules</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>Tho. Bankes</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>London</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
