<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The famous history of the life of the renowned Prince Palmerin of England: or, The glory of knightly prowess In three parts. Containing his parentage, birth, education, travels, strange adventures, noble exploits and victories; combats with monsters, gyants, armies, and armed knights, dissolving inchantments, delivering distressed ladies; and his success in love. The whole being a compleat series, inter-woven with the heroick actions of many valiant emperours, kings, princes, and knights of undoubted fame, whose matchless deeds have won them immortal honour. A book worthy the perusal of either sex. Written originally in French; and now faithfully done into English (for the better satisfaction of the reader) by J.S.</title>
      <title>Palmerin of England (Romance). Part 2. English.</title>
      <author>Morais, Francisco de, ca. 1500-1572, attributed name.</author>
      <author>J. S.</author>
      <author>Hurtado, Luis, ca. 1510-ca. 1598, attributed name.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 190 p. : ill., frontis.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">William Thackeray</persName>, in <placeName>Duck-Lane</placeName> and <persName type="publisher">Thomas Passinger</persName> on <placeName>London-Bridge</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>MDCLXXXV. [1685]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of part 2 of: Cr&#243;nica de Palmeirim de Inglaterra.</note>
      <note>Has no connection with the Palladine of England romances with which it has often been confused. Cf. Thomas, H. Biblio. Soc. Trans., v. 13, p. 128.</note>
      <note>Sometimes attributed to Francisco de Morais and to Luis Hurtado.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Harvard University Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Passinger</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>William Thackeray</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Duck-Lane</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>London-Bridge</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
