<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A good-work for bad times, or, A way to make England rich and happy shewing how the charge of the war if it should continue may be born without any tax or pressure to the subject, and all the poor and idle persons in this nation may be employed or set to work, by which the nation will gain more than double the charge of the war as is herein plainly set forth, and the poor of all sorts that are not able to get their living by their work may be better maintain'd than now they are, without begging, and the children be brought up to work and taught to read, write and cast accompts, and be virtuously educated so as they may be serviceable to the nation : and also money will be made plenty and trade brisk, and some, amongst a great many, of the vast advantages that will accrue to the nation by it are here set forth : most humbly dedicated to the consideration of His Majesty and the Parliament / by G. Malkin.</title>
      <author>Malkin, G. (Gilbert)</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 8 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">D.E.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">the author</persName> and sold by <persName type="bookseller">E. Whitlock</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1697]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Advocates the establishment of a national bank and work houses for the employment of the poor.</note>
      <note>Running title: A remedy for the worst of times.</note>
      <note>Imprint from NUC pre-1956.</note>
      <note>Advertisement on p. 8.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in Huntington Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>the author</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>E. Whitlock</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>D.E.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
