<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Father Malebranche his treatise concerning the search after truth The whole work complete. To which is added the author's Treatise of nature and grace: being a consequence of the principles contained in the search. Together with his answer to the animadversions upon the first volume: his defence against the accusations of Monsieur De la Ville, &amp;c. relating to the same subject. All translated by T. Taylor, M.A. late of Magdalen College in Oxford.</title>
      <author>Malebranche, Nicolas, 1638-1715.</author>
      <author>Taylor, Thomas, 1669 or 70-1735.</author>
      <author>Malebranche, Nicolas, 1638-1715. Trait&#233; de la nature et de la grace. English.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <editionStmt>
      <edition>The second edition, corrected with great exactness. With the addition, of A short discourse upon light and colours, by the same author. Communicated in manuscript to a person of quality in England: and never before printed in any language.</edition>
    </editionStmt>
    <extent>[12], 40, 168, 8, 159, 170-196 p. : ill.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">W. Bowyer</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Bennet</persName> at <placeName>the Half-Moon</placeName>, and T. Leigh and <persName type="publisher">W. Midwinter</persName> at <placeName>the Rose</placeName> and Crown, in <placeName>St. Paul's Church-yard</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1700.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation, by Thomas Taylor, of: Malebranche, Nicolas.  Recherche de la v&#233;rit&#233;.</note>
      <note>Another "second" edition has "D. Midwinter" in imprint.</note>
      <note>Text continuous despite pagination.</note>
      <note>"A treatise concerning nature and grace" has divisional title page, and separate pagination and register.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original at the Union Theological Seminary Library, New York.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Bennet</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>W. Midwinter</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>W. Bowyer</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>St. Paul's Church-yard</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Half-Moon</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Rose</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
