<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A compleat history and mystery of the Old and New Testament logically discust and theologically improved : in four volumes ... the like undertaking (in such a manner and method) being never by any author attempted before : yet this is now approved and commended by grave divines, &amp;c. / by Christopher Ness ...</title>
         <author>Ness, Christopher, 1621-1705.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[6], 468, 120, 368 [i.e. 360], [2], 369-755, [45], 524 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Thomas Snowden</persName>, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Tho. Parkhurst</persName> ... and <persName type="bookseller">Jonathan Robinson</persName> ...,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1696.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Vols. 3 and 4 have special t.p.'s, with 1695 and 1696 imprint dates respectively.</note>
         <note>Vols. 1 and 4 have separate paging and signatures; vols. 2-3 are paged and signed continuously.</note>
         <note>"Probably made up partially of remainder sheets of the separate volumes; v. 1 first published in 1690, v. 2-3 in 1695, and v.4 in 1696"--NUC pre-1956 imprints.</note>
         <note>Vols. 1, 2, and 4 are listed in Wing and are cataloged separately.</note>
         <note>Errata: p. [5] of the 7th page count.</note>
         <note>Advertisements: p. [26] and [39] of 7th page count.</note>
         <note>Numerous errors in paging.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the Harvard University Library.</note>
         <note>(from t.p.) The first, beginning at the creation of the world, and ending at Moses -- The second, beginning at the particular remarks of Israel's motions and mansions in the wilderness, until the death of Moses, and the succession of Joshua, and so forward unto the birth of Solomon -- The third, beginning at David's repentance, before the birth of Solomon, and ending at the birth of Christ, wherein an ample account is given of all the apocryphal times (betwixt Malachy and the Messiah) also, as well as of all the canonical books until that time -- The fourth, beginning at the first of Matthew, and ending at the last of the Revelations, wherein is held forth the most illustrious life of Christ, and the lives of all the apostles, to the death of the last and longest living apostle John the Divine.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="printer"><persName>Thomas Snowden</persName></person><person type="bookseller"><persName>Jonathan Robinson</persName></person><person type="bookseller"><persName>Tho. Parkhurst</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
