<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>An exact and faithful narrative of the horrid conspiracy of Thomas Knox, William Osborne, and John Lane, to invalidate the testimonies of Dr. Titus Oates, and Mr. William Bedlow by charging them with a malicious contrivance against the E. of Danby, and the said Dr. Oates with an attempt of sodomy wherein are exemplified from the originals I. Four forged letters dictated by Thomas Knox, II. Five false informations, one paper of memorials, and one other information against Dr. Oates for sodomy, forged by Knox in the names of Lane and Osborne, III. The informations, depositions, examinations, and confessions of the said Knox, Osborne, and Lane, taken upon oath before Sir William Waller and Edmund Warcup, Esq., IV. An account of some depositions taken before the Lords Committees of Secresie, relating thereunto, V. The breviates of the councel for the King at the trials of the said Knox and Lane, Nov. 25, 1679, wherein full satisfaction is given to the world of the whole cause, by the particular evidences of the witnesses in behalf of the King / published by the appointment of me, Titus Oates.</title>
         <author>Oates, Titus, 1649-1705.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[7], 36 [i.e. 28] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Tho. Parkhurst</persName>, <persName type="publisher">Tho. Cockerill</persName> and <persName type="publisher">Benj. Alsop</persName> ...,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1680.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>First edition?</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in Duke University Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Benj. Alsop</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>Tho. Cockerill</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>Tho. Parkhurst</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
