<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The Popish royall favourite: or, a full discovery of His Majesties extraordinary favours to, and protections of notorious papists, priestes, Jesuites, against all prosecutions and penalties of the laws enacted against them notwithstanding his many royall proclamations, declarations, and protestations to the contrary: as likewise of a most desperate long prosecuted designe to set up popery, and extirpate the Protestant religion by degrees, in this our kealme [sic] of England, and all His Majesties dominions. Manifested by sundry letters of grace, warrants, writings under the Kings own signe-manuall, privy-signet, his privy-councels, and Secretary Windebanks hands and seals, by divers orders and proceedings in open sessions at Newgate, in the Kings Bench, and elsewhere ... Collected and published by authority of Parliament: by William Prynne, of Lincolns Inne, Esquire.</title>
         <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8], 72, [4] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>for <persName type="publisher">Michael Spark Senior</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>the Blue-Bible in Green-Arbour</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1643.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>In this edition Prynne's name in title is printed in capitals.</note>
         <note>Imperfect; pages stained and torn affecting numbering. The final [3] pages have no printed numbers.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Michael Spark Senior</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the Blue-Bible in Green-Arbour</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
