<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The Revelation reveled By two apocalyptical treatises. Shewing. I. How neer the period of the time is, wherein the mysterie of God shall bee fulfilled. II. What things are already fulfilled, and what shall shortly follow thereupon, as they are foretold in the Revelation. Translated out of High-Dutch. With an introductorie preface, shewing that besides the accomplishment of the particular historical events, spoken of in the Revelation, which are com, ... there is a deeper mysterie, and matter of more necessarie and profitable knowledg, to bee reflected upon in the words of this prophesie;  whereof also a summarie and a key, ... to bee thought upon by all the Godlie-wise in the three nations.</title>
         <author>Dury, John, 1596-1680.</author>
         <author>Hartlib, Samuel, d. 1662.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8], 79, [3], 163, [3] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">William Du-Gard</persName>, and are to bee sold by <persName type="bookseller">Rob. Littleberrie</persName> at <placeName>the sign of the Unicorn in Little Britain</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1651.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Errata p.[8].</note>
         <note>Preface signed: Samuel Hartlib; signed on p. 79: John Durie.</note>
         <note>"Clavis apocalyptica, or A prophetical key" has a caption title, separate pagination, register begins with signature B. "Apocalypsis reserata" has a separate dated title page, continuous pagination and register.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Trinity College Library, Dublin.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="printer"><persName>William Du-Gard</persName></person><person type="bookseller"><persName>Rob. Littleberrie</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the sign of the Unicorn in Little Britain</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
