<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The history of the Turks Beginning with the year 1679. Being a full relation of the last troubles in Hungary, with the sieges of Vienna, and Buda, and all the several battles both by sea and land, between the Christians, and the Turks, until the end of the year 1698, and 1699. In which the peace between the Turks, and the confederate Christian princes and states, was happily concluded at Carlowitz in Hungary, by the mediation of His Majesty of Great Britain, and the States General of the United Provinces. With the effigies of the emperors and others of note, engraven at large upon copper, which completes the sixth and last edition of the Turks. In two vol. in folio. By Sir Paul Rycaut, kt. eighteen years consul at Smyrna, now his Majesty's resident at Hamburg, and fellow of the Royal Society.</title>
         <author>Rycaut, Paul, Sir, 1628-1700.</author>
         <author>White, Robert, 1645-1703,</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8], 250, 241-607, [11] p., plates : ill., ports.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">Robert Clavell</persName>, in <placeName>St. Paul's Church-Yard</placeName>, and <persName type="publisher">Abel Roper against St. Dunstan's Church</persName> in <placeName>Fleetstreet</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>MDCC. [1700]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>With engraved frontispiece, signed: R White sculpsit.</note>
         <note>Includes index.</note>
         <note>Text is continuous despite pagination.</note>
         <note>Identified at reel 424 as part of Wing K702, and at reel 1952 as part of Wing K703B.</note>
         <note>Reproductions of the originals in the Library of Congress (reel 424), Cambridge University Library (reel 1819), and Dr. Williams's Library (reel 1952).</note>
         <note>Item at reel 1952:4b with: The Turkish history / by Richard Knolles. London : Printed for Jonathan Robinson ..., 1687.</note>
         <note>Item at reel 424:1b with: The Turkish history / by Richard Knolles. London : Printed for Tho. Basset ..., 1687.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Abel Roper against St. Dunstan's Church</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>Robert Clavell</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>Fleetstreet</placeName></place><place type="location"><placeName>St. Paul's Church-Yard</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
