<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The history of the Turkish Empire, from the year 1623, to the year 1677 Containing the reigns of the three last emperors, viz. Sultan Morat, or Amurat IV. Sultan Ibrahim, and Sultan Mahomet IV, his son, the thirteenth emperor, now reigning. By Sir Paul Rycaut, late consul of Smyrna.</title>
         <author>Rycaut, Paul, Sir, 1628-1700.</author>
         <author>Knolles, Richard, 1550?-1610. Generall historie of the Turkes. aut</author>
         <author>Manley, Roger, Sir, 1626?-1688. History of the Turkish Empire continued. aut</author>
         <author>Rycaut, Paul, Sir, 1628-1700. Memoirs. aut</author>
         <author>White, Robert, 1645-1703,</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[4], 93, [6], 97-259, 262-262 [i.e. 264], [2], 277-338, [10] p., [2] leaves of plates : ill., port.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">J.D.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Tho. Basset</persName>, <persName type="publisher">R. Clavell</persName>, <persName type="publisher">J. Robinson</persName>, and <persName type="publisher">A. Churchill</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>MDCLXXXVII. [1687]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A continuation of: Knolles, Richard.  The generall historie of the Turkes.</note>
         <note>With engraved frontispiece, signed: R. White sculpsit.</note>
         <note>"The memoirs of Sir Paul Rycaut containing the history of the Turks from the year 1660 to the year 1678" and "The history of the Turkish Empire continued from the year One Thousand Six Hundred Seventy Six to the year One Thousand Six Hundred Eighty Six" by Sir Roger Manley, each have divisional half title; register is continuous, and text is continuous despite pagination.</note>
         <note>Also appears at reel 424:1a as part of Wing K702 (vol. 2), and at reel 1952:4a as part of Wing K703B (vol. 2).</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>A. Churchill</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>J. Robinson</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>R. Clavell</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>Tho. Basset</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>J.D.</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
