<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Sir Thomas Fairfax's proceedings in the vvest against the enemy since he advanced to Bodman in Cornvval sent to the Honoble William Lenthal Esq; Speaker of the Honorable House of Commons. Wherein is a list of the names of the Lord Mohuns and divers other persons of quality of that county that are come in to the Parliament. Together with the Cornish petition to Sir Tho: Fairfax, for their acceptance to joyn with him in this cause. Also a summons sent to the Lord Hopton. Ordered by the Commons assembled in Parliament, that this letter and petition be forthwith printed and published. H: Elsynge, Cler. Parl. D. Com.</title>
         <author>Rushworth, John, 1612?-1690.</author>
         <author>England and Wales. Parliament. House of Commons. Proceedings. 1646-03.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>8 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">Edw. Husband</persName>, printer to <persName type="patron">the Honorable House of Commons</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop at the signe of the Golden Dragon in Fleetstreet, neer the Inner-Temple</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>March 7. 1645. [i.e. 1646]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Signed on page 7: Jo. Rushworth.</note>
         <note>Publication year is given according to Lady Day dating.</note>
         <note>Imperfect; pages have print show-through.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Edw. Husband</persName></person><person type="patron"><persName>the Honorable House of Commons</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>his shop at the signe of the Golden Dragon in Fleetstreet, neer the Inner-Temple</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
