<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The sixth book of Practical physick Of occult or hidden diseases; in nine parts Part I. Of diseases from occult qualities in general. Part. II. Of occult, malignant, and venemous diseases arising from the internal fault of the humors. Part III. Of occult diseases from water, air, and infections, and of infectious diseases. Part IV. Of the venereal pox. Part V. Of outward poysons in general Part VI. Of poysons from minerals and metals. Part. VII. Of poysons from plants. Part VIII. Of poysons that come from living creatures. Part IX. Of diseases by witchcraft, incantation, and charmes. By Daniel Sennertus, N Culpeper, and Abdiah Cole, Doctors of Physick</title>
      <author>Sennert, Daniel, 1572-1637.</author>
      <author>Culpeper, Nicholas, 1616-1654.</author>
      <author>Cole, Abdiah, ca. 1610-ca. 1670.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[14], 108 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">Peter Cole, printer and</persName> bookseller, at <placeName>the sign of the Printing-press in Cornhill, near the Royal Exchange</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1662.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>With an initial section of advertisements, and a table of contents.</note>
      <note>The author's names are bracketed together on the title page.</note>
      <note>Imperfect; pages faded and stained with slight loss of text.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Peter Cole, printer and</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the sign of the Printing-press in Cornhill, near the Royal Exchange</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
