<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Legends no histories, or, A specimen of some animadversions upon The history of the Royal Society wherein, besides the several errors against common literature, sundry mistakes about the making of salt-petre and gun-powder are detected and rectified : whereunto are added two discourses, one of Pietro Sardi and another of Nicolas Tartaglia relating to that subject, translated out of Italian : with a brief account of those passages of the authors life ... : together with the Plus ultra of Mr. Joseph Glanvill reduced to a non-plus, &amp;c. / by Henry Stubbe ...</title>
      <author>Stubbe, Henry, 1632-1676.</author>
      <author>Tartaglia, Niccol&#242;, d. 1557. Quesiti et inventioni diverse. Libro 3. English.</author>
      <author>Sardi, Pietro, b. 1559? Artiglieria. English. Selections.</author>
      <author>Stubbe, Henry, 1632-1676. Plus ultra reduced to a non plus.</author>
      <author>Henshaw, Thomas, 1618-1700.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[28], 3-127, [12], 179, [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>[s.n.],</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Printed at London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1670.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>An attack upon Thomas Sprat's The history of the Royal-Society.</note>
      <note>"The Plus ultra reduced to a non plus, or, A specimen of some animadversions upon the Plus ultra of Mr. Glanvill" has special t.p. and separate pagination.</note>
      <note>"Animadversions upon the history of making salt-petre, which was penned by Mr. Henshaw": p. 35.</note>
      <note>"Animadversions upon the history of making gun-powder, written also by Mr. Henshaw": p. 89.</note>
      <note>Errata on p. [2] at end of work.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in Harvard University Libraries.</note>
      <note>Marginal notes.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
