<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Bibliotheca Tillotsoniana: or A catalogue of the curious library of Dr. John Tillotson late Lord Archbishop of Canterbury Containing, a collection of Greek and Latin fathers, councils, historians (ecclesiastical and civil) philosophers, poets, orators, lexicographers, &amp;c. all of the best editions and neatly bound. Together with the library of Mr. Seth-Mountley Buncle, late master of Mercers school, London. Consisting of Hebrew, Chaldaick, Syriack, Persick, and other Oriental books, with French, Italian and Spanish. Which will be sold by retail at Mr. Christoph. Bateman's shop, the Bible and Crown in Middle Row, Holborn, on Tuesday April 9. 1695. According to the method of the following page.</title>
         <author>Tillotson, John, 1630-1694.</author>
         <author>Buncle, Seth-Mountley. aut.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[4], 87, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Catalogues are to be sold for <persName type="publisher">six-pence apiece</persName> by <persName type="printer">Mr. Jos. Hindmarsh over-against the Royal-Exchange</persName> in <placeName>Cornhil; Mr. James Partridge at the Post-Office near Charing-cross;</placeName> (and at <placeName>the place of sale.) By Mrs. Dickenson at Cambridge</placeName>, and Mr. H. Clements at <placeName>Oxford</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
         <date>1695.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Place of publication from Wing.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>six-pence apiece</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>Mr. Jos. Hindmarsh over-against the Royal-Exchange</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>Cornhil; Mr. James Partridge at the Post-Office near Charing-cross;</placeName></place><place type="location"><placeName>Oxford</placeName></place><place type="location"><placeName>the place of sale.) By Mrs. Dickenson at Cambridge</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
