<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A full and true relation of the most terrible and dreadful tempest of thunder &amp; lightening, hail and rai[n] that ever yet was seen or heard in England Giving a faithful account of the vast losses, damages, and calamities sustaine[d] thereby in the towns of Hitchin, Offly, Eccleford, ... with several other villag[es] and market-towns in the counties of Harford, Bedfor[d,] Huntington, &amp;c ... To which is added, particular account of the sad and dismal disasters that happen'd at Potton in Bedfordshire, ... As also a particular relation of the great damages sustained by Sq; Harvey and others, in their houses, corn, cattle &amp;c. The whole communicated in a letter out of Hartfordshire, from Mr. I. Tord, to his son-in-law Mr Burchfield near the Blew-Coat at Bishopsgate Barrs. Note, the truth of this relation will be confirm'd by Mr. Nicholas Beaumont, at the sign of the Hand in Hand-Alle[y] ...</title>
         <author>Tord, I.</author>
         <author>Burchfield, Mr., recipient.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>8 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>peinted [sic] and sold by <persName type="bookseller">J. Wilkins</persName>, <persName type="bookseller">[ ]nd the green Dragon Tavern</persName>, in <placeName>Fleet-street</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>[[Lo]ndon :</pubPlace>
         <date>1697]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Caption title on p. 2: True and particular account of the late terrible and dreadful stormm of hail, &amp;c.</note>
         <note>Imprint from colophon.</note>
         <note>Copy imperfect; closely cropped along outer margin with considerable loss of print; title and colophon mutilated.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="bookseller"><persName>J. Wilkins</persName></person><person type="bookseller"><persName>[ ]nd the green Dragon Tavern</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>Fleet-street</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
