<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Dr. Willis's practice of physick being the whole works of that renowned and famous physician wherein most of the diseases belonging to the body of man are treated of, with excellent methods and receipts for the cure of the same : fitted to the meanest capacity by an index for the explaining of all the hard and unusual words and terms of art derived from the Greek, Latine, or other languages for the benefit of the English reader : with forty copper plates.</title>
         <author>Willis, Thomas, 1621-1675.</author>
         <author>Pordage, Samuel, 1633-1691?</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <editionStmt>
         <edition>The pharmaceutice new translated and the whole carefully corrected and amended.</edition>
      </editionStmt>
      <extent>1086 p. in various pagings, 40 leaves of plates : ill.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">T. Dring</persName>, <persName type="publisher">C. Harper</persName>, and <persName type="publisher">J. Leigh</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1684.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>"Containing these eleven several treatises, viz. I. Of fermentation. II. Of feavers, III. Of urines, IV. Of the accension of the blood, V. Of musculary motion, VI. Of the anatomy of the brain, VII. Of the description and use of the nerves, VIII. Of convulsive diseases, IX. Pharmaceutice rationalis, the first and second part, X. Of the scurvy, XI. Two discourses concerning the soul of brutes."</note>
         <note>Translated by Samuel Pordage--LC.</note>
         <note>Many of the treatises have special t.p.'s.</note>
         <note>Includes indexes.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the Harvard University Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>C. Harper</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>J. Leigh</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>T. Dring</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
