<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>God's great and vvonderful vvork in Somerset-shire the charitable farmer miraculously rewarded h[a]ppening at Welling within three miles of the city of Wells this last harvest, where an honest Godly farmer having sold most part of this last summer and winter great quantities of corn to the poor in their distress at five or six shillings the bushel, when the market price was ten and eleven shillings; for which he was much derided and scoft at by his rich neighbours, he was recompensed by an extraordinary crop of wheat, the like was never before heard; of each stalk of straw having divers full large ears, some nine, ten and thirteen, but generally ten ears on every straw throughout the field which was ten acres and upwards; of which ears are to be seen at divers coffy-houses by the Royal Exchange, and at other places in London, published as a grateful acknowledgement to the goodness of providence, and to stir up all into faith in God, and charity towards their poor neighbours from the consideration of so remarkable an example. The tune i</title>
         <author>L. W.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>1 sheet ([1] p.) : ill. (woodcut)  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">F. Coles</persName>, <persName type="publisher">T. Veres. J. Wright.</persName> and <persName type="publisher">John Clarke</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>[1676]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Signed at end: By L. W.</note>
         <note>Imprint date added in MS.: "1676".</note>
         <note>At foot of text: With allowance.</note>
         <note>A ballad adaptation of an anonymous pamphlet with a similar title published in 1674 (Wing G958A).</note>
         <note>Verse - [lacking first stanza]; first line of stanza three: "Some being put to such great want and need".</note>
         <note>Includes "The second part to the same tune" on the same sheet.</note>
         <note>Printed in columns with woodcut at head of first two; text in black letter.</note>
         <note>Copy torn at left edge, with loss of text and part of illustration.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original at the Bodleian Library, Oxford.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>F. Coles</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>John Clarke</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>T. Veres. J. Wright.</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
