<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The warming stone Excellent helps really found out, tried, and had, by a warming stone in his case, which not costing much, will save much cost in fire, and withall avoyd the danger of fire: and likewise is very usefull and comfortable for the colds of aged and sicke people, and for women with child, and in child-bed: as also for fluxes, rheumes, colicks, ruptures, or any cold disease: and for those that in beds, studies, shops, ships, churches, or elsewhere, have need of heate, yet cannot conveniently make use of fire: and likewise for the poore, when having no fire of their owne, they may borrow the heating of this stone at a neighbours fire, if his charity be not altogether cold. These stones with their cases are to be sold at [blank] where more particular satisfaction may be had of the contents of the booke.</title>
         <author>Carew, Richard, Sir, d. 1643?</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 8 [i.e. 6] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">R[ichard] H[odgkinson]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Iohn Bartlet</persName>, at <placeName>the signe of the gilt Cup in Pauls Church-yard, neere S. Augustines Gate</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1640.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>By Sir Richard Carew.</note>
         <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
         <note>P. 6 misnumbered 8.</note>
         <note>Identified as STC 25075 on UMI microfilm.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
         <note>Pages creased with slight loss of text; A4 mutilated.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Iohn Bartlet</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>R[ichard] H[odgkinson]</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the signe of the gilt Cup in Pauls Church-yard, neere S. Augustines Gate</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
