<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A solemn testimony against toleration and the present proceedings of sectaries and their abettors in England in reference to religion and government with an admonition and exhortation to their brethren there from the Commissioners of the General Assembly of the Kirk of Scotland : with the return of the Honourable Estates of Parliament upon the said testimony communicated to them, and their concurrence with the same : together with the paper of the 5. of July given in by the Commissioners for the kingdom of Scotland to the speaker of the House of Commons mentioned in the said return.</title>
      <author>Church of Scotland. General Assembly. Commission.</author>
      <author>Ker, A.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 18, 5 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Evan Tyler</persName> ...,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Edinburgh :</pubPlace>
      <date>1649.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>First part signed: A. Ker.</note>
      <note>First part has caption title, "A necessary and seasonable testimony against toleration and the present proceedings of sectaries and their abettors in England," and appears as N366A in Wing (2nd ed.).</note>
      <note>"The return of the Estates of Parliament upon the testimony communicated unto them by the Commissioners of the Generall Assembly ..." also appears at reel 1748:14 incorrectly identified as Wing (2nd ed.) N366A.</note>
      <note>"The paper of the 5. of July" has separate pagination, and is signed: Lothian, Jo: Cheisly, William Glendoning.</note>
      <note>Imperfect: torn, with slight loss of print.</note>
      <note>Complete work is at reel 1148:26; reel 1748:14 has "Return of the Estates of Parliament ..." only.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of originals in the Huntington Library and British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Evan Tyler</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
