<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A true discovery to the commons of England how they have been cheated of almost all the gold and silver coyn of this nation, which hath been, and is daily transported into forraign parts. And how the people of this nation are, and have been abused by light and clipped English money, and the means shewed for the prevention thereof. Humbly presented to the Parliament of the Common-wealth of England. By Thomas Violet a true lover of his countrey.</title>
         <author>Violet, Thomas, fl. 1634-1662.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 94 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">W.B.</persName> and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">W. Sherres</persName> at <placeName>the sign of the Bible over against the North door of Pauls</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1650.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Caption title on p. 1 reads: A true discovery how the Common-wealth of England, have been cheated of their treasure, and means shewed for prevention thereof.</note>
         <note>Item at reel 1877:15 identified as Wing V591 (number cancelled).</note>
         <note>Imperfect: Lu copy has pages faded, slightly affecting text.</note>
         <note>Imperfect: L copy has torn and severely stained title page; date of publication has been altered in MS. to 1659.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Goldsmiths' Company Library, University of London (reel 1981), and the British Library (reel 1877).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="printer"><persName>W.B.</persName></person><person type="bookseller"><persName>W. Sherres</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the sign of the Bible over against the North door of Pauls</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
