<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The compleat History of independencie Upon the Parliament begun 1640. By Clem. Walker, Esq; Continued till this present year 1660. which fourth part was never before published.</title>
      <title>History of independency.</title>
      <author>Walker, Clement, 1595-1651.</author>
      <author>Theodorus Verax. aut</author>
      <author>T. M., lover of his king and country. aut</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8], 174, [2], 18, [12], 262, [2], 71, [9], 124 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">Iohn Wiliams</persName> at <placeName>the Crown in St. Paul's Church-yard</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1661.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Also published as: The compleat history of independency.</note>
      <note>Title page in red and black.</note>
      <note>With a general title page for the first part of the History of Independency and its Appendix, dated 1648, individual dated title pages for parts I through IV, separate pagination for each part (including the Appendix to part I), and separate register for parts II, III and IV.</note>
      <note>Title to part I reads: The history of independency, with the rise, growth, and practices of that powerfull and restlesse faction.</note>
      <note>Part II title page, dated 1659, reads in part: Anarchia Anglicana: or, the history of independency. The second part. .. By Theodorus Verax.</note>
      <note>Part III title page, dated 1660, reads in part: The high court of justice, or Cromwel's new slaughter-house in England. .. Written by the same author.</note>
      <note>Title page to part IV reads in part: The history of independency. The fourth and last part. .. By T. M. Esquire, a lover of his king and country.</note>
      <note>This edition is not in Wing.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library, Oxford.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Iohn Wiliams</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Crown in St. Paul's Church-yard</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
