<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The tragedies, gathered by Ihon Bochas, of all such princes as fell from theyr estates throughe the mutability of fortune since the creacion of Adam, vntil his time wherin may be seen what vices bring menne to destruccion, wyth notable warninges howe the like may be auoyded. Translated into Englysh by Iohn Lidgate, monke of Burye.</title>
      <title>De casibus virorum illustrium. English</title>
      <author>Boccaccio, Giovanni, 1313-1375.</author>
      <author>Lydgate, John, 1370?-1451?</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[9], clxiii, xxxvi, xxxv-xxxvii, [1] leaves : ill. (woodcuts)  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">Iohn Wayland</persName>, at <placeName>the signe of the Sunne oueragainst the Conduite in Flete-strete. Cum priuilegio per septennium</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date>[1554?]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A verse translation of: Boccaccio, Giovanni.  De casibus illustrium virorum.</note>
      <note>Publication date conjectured by STC.</note>
      <note>The eighth book begins new foliation on 2A1.</note>
      <note>The last leaf, usually lacking, bears the title page to STC 1246, which was intended to have formed part 2 of the present work, but the printing was suppressed.</note>
      <note>Another state, with cancel title page, of "The fall of princes" (STC 3177.5).</note>
      <note>Sometimes bound with "The bayte &amp; snare of fortune" by Roger Bieston (STC 3055) or "A memorial of suche princes, as since the tyme of king Richard the seconde, have been unfortunate in the realme of England" edited by William Baldwin.</note>
      <note>Identified as part of STC 1246 on UMI microfilm reel 307.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery and Harvard University. Library.</note>
      <note>Appears at reel 285 (Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery copy) and at reel 307 (Harvard University. Library copy).</note>
      <note>Reel 307: lacks title page.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Iohn Wayland</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the signe of the Sunne oueragainst the Conduite in Flete-strete. Cum priuilegio per septennium</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
