<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>An act for the better ordering and managing the estates of papists &amp; delinquents. Die Veneris, 25 Januarii, 1649. Ordered by the Parliament, that John Field printer, nominated by Mr. Speaker, be joyned with Mr. Husbands stationer, in printing the Act for the better ordering and managing the estates of papists and delinquents, and all other acts and proceedings in Parliament; and that his name be used in printing of the said act, and all other acts and proceedings: and that the said John Field have equal benefit in printing accordingly. Hen: Scobell, Cleric. Parliamenti.</title>
         <author>England and Wales.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 669-680, [1];  [i.e. 15] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">Edward Husband</persName> and <persName type="printer">John Field</persName>, printers to <persName type="patron">the Parliament of England</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>the Golden Dragon in Fleetstreet</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1649 [i.e. 1650]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>On 6H2: the last word of first line of text: 'Eng-'; first word of line below initial: 'authority'; last word of last full line of text: 'ordinance'.</note>
         <note>Also issued as part of a through-paged folio set with a table for the entire set added.</note>
         <note>Signatures: 6H-6I&#8308;.</note>
         <note>Ornament on t.p.; initial letter;  text in black letter.</note>
         <note>The final leaf is blank.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="patron"><persName>the Parliament of England</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>Edward Husband</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>John Field</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the Golden Dragon in Fleetstreet</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
