<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The bloody almanack; or, Monethly observations and predictions, for the year of our Lord, 1654. Fore-telling I The great and wonderful mutation of times, and change of government, in England, Scotland, and Ireland. II The proclaiming of open wars by the Christian kings and princes, and the setting up of their royal standards. III Their proceedings touching the King of Scots, and the lamentable and unparallel'd engagement that will happen between the two mighty fleets of England and Europe. IV. The event and success of this great and memorable sea fight; and the dying of the curled waves with the bloud of princes and nobles, &amp;c. V The advance of the King of Scots, ...; and the total vanquishing and dispersing their great armado. VI The calling to an account the officers of the nation; and the beheading of divers great ones, ... VII The taking off all oppressions and burdens from the people, ... VIII The taking away and extirpating of the power, rule, and government of the tyrannical Norman sword. IX The sad and woful condition that women with child will be exposed unto, if not prevented, by the ensuing potions here administred. Published for the general good of the Common-wealth of England, by a cordial lover of his native-countrey's rights and liberties; and freely exposed to the view of all cities, towns, and corporations,.</title>
      <author>Livie, John, fl. 1654-1659.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 6 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>for <persName type="publisher">G. Horton</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1654. [i.e. 1653]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Attributed to John Livie.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Octo. 31. 1653"; the 4 in imprint date has been crossed out.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>G. Horton</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
