<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>An Anti-Brekekekex-Coax-Coax, or, A throat-hapse for the frogges and toades that lately crept abroad, croaking against the Common-prayer book and Episcopacy and the copie of a letter from a very reverend church-man, in answer to a young man, who desired his judgement upon this case, viz. whether every minister of the Church of England be bound in conscience to reade the Common-prayer : with another letter from a convinced associatour, that a while boggled at the Common-prayer, to a brother of the same association, not yet convinced, together with the above-said reverend person's brief and candid censure thereupon, with some uses of application by the publisher.</title>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>32 [i.e. 36] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed in <placeName>hopes to doe good to the publick, or at least to give some check to the impudent slanders of some malicious non-conformists, who</placeName> by <persName type="printer">the same artifice, as they did</persName> in <placeName>the year 1642, goe about to re-inflame these nations</placeName> by <persName type="printer">their libellous pamphlets</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1660.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Reproduction of original in: Dr. Williams's Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="printer"><persName>the same artifice, as they did</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>their libellous pamphlets</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>hopes to doe good to the publick, or at least to give some check to the impudent slanders of some malicious non-conformists, who</placeName></place><place type="location"><placeName>the year 1642, goe about to re-inflame these nations</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
