<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The sword of the Lord dravvn, and furbished against the man of sin: or Something in answer to a paper set forth by three of the chief priests of London, whose names are Thomas Goodwine, and one Nye, and Sydrach Sympson, which they have put forth to the propagating of the Gospel, signed by him that is the clerk of the Parl. whose name is Henry Scobell, with their deceits and deceitfull actings laid open and cleared from Scripture, that they have no example in Scripture for their practice. Therefore I was moved by the Lord God of life to lay open their deceit by the spirit of truth, as it was made manifest in me from the Lord, that the simple might not be deceived by them, but might have the knowledge of the truth, from that which is for ever, and shall not change nor fade away. / By one whose name in the flesh is, Christopher Atkinson, who am one that the world doth scornfully call a Quaker.</title>
      <author>Atkinson, Christopher.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 6 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Giles Calvert;</persName> at <placeName>the sign of the Black-spread-Eagle at the west end of Pauls.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1654.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A reply to: Thomas Goodwin, Sidrach Simpson, and Philip Nye.  The principles of faith.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Nouemb. 28".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Giles Calvert;</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the sign of the Black-spread-Eagle at the west end of Pauls.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
