<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The throne of truth exalted over the povvers of darkness. From whence is judged, the mouth of Ralph Farmer (an unclean and blood-thirsty priest of Bristol) opened in blasphemy against God, and his name, and his tabernacle, and them that dwell in heaven; in a late noysome pamphlet of his, intituled, Satan enthron'd in his chair of pestilence; or, Quakerism in its exaltation. And in the light and power of which is comprehended, swept away, and overthrown the filthy matter, and mischievous design of Satan in that heap of falshood; and his confusion, dishonesty, lyes, slanders, scoffs, blasphemies, and other polluted stuff with which it is fill'd, made manifest, and turned back into his own bosome, the lake from whence it came; and the truth fully vindicated, &amp; made to apear clear, as to all that's endeavoured to be cast thereon by him, either as to I.N. and that companie's late coming to Bristol, their papers, &amp;c. or upon occasion thereof in that his book. For the sake of the simple-hearted in this great hour of temptation, and power of darkness. By a witness of the truth, ... Geo. Bishope.</title>
         <author>Bishop, George, d. 1668.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[4], 94, 93-111, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">Giles Calvert</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop at the Black-spread-Eagle neer the West end of Pauls</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1657.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A reply to: Farmer, Ralph.  Sathan inthron'd in his chair of pestilence.</note>
         <note>Text continuous despite pagination.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "alias fop" after 'Geo. Bishope.'; "March 28".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Giles Calvert</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>his shop at the Black-spread-Eagle neer the West end of Pauls</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
