<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Concerning the election of grace. Or Of Gods will towards man. Commonly called predestination. That is, how the texts of Scripture are to be understood which treat of fallen lost Adam, and of the new birth from Christ. Being a short declaration and introduction concerning the highest ground, shewing how man may attain divine skill and knowledge. Written in the German tongue, anno 1623. / By Jacob Behme. Teutonicus philosophus.</title>
         <title>Von der Gnadenwahl. English</title>
         <author>B&#246;hme, Jakob, 1575-1624.</author>
         <author>Sparrow, John, 1615-1665?</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[26], 197, [2], 199-201, 102-104, [14] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">John Streater</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">Giles Calvert</persName>, and <persName type="publisher">John Allen</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>their shops, at the Black-spread-Eagle at the west end of Pauls;</placeName> and at <placeName>the Sun Rising in Paul's Church-Yard in the new buildings between the two north doores</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
         <date>1655.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A translation, by John Sparrow, of: B&#246;hme, Jakob.  Von der Gnadenwahl.</note>
         <note>"An appendix to the book of election or predestination." (p. 199-204), and "Jacob Behme's Table, of the divine manifestation." ([12] p. at end) each have separate dated title page; register and pagination are continuous.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Nouemb: 13.".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Giles Calvert</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>John Allen</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>John Streater</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the Sun Rising in Paul's Church-Yard in the new buildings between the two north doores</placeName></place><place type="location"><placeName>their shops, at the Black-spread-Eagle at the west end of Pauls;</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
