<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Precious remedies against Satans devices or, salve for believers and unbelievers sores. Being a companion for those that are in Christ, or out of Christ; that are high, or low, learned, or illiterate, staggering, or wandering; that slight, or neglect ordinances, under a pretence of living above them; that are growing (in spiritualls) or decaying; that are tempted, or deserted, afflicted, or opposed; that have assurance, or that want assurance; that are self-seekers, or the common-wealths caterpillars; that are in love sweetly united, or that yet have their spirits too much imbittered, &amp;c. By Thomas Brookes, a willing servant unto God, and the faith of his people, in the glorious gospel of Christ, at Margarets fish-street hill.</title>
      <author>Brooks, Thomas, 1608-1680.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <editionStmt>
      <edition>The second edition corrected and enlarged.</edition>
    </editionStmt>
    <extent>[22], 378, [16]   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">M. Simmons</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">John Hancock</persName> at <placeName>the first shop in Popes-head Alley, next to Corn-hill</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1653.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Includes a twelve page table, an advertisement leaf, and a note from the author concerning errata, at end.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "May. 10".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>John Hancock</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>M. Simmons</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the first shop in Popes-head Alley, next to Corn-hill</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
