<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The ninth, tenth, and eleventh books of Mr Jeremiah Burroughs: containing three treatises: I. Of precious faith. II. Of hope. III. The saints walk by faith on earth; by sight in heaven. Being the last sermons that the author preached at Stepney, neer London. / Published by Thomas Goodwyn, William Bridge, Sydrach Sympson, William Adderly, William Greenhil, Philip Nye, John Yates.</title>
      <author>Burroughs, Jeremiah, 1599-1646.</author>
      <author>Goodwin, Thomas, 1600-1680.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[34], 436 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Peter Cole</persName> in <placeName>Leaden-Hill</placeName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop at the sign of the Printing-Press in Cornhil, neer the Royal Exchange.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1655.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>The second sermon has separate dated title page (pagination is continuous) that reads: The tenth book of Mr Jeremiah Burroughs. Being a treatise of hope.</note>
      <note>The third sermon has separate dated title page (pagination is continuous) that reads: The eleventh book of Mr Jeremiah Burroughs. Viz. the saints walk by faith on earth: by sight in heaven.</note>
      <note>Annotations on Thomason copy: "17 Feb:", "Feb. 17 1654:"; the final 5 in imprint date crossed out.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Peter Cole</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Leaden-Hill</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop at the sign of the Printing-Press in Cornhil, neer the Royal Exchange.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
