<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The censures of the church revived. In the defence of a short paper published by the first classis within the province of Lancaster ... but since printed without their privity or consent, after it had been assaulted by some gentlemen and others within their bounds ... under the title of Ex-communicatio excommunicata, or a Censure of the presbyterian censures and proceedings, in the classis at Manchester. Wherein 1. The dangerousness of admitting moderate episcopacy is shewed. ... 6. The presbyterian government vindicated from severall aspersions cast upon it, ... In three full answers ... Together with a full narrative, of the occasion and grounds, of publishing in the congregations, the above mentioned short paper, and of the whole proceedings since, from first to last.</title>
         <author>Harrison, John, 1613?-1670.</author>
         <author>Allen, Isaac, 17th cent.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[64], 140, 177-350, [2] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">George Eversden</persName>, at <placeName>the signe of the Maiden-head in Pauls Church-yard</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1659.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>The dedication is signed: John Harrison moderator.</note>
         <note>"In 1658 a controversy about presbyterian church government arose between the Rev. Isaac Allen of Prestwich and other episcopalians and the Manchester Classis, and Harrison was deputed by that presbytery to write in their defence." This is the resulting volume of papers written on both sides. -- DNB.</note>
         <note>Text continuous despite pagination.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "May 12".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>George Eversden</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the signe of the Maiden-head in Pauls Church-yard</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
