<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>New-Englands Jonas cast up at London: or, A relation of the proceedings of the court at Boston in New-England against divers honest and godly persons, for petitioning for government in the common-wealth, according to the lawes of England, and for admittance of themselves and children to the sacraments in their churches; and in case that should not be granted, for leave to have ministers and church-government according to the best reformation of England and Scotland. Together with a confutation of some reports of a fained miracle upon the aforesaid petition, being thrown over-board at sea; as also a breif [sic] answer to some passages in a late book (entituled Hypocrisie unmasked) set out by Mr. Winslowe, concerning the Independent churches holding communion with the reformed churches. / By Major John Child.</title>
      <author>Child, John, Major.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 13 [i.e. 21], [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">T.R.</persName> and <persName type="publisher">E.M.</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date>1647.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A reply, at least in part, to: Winslow, Edward. Hypocrisie unmasked (Wing W3037). Winslow, in his New-Englands salamander, discovered by an irreligious and scornefull pamphlet, called New-Englands Jonas cast up at London, &amp;c. Owned by Major John Childe, but not probable to be written by him (Wing W3038), obviously doubts Child's authorship of this item.</note>
      <note>Text is continuous despite numerous errors in pagination.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A-C&#8308;.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Aprill 15th".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>E.M.</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>T.R.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
