<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The inhumanity of the Kings prison-keeper at Oxford. Or a true relation of the most transcendent cruelties, cheatings, cozenings, and base dishonest dealings of William Smith Provest [sic] Marshall General of the Kings Army, against the Parliament prisoners under his custody. As it was delivered at the Barre in the House of Commons, by one, who with many others, were sworne before the Lords assembled in Parliament, and were prisoners in Oxford six moneths, being further confirmed by Captain Wingate in the Commons House, he being Member of the said House, and some time prisoner in Oxford, the space of 9. moneths. Together, with the copy of a letter from a Gentleman of quality confirming the former particulars. Also the copy of a petition and articles exhibited to the King, his councell of warre against Smith. Likewise a letter to the Speaker, subscribed with 70. prisoners hands. Whereunto is added the unsufferable cruelties, exercised upon the Cirencester men, in their passage to Oxford, and at Oxford, in the castle and Bride-vvell, vvhen they were taken. Written by Edm. Chillenden. who was a prisoner there 6. moneths. Printed according to order.</title>
      <author>Chillenden, Edmund, fl. 1656.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 14 [i.e. 28], [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">G.D.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">John Bull</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1643.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>P. 28 misnumbered 14. Variant: p. 28 correctly numbered.</note>
      <note>The last leaf bears "A postscript".</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Aug: 4th".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>John Bull</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>G.D.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
