<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>An answer to a book which Samuel Eaton put up to the Parliament: which he saith he is a teacher of the Church of Christ, heretofore meeting at Ducken-field, now at Stockport in Cheshire; and he cals the title of his book Quakers confuted. Moses who was a judg quaked and trembled, David a king in Israel quaked and trembled, and Solomon who was a king trembled, and Daniel a servant of the most high God trembled, ... And these heard the voice of God, and thou that writest, thou mayest say thou hast confuted all them; for he that is against them, is against us, and he that is against us, is against them, for the same power is witnessed; but thou Eaton, who saith thou art a teacher of the church at Duckenfield, who saith thou hast heard the voice of the living God, and that such a voice as this, as comes immediately from God, you have not heard, ... And Isaiah saith, hear the word of the Lord all ye that tremble at his word; and this is the man that I do regard, saith the Lord, that is of a contrite heart, and trembleth at my word; but such Eaton and his church doth not regard, but custs out friends of the Lord from them, whom the world calls Quakers.</title>
         <author>Camm, John, 1604?-1656.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>55, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Giles Calvert</persName>, at <placeName>the black Spread-Eagle, at the west end of Pauls</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1654.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "may. 13.".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Giles Calvert</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the black Spread-Eagle, at the west end of Pauls</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
