<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Magna charta containing that which is very much the sence and agreement of the good people of these nations, notwithstanding their differences relating to worship. Humbly tendered to those that are in eminent place, both in a civil and in a military capacity, and earnestly desired that it may be by them also (in this juncture of affaires) speedily concurred with, resolved upon, and vigorously prosecuted, for the escaping of the sadest, and for the enjoying of the joyfullest dayes and station, that England hath seen. By an unfeined lover of his countrys welfare, and a sincere promoter of the Common-wealth and just concernments of all men. As some further essay in order to a well grounded vnity, peace and settlement, of the poor shaken and shattered nations, upon that sure and durable foundation of righteousness, which will without doubt, according to the wise mans experience, not only establish, but exalt a nation.</title>
         <author>J. C.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>1 sheet ([1] p.)   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Francis Smith</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop, at the Elephant</placeName> and Castle near <placeName>Temple-Barre</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1659.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Signed: J.C.</note>
         <note>Not in fact the Magna carta, but a demand that the liberties enjoyed under the Commonwealth be maintained.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "xber [i.e. December] 7".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Francis Smith</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>Temple-Barre</placeName></place><place type="location"><placeName>his shop, at the Elephant</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
