<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The bloudy tenent, washed, and made white in the bloud of the Lambe: being discussed and discharged of bloud-guiltinesse by just defence. Wherein the great questions of this present time are handled, viz. how farre liberty of conscience ought to be given to those that truly feare God? And how farre restrained to turbulent and pestilent persons, that not onely raze the foundation of godlinesse, but disturb the civill peace where they live? Also how farre the magistrate may proceed in the duties of the first table? And that all magistrates ought to study the word and will of God, that they may frame their government according to it. Discussed. As they are alledged from divers Scriptures, out of the Old and New Testament. Wherein also the practise of princes is debated, together with the judgement of ancient and late writers of most precious esteeme. Whereunto is added a reply to Mr. Williams answer, to Mr. Cottons letter. / By John Cotton Batchelor in Divinity, and teacher of the church of Christ at Boston in New England.</title>
      <author>Cotton, John, 1584-1652.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 195, [1], 144 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Matthew Symmons</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Hannah Allen</persName>, at <placeName>the Crowne in Popes-Head-Alley.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date>1647.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>In two parts. Part 2 is a reply to: Williams, Roger. The bloody tenent of persecution, for cause of conscience (Wing W2758 et seq.).</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "May 15th".</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Hannah Allen</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Matthew Symmons</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Crowne in Popes-Head-Alley.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
