<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The stumbling-stone, or, A discourse touching that offence which the world and worldly church do take against 1. Christ himself. 2. His true word. 3. His true worship. 4. His true church. 5. His true government. 6. His true ministry. Wherein the University is reproved by the Word of God. Delivered partly to the University-congregation in Cambridge, partly to another in the same town. Together with a brief touch in the epistle (for the present) on the late quarrelsom, weak, and erroneous Animadversions of one Mr. Chambers, called Doctor in Divinity, and Pastor of Pewsy in Wiltshire. By William Dell minister of the Gospel, and Master of Gonvil and Cains Colledge in Cambridge.</title>
         <author>Dell, William, d. 1664.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8], 40 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">R.W.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Giles Calvert</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>the Black-spread Eagle at the West end of Pauls.</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
         <date>1653.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A sermon on Matt. xi. 6, warning all universities to repent, in reply o Humphrey Chamber's "Animadversions on Mr. William Dells book intituled The crucified and quickned Christian".</note>
         <note>The words "1. Christ himself. .. 6. His true ministry." are enclosed in brackets on title page.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Aprill 20th".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Giles Calvert</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>R.W.</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the Black-spread Eagle at the West end of Pauls.</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
