<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Forms the pillars of Antichrist; but Christ in spirit the true teacher of his people; and not tradition: for the spirit of God is not bound to any place, nor time, nor form; we may not limit the holy one of Israel. The spirits teaching doth unmask and unvail the false prophet, or the carnal worshipper, and discovers them to be the agents and agitators of Antichrist. And the kingdome of Antichrist is subdued to us, and destroyed in us, by the Spirits teaching. And to him that is led by the Spirits teaching do I commend these to be received, and not to the naturall mans wisdom; ... / Written in Scotland in opposition to some people who do imitate John the Baptist, by dipping themselves in water, holding out free-will, and falling from grace, and pretend that they are the only disciples of Christ, and reject the Spirits teaching, by one who waits to see the downfal of the kingdom of Antichrist, and the prosperity of Sion, Jonas Dell something in answer to a scandalous paper given forth by W.P. to the souldiers in the garrison of Holmdell in Southerland.</title>
         <author>Dell, Jonas, d. 1665.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[6], 72 [i.e. 66] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">the author</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>the Black-moor neer Fleet-Bridge</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
         <date>1656.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Pages 12-66 misnumbered 18-72.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "July. 5".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>the author</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the Black-moor neer Fleet-Bridge</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
