<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A declaration of the Parliament of the Commonwealth of England, relating to the affairs and proceedings between this Commonwealth and the States General of the United Provinces of the Low-Countreys, and the present differences occcasioned [sic] on the States part. And the answer of the Parliament to three papers from the ambassadors extraordinary of the States General, upon occasion of the late fight between the fleets. With a narrative of the late engagement betvveen the English and Holland fleet. As also a collection of the preceedings in the treaty between the Lord Pauw, Ambassador Extraordinary from the States General of the United Provinces, and the Parliament of the Commonwealth of England. Friday the ninth of Iuly, 1652. Ordered by the Parliament, that no person whatsoever, without particular license from the Parliament, do presume to print the declaration ... Nor any the papers therewith printed, other then the printer to the Parliament. Hen: Scobell, Cleric. Parliamenti.</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
      <author>Pauw, Adriann, 1585-1653.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>70 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Iohn Field</persName>, printer to <persName type="patron">the Parliament of England</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1652.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Includes documents by A. Pauw and others.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="patron">
      <persName>the Parliament of England</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Iohn Field</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
