<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The humble petition and advice, presented unto His Highness the Lord Protector by the knights, citizens and burgesses assembled at the Parliament begun and held at Westminster the 17th day of September 1656. and there continued until the 26th day of Iune following, and then adjourned unto the 20th day of Ianuary 1657. As also, their humble additional and explanatory petition and advice, presented unto His Highness in the same Parliament; together with His Highness consent unto the said petitions when they were respectively presented.</title>
         <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
         <author>England and Wales. Lord Protector (1653-1658 : O. Cromwell)</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[4], 30 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Henry Hills</persName> and <persName type="printer">John Field</persName>, Printers to <persName type="patron">His Highness</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1657.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>With an initial blank leaf.</note>
         <note>The first petition is dated 25 May 1657.</note>
         <note>"To His Highness the Lord Protector of the Commonwealth of England, Scotland, and Ireland, and the dominions and territories thereunto belonging: the humble additional and explanatory petition and advice, of the knights, citizens, and burgesses now assembled in the Parliament of this Common-VVealth", dated 26 June 1657, has separate dated title page; pagination and register are continuous.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="patron"><persName>His Highness</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>Henry Hills</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>John Field</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
