<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A declaration of the Commons assembled in Parliament concerning the rise and progresse of the grand rebellion in Ireland. Together vvith a multitude of examinations of persons of quality, whereby it may easily appear to all the world, who were, and still are the promoters of that cruell and unheard of rebellion. With some letters and papers of great consequence of the Earl of Antrims, which were intercepted. Also some letters of Mart, which were granted by the Lord Mohun, Sir Ralph Hopton, &amp;c. And likewise another from the rebells in Ireland, who term themselves, the supreme councel for the Catholique-cause. Ordered by the Commons in Parl. that this declaration, examinations, and letters, be forthwith printed and published: H. Elsynge, Cler. Parl. D. Com.</title>
      <title>Proceedings. 1643-07</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament. House of Commons.</author>
      <author>Antrim, Randal MacDonnell, Earl of, 1609-1683.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>63, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">Edw. Husbands</persName>, and are to be sold in <placeName>the Middle-Temple</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>Iuly 1643.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Another impression (Wing E2557) has "July 25, 1643" in imprint, and lacks the order to print on title page verso.</note>
      <note>With no ornaments on A2v. Variant: outer forme of quire A partly reset. Imprint has "Iuly 25. 1642."; A2v has row of ornaments between text and catchword.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Folger Shakespeare Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Edw. Husbands</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Middle-Temple</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
