<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A sober answer to an angry epistle, directed to all the publick teachers in this nation, and prefixed to a book, called (by an antiphrasis) Christs innocency pleaded against the cry of the chief priests. Written in hast by Thomas Speed, once a publick teacher himself, and since revolted from that calling to merchandize, and of late grown a merchant of soules, trading subtilly for the Quakers in Bristoll. Wherein the jesuiticall equivocations and subtle insinuations, whereby he endeavours secretly to infuse the whole venome of Quaking doctrines, into undiscerning readers, are discovered; a catlogue of the true and genuine doctrines of the Quakers is presented, and certaine questions depending between us and them, candidly disputed, / by [brace] Christopher Fowler &amp; Simon Ford, [brace] ministers of the Gospel in Reding,</title>
      <author>Fowler, Christopher, 1610?-1678.</author>
      <author>Ford, Simon, 1619?-1699.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 76 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Samuel Gellibrand</persName>, at <placeName>the Ball in Pauls Church Yard</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date>1656.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A reply to: Speed, Thomas.  Christ's innocency pleaded against the cry of the chief priests, or, a reply unto certain papers received from William Thomas.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "June 29".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Samuel Gellibrand</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Ball in Pauls Church Yard</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
