<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>New propositions from His Excellency Sir Thomas Fairfax, agreed upon by the Generall, Lieutenant-Generall, Colonels, Lieutenant-Colonels, Majors, and Captaines, under his Excellencies command, at a late Councell of Warre. Concerning, the brotherly meetings of Independents, and divers other well-affected people of this kingdome. With their desires to both Houses of Parliament concerning the same. Also, some particulars concerning the Booke of Common-Prayer. And the last propositions from the souldiery to his Excellency Sir Thomas Fairfax, concerning a great member of this kingdome. Published for generall satisfaction.</title>
         <author>England and Wales. Army. Council.</author>
         <author>Fairfax, Thomas Fairfax, Baron, 1612-1671.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>for <persName type="publisher">T: Deane</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
         <date>anno 1647.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A collection of three documents: "The copy of a letter from Wooburn Lodge in Bedfordshire, concerning the Kings Majesty, &amp;c."; "A copy of the propositions and desires of the souldiery, concerning Col. Gen. Poyntz presented to his Excellency Sir Thomas Fairfax"; and "Another paper from his Excellency to the Lord Mayor and Common-Councel of the City of London", which is dated and signed at end: Reading Iuly 19. 1647. By the appointment of his Excellency Sir Thomas Fairfax and the Counsell of Warre. Signed Io. Rushworth Secret.</note>
         <note>Signatures: A&#8308;.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "July 26".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>T: Deane</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
