<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A Full and the truest narrative of the most horrid, barbarous and unparalled murder, committed on the person of John Knight, apprentice to Mr. Arthur Worth, silk-man in milk-street, London. Which ... was committed by the desperate and bloody hand of Nathaniel Butler ... on Thursday morning August 6. 1657. Together with the manner of his being apprehended and examined; and the confession from the mouth of the said Butler ... an account of the tryall, condemnation and sentence pronounced against him, which was executed upon him, on Monday August 31. 1657. And his last speech upon the ladder immediately before his death, which he desired might be printed after his death; and to that end gave it at large in writing from off the ladder, to Mr. Yearwood chaplain to the right honourable Sir Robert Titchbourn lord mayor of London ...</title>
         <author>Butler, Nathaniel, d. 1657.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[4], 15, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">T. Mabb</persName> for <persName type="publisher">J. Saywell</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>the Pile of Bibles, the corner shop of the east end of the fish-market, in the stocks, looking into Lombard-street, over against the post house, between Cheap-side</placeName> and the .. ,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>[1657]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Imprint date from Thomason.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Septem. 4th".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>J. Saywell</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>T. Mabb</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the Pile of Bibles, the corner shop of the east end of the fish-market, in the stocks, looking into Lombard-street, over against the post house, between Cheap-side</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
