<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A fresh discovery of the high-Presbyterian spirit. Or The quenching of the second beacon fired. Declaring I. The un-Christian dealings of the authors of a pamphlet, entituled, A second beacon fired, &amp;c. In presenting unto the Lord Protector and Parlament, a falsified passage out of one of Mr John Goodwins books, as containing, either blasphemie, or error, or both. II. The evil of their petition for subjecting the libertie of the press to the arbitrariness and will of a few men. III. The Christian equity, that satisfaction be given to the person so notoriously and publickly wronged. Together with the responsatory epistle of the said beacon firers, to the said Mr Goodwin, fraught with further revilings, falsifications, scurrilous language, &amp;c. insteed of a Christian acknowledgment of their errour. Upon which epistle some animadversions are made, / by John Goodwin, a servant of God in the Gospel of his dear Son. Also two letters written some years since, the one by the said John Goodwin to Mr. J. Caryl; the other, by Mr Caryl in answer hereunto; both relating to the passage above hinted.</title>
      <author>Goodwin, John, 1594?-1665.</author>
      <author>Caryl, Joseph, 1602-1673.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[10], 84 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">the author</persName>, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">H. Cripps</persName>, and <persName type="publisher">L.Ll.</persName> in <placeName>Popes head Alley.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date>1654. [i.e. 1655]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>One of a series in a controversy over the publication of seditious or blasphemous works.</note>
      <note>Includes a letter from Goodwin to the so-called "Six booksellers" and their answer, with Goodwin's responses to it interspersed.</note>
      <note>Annotations on Thomason copy: "Jan: 5th";"Jan 5:".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>L.Ll.</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>the author</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>H. Cripps</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Popes head Alley.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
