<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Basanistai. Or The triers, (or tormenters) tried and cast, by the laws both of God and of men. Or, arguments and grounds as well in reason as religion, clearly evincing the unlawfulnesse of those ordinances or commissions (at least as they have been from time to time declared and interpreted, aloud by the persons acting them, and tacitly by the authority enacting them) with all others of like import, by which the respective courts, or consistories of triers and ejectors (so called) amongst us, are established: together with the unwarrantablenesse of the acceptation and exercise of the powers delegated and granted in the said commissions, by any man, or company of men whatsoever, now in being. By John Goodwin, an aged minister of Jesus Christ, and pastor to that remnant of his sheep, usually assembling in Coleman-street, London.</title>
         <author>Goodwin, John, 1594?-1665.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[16], 33, [3] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">Henry Eversden</persName>, at <placeName>the Grey-hound in Pauls Church-yard</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1657.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>First word of title transliterated from Greek.</note>
         <note>The words "or tormentors" are enclosed in square brackets on title page.</note>
         <note>Running title reads: The triers tried, and cast by the laws both of God and men.</note>
         <note>The first leaf is blank.</note>
         <note>The last leaf contains a postscript.</note>
         <note>With an errata slip.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "May 23".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Henry Eversden</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the Grey-hound in Pauls Church-yard</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
