<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The great memorial or, A list of the names of those pretended judges vvho sate, and sentenced our late soveraign King Charles the First, in the place which they called the High Court of Justice, January 27. 1648. And also of those witnesses sworne against the said King; the sentence read against him; with the catalogue of the names of those that subscribed and sealed the warrant for his execution; and the manner of his cruel murther.</title>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>1 sheet ([1] p.) : ill. (port.)  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Edward Thomas</persName> at <placeName>the Adam</placeName> and Eve in <placeName>Little Britain</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1660.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>In this edition (probably the later), the portrait of Charles I has no background and there is a small execution scene at upper left. There are 8 lines of engraved verse below, the first line reading "But lo a charg is drawne a day is set". Another edition, probably earlier and with title and text partly in a different setting, has an entirely different portrait of Charles I with cross-hatched background and a skull on a stand to the right at shoulder level. There are 8 lines of type-set verse under the portrait with first line reading "Weep England weep, help all to raise loud cry". In the earlier edition, line 4 of title begins "And also of those thirty five witnesses sworne" and the list of witnesses contains 35 names. In this later edition, line 4 of title begins "And also of those witnesses sworne" and the list of witnesses contains 30 names.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "May 8.".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Edward Thomas</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>Little Britain</placeName></place><place type="location"><placeName>the Adam</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
