<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The nullity of the pretended-assembly at Saint Andrews &amp; Dundee: wherein are contained, the representation for adjournment, the protestation &amp; reasons therof. Together with a review and examination of the Vindication of the said p. assembly. Hereunto is subjoyned the solemn acknowledgment of sins, and engagement to duties, made and taken by the nobility, gentry, burroughs, ministry, and commonalty, in the year 1648. when the Covenant was renewed. With sundry other papers, related unto in the foresaid review.</title>
         <author>Guthrie, James, 1612?-1661.</author>
         <author>Wood, James, 1608-1664.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[4], 5, 8-14, 7-22, 25-27, [1]; 312 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed [by <persName type="printer">E. Tyler]</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>[Leith] :</pubPlace>
         <date>in the yeer, 1652.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Anonymous. By James Guthrie.</note>
         <note>Place of publication from Wing; printer's name from Wing W3400.</note>
         <note>"A vindication of the freedom and lawfulnesse, and so of the authority of the late Generall Assembly, begun at St. Andrews, and continued in Dundee, .." (Wing W3400) has separate dated title page, pagination, and register. It is in fact a reprinting of and reply to: Wood, James.  A vindication of the freedom &amp; lawfulnes of the Generall Assembly begun at St. Andrews and continued at Dundee.</note>
         <note>The last digit of the imprint in the Huntington copy resembles a "3", and may be overprinted or stamped.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "ffebr:".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="printer"><persName>E. Tyler]</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
