<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The pagan preacher silenced. Or, an answer to a treatise of Mr. John Goodwin, entituled, the pagans debt &amp; dowry. Wherein is discovered the weaknesse of his arguments, and that it doth not yet appear by scripture, reason, or the testimony of the best of his own side, that the heathen who never heard of the letter of the Gospel, are either obliged to, or enabled for the believing in Christ; and that they are either engaged to matrimonial debt, or admitted to a matrimonial dowry. Wherein also is historically discovered, and polemically discussed the doctrin of Universal grace, with the original, growth and fall thereof; as it hath been held forth by the most rigid patrons of it. / By Obadiah Howe, A.M. and pastor of Horne-Castle in Lincolnshire. With a verdict on the case depending between Mr. Goodwin and Mr. Howe, by the learned George Kendal, DD.</title>
         <author>Howe, Obadiah, 1615 or 16-1683.</author>
         <author>Kendall, George, 1610-1663.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8], 11, [1], 120 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Th. Maxey</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">John Rothwell</persName>, at <placeName>the Fountian</placeName> and Bear in <placeName>Cheap-side.</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
         <date>1655.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A reply to: Goodwin, John. The pagans debt and dowry.</note>
         <note>The first numbered sequence of 11 pages contains: A verdict in the case depending between master J. Goodwin, and master Howe, concerning the Heavens preaching the Gospel; maintained by master Goodwin in his Pagans debt and dowry, as well as his Redemption redeemed. By George Kendall, D.D.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Aug. 16".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>John Rothwell</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>Th. Maxey</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>Cheap-side.</placeName></place><place type="location"><placeName>the Fountian</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
