<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>At the general quarter-sessions of the publick peace holden for the City of London by adjournament at Justice-hall in the old Baily London, on VVednesday the xij day of January in the year of our Lord 1652 before John Fowke Maior of the City of London, Thomas Atkins, Thomas Andrewes, Thomas Foote, John Kendricke, aldermen of the City of London, and William Steel recorder of the same city, Samuel Avery, Robert Titchborne and John Dethicke, aldermen of the said city, and other their fellowes justices assigned to keep the publick peace in the City of London, and also to hear and determine divers fellonies, trespasses and other misdemeanours within the same city committed.</title>
         <author>City of London (England).</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>1 sheet ([1] p.)   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">James Flesher</persName>, Printer to <persName type="patron">the Honourable City of London</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
         <date>[1653]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Imprint place and publication date from Wing.</note>
         <note>The response of the Corporation of London to the 10 December 1652 order of Parliament that the Lord Mayor and aldermen were to inquire into and take remedy for the extraordinary price of coal in which they fix the price "of seacoals untill further or other order shall be duely given in this behalfe".</note>
         <note>Signed: Sadler.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "January 12th".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="patron"><persName>the Honourable City of London</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>James Flesher</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
