<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A compendious body of chymistry, which will serve as a guide and introduction both for understanding the authors which have treated of the theory of this science in general and for making the way plain and easie to perform, according to art and method, all operations, which teach the practise of this art, upon animals, vegetables, and minerals, without losing any of the essential vertues contained in them. By N. le F&#232;bure apothecary in ordinary, and chymical distiller to the King of France, and at present to his Majesty of Great-Britain.</title>
      <title>Chimie th&#233;orique et pratique. English</title>
      <author>Le F&#232;vre, Nicaise, 1610-1669.</author>
      <author>P. D. C., One of the gentlemen of His Majesties Privy-Chamber.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[14], 312, [10], 364, [8] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">Tho. Davies</persName> and <persName type="publisher">Theo. Sadler, and is to be</persName> sold at <placeName>the sign of the Bible over against the little North-door of St. Pauls-Church</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1662.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Translation of: Chimie th&#233;orique et pratique.</note>
      <note>Nicasius le Febure = Nicaise Le F&#232;vre.</note>
      <note>Identified as Wing L924B, reel 2534, of the UMI microfilm set "Early English books 1641-1700".</note>
      <note>Part 1 has separate title page dated 1664 which follows general title page; Part 2 also has separate title page dated 1664, with separate pagination and register. Both have imprint: "London, printed by Tho. Ratcliffe for Octavian Pulleyn Junior, ..." and read: translated "into English by P.D.C. Esq. one of the gentlemen of his Majesties privy chamber."</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Glasgow University Library.</note>
      <note>Identified by ESTC as Wing (CD-ROM, 1996) L924A.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Theo. Sadler, and is to be</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Tho. Davies</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the sign of the Bible over against the little North-door of St. Pauls-Church</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
