<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The expert doctors dispensatory. The whole art of physick restored to practice. The apothecaries shop, and chyrurgions closet open'd; wherein all safe and honest practices are maintained, and dangerous mistakes discovered; and what out of subtilty for their own profits they have indeavoured to reserve to themselves, now at last impartially divulged and made common. Together with a strict survey of the dispensatories of the most renowned colledges of the world ... Containing, ... the Latine names of all simples and compounds English'd. ... the vertues, qualities, properties, quantities, and uses of all simples and componnds [sic]. ...the way of prescribing remedies; ... the nature, qualities, and symptomes of all diseases ... cautions for the applying all both internal and external medicines. To which is added by Jacob a Brunn ... a compendium of the body of physick; wherein all the medicaments vniversal and particular, simple and compound, are fitted to the practice of physick; and these forms of remedies now before prescribed by the famous P. Morellus, ...</title>
      <title>Methodus praescribendi formulas remediorum elegantissima. English</title>
      <author>Morel, Pierre.</author>
      <author>Brunn, Johannes Jacobus, 1591-1660. Systema materiae medicae. English.</author>
      <author>Culpeper, Nicholas, 1616-1654.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[30], 471, [9] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">N. Brook</persName> at <placeName>the Angel in Cornhil neer the Royal Exchange</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date>1657.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation, edited by Nicholas Culpeper, of: Morel, Pierre.  Methodus praescribendi formulas remediorum elegantissima.</note>
      <note>"The physicall magazeen. Or A systeme of the matter of physick, .. by Doctor Jacob A Brunn" has separate dated title page; register and pagination are continuous.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "August. 4.".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>N. Brook</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Angel in Cornhil neer the Royal Exchange</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
