<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A discovery of the man of sin, acting in a mystery of iniquitie, pleading for his kingdom, against the coming of Christ to take away sin. Or, an answer to a book set forth by Tho. Weld of Gateshead, Richard Prideaux, Sam. Hamond, Will. Cole, and Will. Durant of Newcastle. By way of reply to an answer of James Nayler's to their former book, called The perfect Pharisee: who call themselves ministers of Christ, but are found ministring for the kingdom of Antichrist. Published for clearing the innocency of the truth from their malicious slanders, and discovering their deceits. By one whom the world calls James Nayler.</title>
      <author>Naylor, James, 1617?-1660.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 51, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Giles Calvert</persName>, at <placeName>the black Spread-Eagle neer the west-end of Pauls.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date>1654.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A reply to: Weld, Thomas.  The perfect Pharisee under monkish holinesse, opposing the fundamentall principles of the doctrine of the Gospel, and Scripture-practices of Gospel-worship manifesting himselfe in the generation of men called Quakers.</note>
      <note>The names "Tho. Weld .. Newcastle." are enclosed in a complex system of brackets on title page.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "June. 3.".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Giles Calvert</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the black Spread-Eagle neer the west-end of Pauls.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
