<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Platerus golden practice of physick fully and plainly discovering, I. All the kinds. II. The several causes of every disease. III. Their most proper cures, in respect to the kinds, and several causes, from whence they come. After a new, easie, and plain method; of knowing, foretelling, preventing, and curing, all diseases incident to the body of man. Full of proper observations and remedies: both of ancient and modern physitians. In three books, and five tomes, or parts. Being the fruits of one and thirty years travel: and fifty years practice of physick. By Felix Plater, chief physitian and professor in ordinary at Basil. Abdiah Cole, doctor of physick, and the liberal arts. Nich. Culpeper, gent. student in physick, and astrology.</title>
         <author>Platter, Felix, 1536-1614.</author>
         <author>Cole, Abdiah, ca. 1610-ca. 1670. aut</author>
         <author>Culpeper, Nicholas, 1616-1654. aut</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[6], 446, 185-186, 499-688 p. : ill.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">Peter Cole, printer and</persName> book-seller, at <placeName>the sign of the Printing-press in Cornhill, near the Royal Exchange</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1664.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>The words "I. All the ... several causes" are joined by a right bracket, and the words "Felix Plater, ... astrology" are joined by a left bracket.</note>
         <note>Wing (CD-ROM edition) reports title as "The golden practice of physic".</note>
         <note>Text appears to be complete despite pagination.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the Folger Shakespeare Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="printer"><persName>Peter Cole, printer and</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the sign of the Printing-press in Cornhill, near the Royal Exchange</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
