<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Conscientious, serious theological and legal qu&#230;res, propounded to the twice-dissipated, self-created anti-Parliamentary Westminster juncto, and its Members. To convince them of, humble them for, convert them from their transcendent treasons, rebellions, perjuries, violences, oppressive illegal taxes, excises, militiaes, imposts; destructive councils, proceedings against their lawfull Protestant hereditarie kings, the old dissolved Parliament, the whole House of Lords, the majoritie of their old secured, secluded, imprisoned fellow-Members, the counties, cities, boroughs, freemen, commons, Church, clergie of England, their Protestant brethren, allies; contrary to all their oathes, protestations, vowes, leagues, covenants, allegiance, remonstrances, declarations, ordinances, promises, obligations to them, the fundamental laws, liberties of the land; and principles of the true Protestant religion; and to perswade them now at last to hearken to and embrace such counsels, as tend to publike unitie, safetie, peace, settlement, and their own salvation. / By William Prynne Esq; a bencher of Lincolns Inne.</title>
         <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 48, [2] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Edward Thomas</persName> at <placeName>the Adam</placeName> and Eve in <placeName>Little Britain</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1660.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>With a final errata leaf.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "9ber [i.e. November] 5".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="bookseller"><persName>Edward Thomas</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>Little Britain</placeName></place><place type="location"><placeName>the Adam</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
