<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Diotrephes catechised: or Sixteen important questions touching the ecclesiastical iurisdiction and censures (contradistinct to civill) now eagerly pretended to and challenged by a divine right, by some over-rigid Presbyterians, and Independents. Propounded to both these dissenting parties, for the further discovery of truth; the preservation of the civill Christian magistrates interest, and speedier comprimising [sic] of our present unhappie controversies touching church-government. On which many so over-dote, as to place the whole Kingdome of Christ and substance of religion therein: to repute all our former reformation, a meer nothing, the Church of Christ undone, and the exercise of their ministry, not only fruitlesse but unlawfull, so as they cannot with good conscience continue, but threaten to relinquish it, in case they cannot obtaine their demands of such an exorbitant power, by divine justicution, which Christ and his Apostles never claimed, exercised, nor themselves, nor predecessors, ever formerly enjoyed, petitioned for, or pretended to in any age, but this. / Proposed, published by W. Pryn, a well-wisher to verity and unitie.</title>
      <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <editionStmt>
      <edition>The third edition with some enlargements.</edition>
    </editionStmt>
    <extent>16 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Michael Sparke</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>Anno Dom. 1646.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "July 14th".</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the Harvard University Library and the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Michael Sparke</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
