<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A looking glasse for the Anabaptists and the rest of the separatists: wherein they may clearly behold a brief confutation of a certain un-licensed, scandelous pamphlet, intituled, The remonstrance of the Anabaptists, by way of vindication of their separation. The impertinancies, incongruities, non-consequences, falsities, and obstinacy of William Kiffen, the author, and grand ring leader of that seduced sect is discovered and laid open to the view of every indifferent eyed reader that will not shut his eyes against the truth. With certaine queries, vindicated from Anabaptisticall glosses, together with others propounded, for the information and conviction, (if possible) the reformation of the said William Kiffen and his prosylites. / By Josiah Ricraft, a well willer to the truth. Published by authority.</title>
         <author>Ricraft, Josiah, fl. 1645-1679.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[4], 26 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed, and are to be so[l]d by <persName type="printer">Peter Cole</persName> in <placeName>Cornhill, at the signe of the Printing Presse;</placeName> and John Hancock in <placeName>Popes-head Alley</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1645.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A reply to: Kiffin, William.  A briefe remonstrance of the reasons and grounds of those people commonly called Anabaptists, for their seperation, &amp;c. (Wing K423).</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Sept. 4th".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="printer"><persName>Peter Cole</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>Cornhill, at the signe of the Printing Presse;</placeName></place><place type="location"><placeName>Popes-head Alley</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
