<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The royal academy of complements. Wherein is set forth, a new packet of letters erected for ladies, gentlewomen, courtiers, gentlemen, scholars, souldiers, citizens, country-men, and all persons of what degree soever of both sexes, viz Complemental expressions towards men and women; leading to the art of courtship. 1. A tender of service to a King. 2. A tender of service to a Queen. 3. Respects from an honourable Lady to a Queen. 4. A fair young virgin to an old rich miser, whom her guardian did design should wed her. 5. A gentlemans request to his friend, to borrow money. 6. A gentleman to his friend, that sent to borrow money. 7. A virgin to her parents, that would have matched her to one whom she cannot love. 8. A courteous lass to her paramour, who had gotten her with child. 9. A husband to his lascivious wife. 10. A wife to her extravagant husband! 11. Civilities from one lady to another. 12. The forsaken maid, to her treacherous friend. 13. One ladies advice to another near marriage. 14. A gentleman to his lady, upon his urgent occasion to taking a journey. Composed by the most refin'd wits of this age.</title>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[16] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">E. H.</persName> and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Absalom Chamberlain, over against the Cap</persName> and <persName type="bookseller">Feather</persName>, in <placeName>White Cross-street, next to Old-street: removed from Swan-alley, in St. John-street</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>[1687?]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Signatures: A.</note>
         <note>Date of publication from Wing CD-ROM, 1996.</note>
         <note>MS. note on title page: 21. Jan: 1687/6.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the Folger Shakespeare Library, Washington, D.C..</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>E. H.</persName></person><person type="bookseller"><persName>Absalom Chamberlain, over against the Cap</persName></person><person type="bookseller"><persName>Feather</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>White Cross-street, next to Old-street: removed from Swan-alley, in St. John-street</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
