<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The history of the propagation &amp; improvement of vegetables by the concurrence of art and nature: shewing the several ways for the propagation of plants usually cultivated in England, as they are increased by seed, off-sets, suckers, truncheons, cuttings, slips, laying, circumposition, the several ways of graftings and inoculations; as likewise the methods for improvement and best culture of field, orchard, and garden plants, the means used for remedy of annoyances incident to them; with the effect of nature, and her manner of working upon the several endeavors and operations of the artist. Written according to observations made from experience and practice: / by Robert Sharrock, Fellow of New Colledge.</title>
         <author>Sharrock, Robert, 1630-1684.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[18], 59, [4], 60-150, [2] p. : fold. plate  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">A. Lichfield</persName>, printer to <persName type="patron">the University</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">Tho: Robinson.</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>Oxford :</pubPlace>
         <date>1660 [i.e. 1659]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>[2] pages at end = advertisements.</note>
         <note>[4] pages in middle of text = two leaves with metal plate of operations on vegetable stem and description; in some copies these are bound before advertisements, in others they are bound before page 60, and in yet others they are bound before page 70. Cf. Madan.</note>
         <note>Thomason received his copy in December 1659.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "xber [i.e. December] 1659"; imprint date crossed through.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Tho: Robinson.</persName></person><person type="patron"><persName>the University</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>A. Lichfield</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
