<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Two books of Mr Sydrach Simpson, late master of Pembroke-Hall in Cambridg; and preacher of the Gospel in London. Viz. I. Of unbelief; or the want of readiness to lay hold on the comfort given by Christ. II. Not going to Christ for life and salvation is an exceeding great sin, yet it is pardonable. In the first book is shewed (besides many other things) 1 What unbelief it is that is here spoken of ... 7 Helps to attain readiness in beleeving. In the second book is shewed, 1 That unbelief is a great sin, and exceeding provoking unto God ... 7 God hath pardoned unbelief, and wil pardon it.</title>
         <author>Simpson, Sidrach, 1600?-1655.</author>
         <author>Nye, Philip, 1596?-1672.</author>
         <author>Loder, John, 1625 or 6-1673.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[28], 126, [2], 129, [5]; [14], 281, [7] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">Peter Cole, printer and</persName> book-seller, at <placeName>the sign of the Printing-press, in Corn-hill, neer the Royall Exchange</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1658.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Editors' note "To the reader" signed: Philip Nye, John Loder.</note>
         <note>Signatures: pi&#178;  B-D&#8308; &#178; C-S&#8308; &#179;D-V&#8308; (-V4); chi&#8308; []&#8308; (-[]4) c-2p&#8308;.</note>
         <note>With a vertical half-title: Mr Simpson on unbelief.</note>
         <note>"Not going to Christ for life &amp; salvation, is an exceeding great sin" begins new pagination on &#179;D1r.</note>
         <note>"Two books of Mr Sydrach Simpson, .. Viz. I Of faith, .. II. Of covetousness. .." has separate dated title page and pagination beginning on c1r.</note>
         <note>Variant: the contents of leaves &#185;C3,4 appear on two leaves signed b1,2. The structure at this point is not known.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Decem: 14th".</note>
         <note>Identified on UMI microfilm (Early English books) as Wing S3828.</note>
         <note>Reproductions of the originals in Magdalen College, Oxford University (Early English books) and in the British Library (Thomason Tracts).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="printer"><persName>Peter Cole, printer and</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the sign of the Printing-press, in Corn-hill, neer the Royall Exchange</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
