<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The Lord Marquesse of Hertford, his letter, sent to the Queen in Holland. Also a letter from the committee in Sommersetshire, to the Houses of Parliament, with a copy of their message to Marquesse Hertford, and his men assembled in arms at Shepton-Mallet, his answer thereunto, and their resolution upon the same. Likewise the information that both Houses received from a marchant in Roterdam, relating how divers captains, and other officers upon a letter from the Queen to the Prince of Orange, are by him discharged, and sent over into England for His Majesties service in the north; and how the papists there have given to the King two hundred thousand pound in mony; with sundry other matters of great concernment. Whereunto is added, certain votes of the Lords and Commons in Parliament, for the apprehending, and bringing up, Sir Ralph Hopton, Master Thomas Smith, Captain John Digby; members of the House of Commons, with Sir Ferdinando Gorges, Sir Francis Dodington, and some others as delinquents. Ordered by the Lords and Commons assembled in Parliament, that these particulars be forthwith printed and published. Joh. Brown, Cler. Parliament.</title>
         <author>Somerset, William Seymour, Duke of, 1588-1660.</author>
         <author>England and Wales. Parliament. aut</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>8, 7, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>August 8. London, Printed for <persName type="publisher">Joseph Huscott</persName>, and <persName type="publisher">John Wright</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
         <date>[August 8] 1642.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>John Wright</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>Joseph Huscott</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
