<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Horometria: or The compleat diallist. Wherein the whole mystery of the art of dialling is plainly taught three several wayes; two of which are performed geometrically by rule and compass onely: and the third instrumentally, by a quadrant fitted for that purpose. With the working of such propositions of the sphere, as are most usefull in astronomy and navigation ... By Thomas Stirrup, philomath. Whereunto is added an appendix, shewing how the parallels of declination; the Jewish, Babylonish, &amp; Italian houres; the azimuths, almicanters, &amp;c. may be easily inscribed on any dial whatsoever, by rule and compasse onely. And to draw a diall on the seeling of a room, by W. Leybourn. Also, Dialling Vniversal, performed by an easie and most speedy way,  ... by certain scales set on a small portable ruler, by G.S. practitioner in the mathematicks.</title>
         <author>Stirrup, Thomas.</author>
         <author>Leybourn, William, 1626-1716. Appendix, shewing how the parallels of declination; the Jewish, Babylonish, &amp; Italian hours; the asimuths, almicanters &amp;c. may be easily inscribed on any dial whatsoever.</author>
         <author>Serle, George. Dialling universal.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <editionStmt>
         <edition>The second edition with additions.</edition>
      </editionStmt>
      <extent>[8], 184; [8], 131, [1] p. : ill. (woodcuts)  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">R.</persName> &amp; <persName type="printer">W. Leybourn</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Pierrepont</persName>, at <placeName>the Sun in Paul's Church-yard</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1659 [i.e.1658]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Frontis = ill.</note>
         <note>"An appendix" has separate dated title page; pagination and register are continuous. "Dialling universal" has separate dated titlepage, pagination, and register and is cataloged separately.</note>
         <note>"Dialling universal" (S2622) also issued separately.</note>
         <note>S2622 appears on UMI microfilm set (Thomason Tracts) on reel 143, E.956[3].</note>
         <note>G.S = George Serle  cf. Wing.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Octob: 20".</note>
         <note>Bound with Thomason items from 1658.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Thomas Pierrepont</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>R.</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>W. Leybourn</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the Sun in Paul's Church-yard</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
