<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Elijah's mantle: or, The remaines of that late worthy and faithful servant of Jesus Christ, Mr. John Tillinghast. Viz. I. The conformity of a saint to the will of God. On Act. 21.14. II. The will of God and Christ concerning sinners. On Gal. 1.4. III. No condemnation to them that are in Christ Jesus. On Rom. 8.1. IV. Christs love to his owne. On Joh. 13.1. V. True gospel humiliation. On Zach. 12.10. VI. The most effectual means to kill and subdue sin. On 1 Joh. 2.2 VII. The advocateship of Jesus Christ, a great ground of saints comfort and support under sins and infirmities. On 1 Joh. 2.2. VIII. The only way for saints to be delivered from the errors and evils of the times. On 1 Tim. 6.11. IX. Of the Old Covenant, from Gal. 4.30. being so farre as the author had proceeded, in a treatise of the two covenants, before his death. Published by his owne notes.</title>
         <author>Tillinghast, John, 1604-1655.</author>
         <author>Manning, John, d. 1694.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[32], 271, 274-566 [i.e. 466] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">Livewell Chapman</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>the Crown in Popes-head Alley.</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
         <date>1658.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Editors' prefaces signed by John Manning and three others.</note>
         <note>P. 466 misnumbered 566.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Jan 30"; the 8 in the imprint date has been crossed out and replaced with a "7".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>Livewell Chapman</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the Crown in Popes-head Alley.</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
