<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>To the right honourable, the peeres assembled in Parliament The humble petition of the sheriffe, knights, esquires, gentlemen, ministers, freeholders and others inhabitants of the county of Bedford.</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament. House of Lords.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>1 sheet ([1]  p.)   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed on <placeName>Bread-street-hill</placeName> by <persName type="printer">a true copy</persName>, with the petitioners approbation, at <placeName>the charge of John Chambers</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date>1641 [i.e. 1642]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Place and date of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>Includes: To the right honourable, the knights, citizens, and Burgesses in the Commons House of Parliament assembled. The humble petition of the hign sheriffe, knights, esquires, gentlemen, ministers, freeholders and others inhabitants of the county of Bedford.</note>
      <note>The first petition thanks the Lords for their help to the Commons. The second thanks the Commons for the Ordinance for the Militia and asks for the relief of Ireland, disarmament of Papists, and the appointment of faithfull ministers. -- Steele.</note>
      <note>With an order to print by the House of Commons, signed: Hen. Elsinge Cler. Dom. Com.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>a true copy</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Bread-street-hill</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the charge of John Chambers</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
