<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The Pope's cabinet unlocked, or, A catalogue of all the popes indulgences belonging to the order of S. Mary together with a list of all the indulgences daily, yearly, and for ever, to be had at Rome, S. James of Galatia in Compostella, Jerusalem and all places in the Holy Land / written in Italian by Fr. Ancangelo Tortello of the said order of S. Mary : and now translated into English by John Sidway late seminary priest, but now of the reformed religion and vicar of selling in Kent and one of the discoverers of the horrid popish plot, with the cause of his conversion : whereunto is added an appendix by the translator in which the grounds and foundation of the said indulgences being themselves apparently proved to be meer cheats : and also shewing that the Church of Rome doth lay the chief basis of their religion on indulgences : dedicated to the right honourable the Earl of Shaftsbury.</title>
      <author>Tortello, Arcangelo.</author>
      <author>Sidway, John.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8], 77 (i.e. 76) p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Isaac Cleve</persName> at <placeName>the Star next to Serjeants-Inn in Chancery-Lane</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1680.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Item at reel 2318:23 incorrectly identified as Wing T1943aA.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of originals in Library of Congress and Bodleian Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Isaac Cleve</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Star next to Serjeants-Inn in Chancery-Lane</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
