<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The doctrines of the Arminians &amp; Pelagians truly stated and clearly answered: or, An examination and confutation of their ancient errors, which by the Church of Christ in former ages were justly abhorred, but of late under the names of Comfortable truths to be embraced are newly published. Concerning I. The universality of Gods free-grace in Christ to mankind. II. Concerning election. III. Redemption. IV. Conversion. V. Perserverance. Wherein the principal arguments brought to maintaine the orthodox faith are propounded, and the principal objections against them answered. / By Thomas Whitfield, minister of the gospel at Bugbrook in Northampton-shire. The Tares of Arminian heresie showed in former times (and by the help of prelatical influence then given to them increasing) and now growing up so much in these; I conceive this book wherein the author doth learnedly state and confute those opinions, is very worthy the publike light. Joseph Caryll.</title>
         <author>Whitfield, Thomas, Minister of the Gospel.</author>
         <author>Carly, Joseph, 1602-1673.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 99 [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">John Bellamie</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop at the three golden Lions in Corn-hill neer the Royall Exchange</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1652 [i.e. 1651]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Nouemb. 20th".</note>
         <note>Thomason copy bound with items from November 1651.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>John Bellamie</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>his shop at the three golden Lions in Corn-hill neer the Royall Exchange</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
