<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A letter intercepted (at sea) by Captaine Moulton, and sent by the Admiralls to the councell of state. Written from Parson Wolby, directed to Mr. Edward Ball, the Princes agent, with Prince Rupert at Kingsale in Ireland. Wherein is discovered a most fearfull and sad designe against the City of London, and such who have estates in England. A new platforme of the Catholicke religion, intended for England. Severall transactions of the Prince's Navy. And the Governour of the island of Scilly. And an account of the Governours letter (who is salne sick) to the Prince. Parson VVolby his desires to Prince Rupert, and his transactions with Sir John Moene, Sir John Beak, Doctor Wats, and Mr. Ball. And some transactions at sea, between 500 of the King of Spain his souldiers at sea, and the Princes Navy. And severall fights at sea, with other considerable passages of the Princes Navy. May 7. 1649. To the end that all who are faithfull to this nation, may unanimously unite, against the common enemy; whose bitternesse doth appeare against us, both in words, and action, in this letter. Therefore I say imprimatur: Theodore Jennings.</title>
      <author>Wolley, Edward, 1603-1684.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 6 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Robert Ibbitson</persName>, in <placeName>Smithfield, neer the Queens-head Tavern</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1649.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Robert Ibbitson</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Smithfield, neer the Queens-head Tavern</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
