<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Directions to young clerks in the court of Kings Bench for making the process of the said court retornable, both at days certain and ubicunque; with other directions in order thereunto. By John Warter, Sen. gent. Deceased.</title>
         <author>Warter, John.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>1 sheet ([1] p.)   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed for and sold by <persName type="bookseller">William Warter stationer</persName>, at <placeName>the sign of the Talbot over against the east end of St. Dunstan's Church in Fleetstreet, where you may be furnished with all sorts of blank bonds, blank writs, blank warrants</placeName> for <persName type="publisher">justices, licenses</persName> for <persName type="publisher">alehouses, blank indentures</persName> for <persName type="publisher">apprentices, blank indentures to put out parish children</persName> by <persName type="printer">the Justices of the Peace, blank Declarations</persName> in <placeName>Ejectment in the King's Bench or Common Pleas, blank rules in ejectment in the King's Bench, blank bayl bonds</placeName> for <persName type="publisher">appearance, blank tickets</persName> for <persName type="publisher">subpena's</persName> for <persName type="publisher">London</persName>, <persName type="publisher">Westminster, or the Assizes, or</persName> for <persName type="publisher">any other court, blank warrants of attorney to confess judgment, or to acknowledge satisfaction</persName> on <placeName>record</placeName>...,</publisher><pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1680.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>London</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>Westminster, or the Assizes, or</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>alehouses, blank indentures</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>any other court, blank warrants of attorney to confess judgment, or to acknowledge satisfaction</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>appearance, blank tickets</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>apprentices, blank indentures to put out parish children</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>justices, licenses</persName></person><person type="publisher"><persName>subpena's</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>the Justices of the Peace, blank Declarations</persName></person><person type="bookseller"><persName>William Warter stationer</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>Ejectment in the King's Bench or Common Pleas, blank rules in ejectment in the King's Bench, blank bayl bonds</placeName></place><place type="location"><placeName>record</placeName></place><place type="location"><placeName>the sign of the Talbot over against the east end of St. Dunstan's Church in Fleetstreet, where you may be furnished with all sorts of blank bonds, blank writs, blank warrants</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
