<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The parfait mareschal, or Compleat farrier. Which teacheth, I. To know the shapes and goodness, as well as faults and imperfections of horses. II. The signs and causes of their diseases, the means to prevent them, their cure, and the good or bad use of purging and bleeding. III. The way to order and preserve them, when upon travel, to feed, and to dress them. IV. The art of shoeing, according to a new design of shoes, which will recover bad feet, and preserve the good. Together with a treatise, how to raise and bring up a true and beautiful race of horses: as also instructions, whereby to fit all kinds of horses with proper bits, whereof the chief draughts are represented in copper-plates. / Written originally in French by the Sieur de Solleysel Escuyer, sometime one of the overseers of the French Kings Royal Academy of Riding, near to the Hostel de Conde in Paris. And translated from the last Paris impression, by Sir William Hope of Kirkliston Kt. Lieutenat Governour of the Castle of Edinburgh. By whom is also added as a supplement to the first part, a most compendious and excellent collection of horsemanship, taken from the best and most modern writers upon that subject, such as Mr. De la Brow, Pluvinel, and the Great Duke of Newcastle. Part I.</title>
         <title>Parfait mareschal. English. 1696</title>
         <author>Solleysel, Jacques de, 1617-1680.</author>
         <author>Hope, William, Sir.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[52], 261, [5], 86, [18], 300, [4] p, 8 leaves of plates (six folded) : ill.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">George Mosman</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>Edinburgh :</pubPlace>
         <date>M.DC.XCVI. [i.e. 1696]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>With additional engraved title pages.</note>
         <note>Includes indices.</note>
         <note>"A supplement of horsemanship, to the first part of The parfair mareschal ... by Sir William Hope" has separate undated title page, with imprint "Printed in Edinburgh", pagination and register.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the National Library of Scotland.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="printer"><persName>George Mosman</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
