<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>An aduertisement from a French gentleman, touching the intention and meaning which those of the house of Guise haue in their late leuying of forces and armes in the realme of France written as an answere to a certaine declaration published in the name of the Cardinal of Burbon.</title>
         <title>Advertissement sur l'intention et but de MM. de Guise en la prise des armes. English</title>
         <author>Mornay, Philippe de, seigneur du Plessis-Marly, 1549-1623.</author>
         <author>Somerset, Thomas.</author>
         <author>Bourbon, Charles, Cardinal de, 1520-1590.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 66, 12 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">C. Barker]</persName>,</publisher><pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
         <date>Anno 1585. Iune.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A French gentleman = Philippe de Mornay.</note>
         <note>Translation by Thomas Somerset of: Advertissement sur l'intention et but de MM. de Guise en la prise des armes.</note>
         <note>Place of publication and printer's name from STC.</note>
         <note>"A declaration of the causes that haue mooued the Cardinal of Bourbon, the princes .. to oppose themselves to those which by all meanes do seeke to subvert the Catholike religion and the estate" (caption title) has separate pagination; register is continuous.</note>
         <note>Identified as STC 154 on UMI microfilm reel 163, and as STC 12505 on reel 320.</note>
         <note>Reproductions of the originals in the Bodleian Library and the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
         <note>Appears at reels 163 and 203 (Bodleian Library copy, same copy filmed twice) and at reel 320 (Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery copy).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="printer"><persName>C. Barker]</persName></person></listPerson></sourceDesc>
