<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A dreadful warning to lewd livers: or, God's revenge against drunkards, swearers, whoremongers, blasphemers, and prophaners of the Lords Day. In about 24 examples of strange judgements immediately inflicted on such notorious sinners, enough to make the ears to tingle, and their hearts to ake that read and consider them containing, 20 visible judgements against drunkards, 11 upon swearers and cursers. 5 remarkable examples of Gods wrath upon whoremongers and adulterers. And 6 against prophaners of the Lords Day. VVith divers seasonable admonitions to avoid these several crying sins, which threaten all that follow them with destruction, both in this world, and that to come. Our God is a consuming fire. / By Mr. Baxter.</title>
         <author>Baxter, Richard, 1615-1691.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>1 sheet ([1] p.). ill.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">P. Brooksby</persName>, at <placeName>the Golden-Ball, near the Hospital-Gate, in West-smithfield</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
         <date>[1682?]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Caption title.</note>
         <note>Sometimes attributed to Richard Baxter; BMC call this "A suppostitious work."</note>
         <note>Imprint from colophon; place and date of publication from Wing.</note>
         <note>Printed in three columns.</note>
         <note>The words "20 visible ... and cursers." are gathered by braces; the words "VVith divers ... and that to come." are gathered by a left brace.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="publisher"><persName>P. Brooksby</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>the Golden-Ball, near the Hospital-Gate, in West-smithfield</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
