<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>By the Lord Lieutenant and council. Ormonde. Whereas we the Lord Lieutenant and Council are required by letters from the Lords of his Majesties most honourable Privy-council in England, dated the sixth of February, 1684. to publish in this Kingdom a proclamation signed by His Majesty: which followeth in these words: A proclamation signifying his majesties pleasures, that all men being in office of Government at the decease of the Late King His Majesties most dear and most entirely beloved brother, shall so continue until His Majeties further directions.</title>
      <author>Ireland. Lord Lieutenant (1677-1685 : Ormonde)</author>
      <author>Ormonde, James Butler, Duke of, 1610-1688.</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Sovereign (1685-1688 : James II). Forasmuch as it hat pleased almighty God lately to call unto his infinite mercy the most high and mighty prince, King Charles the second, ...</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>2 sheets ([2] leaves).   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Benjamin Tooke</persName>, printer to <persName type="patron">the Kings most Excellent Majesty</persName>, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Andrew Crook</persName> in <placeName>Skinner-row</placeName>, and <persName type="bookseller">Samuel Helsham</persName> at <placeName>the Coledge-arms in Castle-street</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Dublin :</pubPlace>
      <date>1684</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>At end of text: Given at the Council-Chamber in Dublin, this eleventh day of February, 1684.</note>
      <note>Arms 187; Steele notation: by  vy  2) Go-  As.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="patron">
      <persName>the Kings most Excellent Majesty</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Andrew Crook</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Samuel Helsham</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Benjamin Tooke</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Skinner-row</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Coledge-arms in Castle-street</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
