<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Commune concilium tentum in camera Guildhall civitatis London, die veneris, vicesimo septimo die Octobris, anno Domini, 1671. Annoq; Regni Domini nostri Caroli Secundi, Dei gratia, Angli&#230;, Scoti&#230;, Franci&#230;, &amp; Hiberni&#230; Regis, Fidei Defensoris, &amp;c. vicesimo tertio; coram Ricardo Ford, milite, majore civitatis London, Ricardo Chiverton, &amp; Johanne Frederick, militibus, Johanne Robinson, milite &amp; baronetto, locum-tenente turris, Thoma Bludworth, Willielmo Peake, Samuele Starling, Roberto Hanson, &amp; Josepho Sheldon, militibus, &amp; Patiente Ward, armigero, aldermannis, Jonathan Dawes &amp; Roberto Clayton, armigeris, aldermannis ac vicecomitibus dict&#230; civitatis London, necnon majore parte communiariorum de Communi Concilio ejusdem civitatis tunc &amp; ibidem assemblat. An Act for setling of lay-stalls, preventing several inconveniences to passengers, and relating also to the cleansing of the streets and passages within this city and liberties thereof</title>
         <title>Act for setling of lay-stalls, preventing several inconveniences to passengers, and relating also to the cleansing of the streets and passages within this city and liberties thereof.</title>
         <author>City of London (England). Court of Common Council.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>3 sheets (verso blank)   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Andrew Clark</persName>, printer to <persName type="patron">the honourable City of London</persName>, at <placeName>his house in Aldersgatestreet</placeName>,</publisher><pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
         <date>MDCLXXI. [1671]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Imprint from colophon.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
<listPerson><person type="patron"><persName>the honourable City of London</persName></person><person type="printer"><persName>Andrew Clark</persName></person></listPerson><listPlace><place type="location"><placeName>his house in Aldersgatestreet</placeName></place></listPlace></sourceDesc>
