<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The elements of geometrie of the most auncient philosopher Euclide of Megara. Faithfully (now first) translated into the Englishe toung, by H. Billingsley, citizen of London. Whereunto are annexed certaine scholies, annotations, and inuentions, of the best mathematiciens, both of time past, and in this our age. With a very fruitfull pr&#230;face made by M. I. Dee, specifying the chiefe mathematicall scie[n]ces, what they are, and wherunto commodious: where, also, are disclosed certaine new secrets mathematicall and mechanicall, vntill these our daies, greatly missed</title>
      <title>Elements. English</title>
      <author>Euclid.</author>
      <author>Dee, John, 1527-1608.</author>
      <author>Candale, Fran&#231;ois de Foix, comte de, 1502-1594.</author>
      <author>Billingsley, Henry, Sir, d. 1606.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[28], 203, 205-464, [1] leaves, folded table : ill.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">Iohn Daye</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date>[1570 (3 Feb.]]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>With a sixteenth book added by Fran&#231;ois de Foix, comte de Candale.</note>
      <note>Colophon reads: At London printed by Iohn Daye, dvvelling ouer Aldersgate beneath Saint Martins. These bookes are to be solde at his shop vnder the gate. 1570.</note>
      <note>The folded table, dated 25 Feb. 1570 and showing the topics covered in Dee's preface, gives the date of the book's publication as 3 Feb.</note>
      <note>Book 11 has onlays intended to be pasted at one edge over the illustrations. These were printed together on six bifolia. Variant: these bifolia are still intact and bound with book.</note>
      <note>The last leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Iohn Daye</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
