<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Newes out of France: concerning great troubles likely to ensue, by occasion of the departure of the Queene Mother from Blois and the causes thereof. Contayned in the letters of the said Queene Mother, vnto her sonne the French King, and his answere therevnto; manifesting the motiues of his taking vp armes, and against whom he entends to imploy them. Dated the 17. of March, 1619. VVith foure other letters of the Queene Mother, to the Lord Chancelor, Keeper of the Seales; President Iannin, and Duke de Mayenne, and the Prince of Pyemont his letter vnto her, concerning these affaires. Faithfully translated, according to the French copie.</title>
         <author>Marie de M&#233;dicis, Queen, consort of Henry IV, King of France, 1573-1642.</author>
         <author>Louis XIII, King of France, 1601-1643.</author>
         <author>Savoie, Victor-Am&#233;, duc de, 1587-1637.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>8; 4, 18 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by T[homas] S[nodham] for Nathanael Newbery, and are to bee sould at his shop vnder S. Peters Church in Cornehill, and in Popes-head Alley at the signe of the Star,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1619">1619.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Evidently a translation of one of several French editions of the same year.</note>
         <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
         <note>"The Queene Mothers first letter, sent vnto the King of France, her sonne, from Loche, the 23. of February, 1619. stilo nouo" begins new register and pagination; within this register, "A letter written by the King of France, in answere to a letter sent by the Queene his mother, bearing date the 17. of March 1619. stilo nouo" has separate dated title page and pagination.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
