<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The mariage of Prince Fredericke, and the Kings daughter, the Lady Elizabeth, vpon Shrouesunday last VVith the shovves on land and water, before, and after the wedding, as also the maskes and reuells in his Highnes court, with the running at the ring, by the Kings Maiestie, the Palsegraue, Prince Charles, and diuers others of the nobilitie.</title>
      <title>Marriage of the two great princes, Fredericke Count Palatine, &amp;c: and the Lady Elizabeth, daughter to the Imperial Majesties of King James and Queene Anne.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <editionStmt>
      <edition>Now the second time imprinted, with many new additions, of the same tryumphs, performed by the gentlemen of the Innes of Court in the Kings pallace of white Hall.</edition>
    </editionStmt>
    <extent>[16] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">T[homas] C[reede]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">W. Barley</persName>, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">W. Wright</persName>, at <placeName>his shop neere S. Pulchers Church, at the signe of the Harrow</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1613.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>An enlarged edition of: The marriage of the two great princes, Fredericke Count Palatine, &amp;c: and the Lady Elizabeth, daughter to the Imperial Majesties of King James and Queene Anne.</note>
      <note>With a title-page woodcut.</note>
      <note>The first word of the title is xylographic.</note>
      <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A-B&#8308;.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: Ioyfull triumphs at the royall mariage.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>W. Wright</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>W. Barley</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>T[homas] C[reede]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop neere S. Pulchers Church, at the signe of the Harrow</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
