<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The exercise of armes for caliures, muskettes, and pikes after the ordre of his Excellence. Maurits Prince of Orange Counte of Nassau etc. Gouernour and Captaine generall. ouer Geldreland. Holland, Zeeland, Vtrecht. Overyssel. etc. Sett forthe in figures. by Iacob de Gheyn. With written instructions. for the service of all captaines and comaundours. For to shewe hereout the better vnto their jong or vntrayned souldiers the playne and perfett maner to handle these armes.</title>
      <title>Wapen-handelinghe van roers, musquetten, en spiessen. English</title>
      <author>Gheyn, Jacob de, 1565-1629.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[20] p., 42, [43], 32 plates   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>They are toe bye at <placeName>Amsterdam</placeName> by <persName type="printer">Robert de Baudous. 1608. Printed</persName> at <placeName>the Hage. With priviledge of the Emperours Matie. the King of Fraunce</placeName>, and the noble and mightye Estates General of the vnited Provinces,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[The Hague] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1608">[1608]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of: Gheyn, Jacob de.  Wapen-handelinghe van roers, musquetten, en spiessen.</note>
      <note>The title page is engraved, with compartments left blank for three English pasted-on engraved labels: (1) arms of Henry, later Prince of Wales, (2) title (see next note for variant), and (3) imprint. Title page variant 1: dated 1607. Title variant 2: dated 1608, but blank spaces now engraved with the arms of Maurice, Prince of Orange (shield with bugles and lions rampant); title in French ("Maniement d'armes d'arquebuses, mousquetz, et piques"); imprint "Imprim&#233; a Amsterdam chez Robert de Badous .."; Latin dedication to Maurice ("Illustrissimo principi, maximo duci, Mauritio Nassauio .."), ending with "On les vend' ausi a Amsterdam chez H. Laurens". Variant 3: like variant 2, but lacking the words "On les vend' ..".</note>
      <note>Pasted-on title label variant 1: lacks the line "They are toe bye ..".</note>
      <note>This edition has nine leaves of English letterpress: dedication is on pi&#185;; preface is on ([three stars])&#185;; A-B&#185; contain directions for the caliver; A-B&#185; (signed in italic) contain directions for the musket; a-b&#185; [c]&#185; contain directions for the pike.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Robert de Baudous. 1608. Printed</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Amsterdam</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Hage. With priviledge of the Emperours Matie. the King of Fraunce</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
