<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Certaine sermons, vpon diuers textes of Holie Scripture Whereof some haue been seuerally before published, and other some for the greater benefit of the godly reader are here now added. By M. George Giffard, preacher of the worde of God at Mauldon Essex.</title>
      <author>Gifford, George, d. 1620.</author>
      <author>Gifford, George, d. 1620. A sermon on the parable of the sower. aut</author>
      <author>Gifford, George, d. 1620. Two sermons upon I. Peter 5. vers. 8 and 9. aut</author>
      <author>Gifford, George, d. 1620. Foure sermons uppon the seven chiefe vertues of faith. aut</author>
      <author>Gifford, George, d. 1620. A godlie, zealous, and profitable sermon upon the second chapter of saint James. aut</author>
      <author>Gifford, George, d. 1620. A sermon preached at Pauls Crosse the thirtie day of May. aut</author>
      <author>Gifford, George, d. 1620. A sermon on the third chapter of Saint Iames. aut</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>288 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">the Widowe Orwin</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Man</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1597">1597.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Reprints in the following order: STC 11862.5: "A sermon on the parable of the sower"; STC 11871: "Two sermons upon I. Peter 5. vers. 8 and 9"; STC 11857.5: "Foure sermons uppon the seven chiefe vertues of faith"; STC 11860: "A godlie, zealous, and profitable sermon upon the second chapter of saint James"; and STC 11862.3: "A sermon preached at Pauls Crosse the thirtie day of May"; adding a sermon on James iii 1-12 before the last. Contents list on title page verso also calls for a reissue? of STC 11870, which is not present.--Cf. STC.</note>
      <note>Each sermon has caption title.</note>
      <note>Identified as STC 11848a on UMI microfilm, reel 713.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Folger Shakespeare Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Man</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>the Widowe Orwin</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
