<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The Kings medicine for this present yeere 1604 prescribed by the whole colledge of the spirituall physitions, made after the coppy of the corporall kings medicine, which was vsed in the city the former yeere. Giuen as a new yeers-gift, to the honorable city of London, to be taken in this yeere for the soule, as the other was for the bodie. Herevnto are intermixed, first, the wonders of the former yeer, his triumphs, two funeralls, two coronations, two preachers. Secondlie, Londons and Englands newyeers-gift, to offer vp vnto the Lord for his new-yeers-gift, containing King Dauids sacrificing after the ceasing of the pestilence, necessarie to teach vs the duty of our deliuerance. The whole collected out of the first book of Chr. ch. 21. / Made and vvritten by Iames Godskall, preacher of the vvorde.</title>
      <author>Godskall, James.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[206] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed [by <persName type="printer">R. Bradock?</persName> and <persName type="printer">E. Allde?]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Edward White</persName>, at <placeName>the little Northdoore of Saint Pauls Church, at the signe of the gunne</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1604">[1604]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Printers' names suggested by STC.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A-N (-A1).</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Folger Shakespeare Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Edward White</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>E. Allde?]</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>R. Bradock?</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the little Northdoore of Saint Pauls Church, at the signe of the gunne</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
