<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Archontorologion, or The diall of princes containing the golden and famous booke of Marcus Aurelius, sometime Emperour of Rome. Declaring what excellcncy [sic] consisteth in a prince that is a good Christian: and what euils attend on him that is a cruell tirant. Written by the Reuerend Father in God, Don Antonio of Gueuara, Lord Bishop of Guadix; preacher and chronicler to the late mighty Emperour Charles the fift. First translated out of French by Thomas North, sonne to Sir Edward North, Lord North of Kirthling: and lately reperused, and corrected from many grosse imperfections. With addition of a fourth booke, stiled by the name of The fauoured courtier.</title>
         <title>Relox de pr&#237;ncipes. English</title>
         <author>Guevara, Antonio de, Bp., d. 1545?</author>
         <author>Munday, Anthony, 1553-1633.</author>
         <author>North, Thomas, Sir, 1535-1601?</author>
         <author>Guevara, Antonio de, Bp., d. 1545? Aviso de privados. English.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[48], 542 [i.e. 560], [2], 561-566, 571-574, 571-768 [i.e. 766] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Imprinted by Bernard Alsop, dwelling by Saint Annes Church neere Aldersgate,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1619">1619.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A translation of the authorised version of: Relox de principes.</note>
         <note>Editor's dedication signed: A.M., i.e. Anthony Munday.</note>
         <note>The first word of the title is in Greek characters.</note>
         <note>P. 560 misnumbered 542; p. 766 misnumbered 768.</note>
         <note>"The fourth booke of the Diall of princes", a translation of "Aviso de privados", has separate dated title page; pagination and register are continuous.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Library of Congress.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
