<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The vnion of the two noble and illustre famelies of Lancastre [and] Yorke, beeyng long in continual discension for the croune of this noble realme with all the actes done in bothe the tymes of the princes, bothe of the one linage and of the other, beginnyng at the tyme of kyng Henry the fowerth, the first aucthor of this deuision, and so successiuely proceadyng to the reigne of the high and prudent prince kyng Henry the eight, the vndubitate flower and very heire of both the sayd linages.</title>
      <author>Hall, Edward, d. 1547.</author>
      <author>Grafton, Richard, d. 1572?</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], C.lxxviij, C.lxxxj-C.xciij, C.xcv-CC.lx [i.e. 250], lix, [1], lxi, [1], CC.lxiij, [1] leaves   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>In officina Richardi Graftoni typis <persName type="printer">impress.]</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Londini :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1548">1548.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>By Edward Hall, whose name appears on [fleuron]2r.</note>
      <note>Continued from 1532 by Richard Grafton from Hall's notes.</note>
      <note>Printer's name from colophon.</note>
      <note>"The pitifull life of kyng Edward the. v.", "The politique gouernaunce of Kyng Henry the. vii.", and "The triumphaunt reigne of Kyng Henry the. VIII." (caption titles) each begin new foliation on AA1r, aaa1r, and AAa1r respectively.</note>
      <note>First series, leaf 250 misnumbered CC.lx.</note>
      <note>In the ideal configuration of this edition the second leaf is signed "[fleuron].ii."; third leaf verso mentions plans for the compilation of a table; fourth leaf recto has "Englishe writers."; in quires Aa-Rr most paragraphs begin with a word in roman type; remaining quires lack line numbers in inner margin. Originally issued without the tables. Copies containing sheets partly from other editions are matched to STC 12723a. For details of printing history see STC corrigendum to vol. 1, p. 557.</note>
      <note>Another state of the title page (STC 12721) has "strate .. Yorke" (no comma) in line 3.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>impress.]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
