<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A short relation of the departure of the high and mightie Prince Frederick King Elect of Bohemia: with his royall &amp; vertuous Ladie Elizabeth; and the thryse hopefull yong Prince Henrie, from Heydelberg towards Prague, to receiue the crowne of that kingdome Whearvnto is annexed the solempnitie or maner of the coronation. Translated out of dutch. And now both togither published ... to giue satisfaction to the world, as touching the ground, and truth, of his Maties. proceedings, &amp; vndertaking of that kingdome ... As also to encourage all other noble &amp; heroicall spirits (especiallie our owne nation, whom in h&#244;nour it first and chieffelie concerneth) by prerogative of that high, and soveraigne title, h&#230;reditarie to our kings &amp; princes: defendees [sic] of the faith) to the lyke Christian resolution, against Antichrist and his adh&#230;rents.</title>
      <author>Harrison, John, fl. 1610-1638.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[16] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Prinred [sic] by <persName type="printer">George Waters</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>At Dort :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1619">1619.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"To the reader" signed "Iohn Harrison", who wrote the first part. To this are appended "some [Latin] anagrams which a frend of myne gave me". The second part is a translation of: Corte ende warachtige beschrijvinge van de crooninge des Conincx van Bohemen, Frederici den eersten van dien name.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A-B&#8308;.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      <note>Beginning-A4 from Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery copy filmed at end.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>George Waters</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
