<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The arch's of triumph erected in honor of the high and mighty prince. Iames. the first of that name. King, of England. and the sixt of Scotland at his Maiesties entrance and passage through his honorable citty &amp; chamber of London. vpon the 15th. day of march 1603. Invented and published by Stephen Harrison ioyner and architect: and graven by William Kip.</title>
      <author>Harrison, Stephen, joiner and architect.</author>
      <author>Kip, William, engraver.</author>
      <author>Dekker, Thomas, ca. 1572-1632. Magnificent entertainment.</author>
      <author>Jonson, Ben, 1573?-1637. B. Jon: his part of King James his royall and magnificent entertainement through his honorable cittie of London, Thurseday the 15. of March. 1603. Selections.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[20] p., [7] plates   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">Iohn VVindet</persName>, printer to <persName type="patron">the honourable citie of London</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>the authors house in Lime-street, at the signe of the Snayle</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1604">1604]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>The texts are by Thomas Dekker (adapatations from his "The magnificent entertainment"), John Webster, Ben Jonson (speeches reprinted from his "B. Jon: his part of King James his royall and magnificent entertainement"), and others.</note>
      <note>Kip may not have done all the engraving.</note>
      <note>The title page is engraved; at head: Exercitationes virtutum in omni &#230;tate minificos [sic] afferunt fructus.</note>
      <note>Imprint from colophon.</note>
      <note>Signatures: [A]&#185; B-K&#185;, including title page.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Iohn VVindet</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="patron">
      <persName>the honourable citie of London</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the authors house in Lime-street, at the signe of the Snayle</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
