<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A declaration and protestation, published by the King of Nauarre, the L. Prince of Conde, and the L. Duke of Montmorency, concerning the peace concluded with the house of Lorrayn, the captaines and chiefe aucthors of the league, to the preiudice of the house of Fraunce. Also two letters written by the sayd King of Nauarre. The one to the Parliament, the other to the maisters of Sorbonne. More an epistle written by Phillipp de Morney to the French King: hereunto, for the playner declaration of the innocencie of the sayd princes, are inserted the articles agreed vpon betweene the King and the Lordes of Guyze. All faithfully translated out of French</title>
      <title>D&#233;claration et protestacion du roy de Navarre, de M. le prince de Cond&#233; et M. le duc de Montmorency sur la paix faicte avec ceux de la maison de Lorraine. English.</title>
      <author>Henry IV, King of France, 1553-1610.</author>
      <author>Mornay, Philippe de, seigneur du Plessis-Marly, 1549-1623, attributed name.</author>
      <author>Aggas, Edward, attributed name.</author>
      <author>Cond&#233;, Henri I de Bourbon, prince de, 1552-1588.</author>
      <author>Montmorency, Henri, duc de, 1534-1614.</author>
      <author>Navarre (Kingdom). Sovereign (1572-1610 : Henry III) aut</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>86, [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>[By <persName type="printer">G. Robinson]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Edward Aggas</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1585">[1585]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of: D&#233;claration et protestacion du roy de Navarre, de M. le prince de Cond&#233; et M. le duc de Montmorency sur la paix faicte avec ceux de la maison de Lorraine.</note>
      <note>Attributed to Mornay, Philippe de--STC. Translated by Edward Aggas?--STC.</note>
      <note>Printer's device (McKerrow 199) on last leaf.</note>
      <note>Formerly also STC 13110.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Edward Aggas</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>G. Robinson]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
