<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A simple, and religious consultation of vs Herman by the grace of God Archebishop of Colone, and prince Electour. [et] c. by what meanes a Christian reformation, and founded in Gods worde, of doctrine, administration of the deuine sacramentes, of ceremonies, and the hole cure of soules, and other ecclesiastical ministeries may be begon among men committed to our pastorall charge, vntil the Lorde graunt a better to be appoynted either by a free, and Christian cou[n]sayle, general, or national, or elles by the states of the empire of the natio[n] of Germanie, gathered together in the holye Gost</title>
      <title>Einfaltigs Bedencken, warauff ein christliche in dem Wort Gottes gegr&#252;nte Reformation an Lehr, Brauch der heyligen Sacramenten un Ceremonien, Seelsorg und anderem Kirchendienst, biss auff eines freyen, christlichen, gemeinen oder nationals Concilii, oder dess Reichs Teutscher Nation Stende, im Heyligen Geyst versamelt, Verbesserung, bei denen so unserer Seelsorge befohlen, anzurichten seye, English</title>
      <author>Wied, Hermann von.</author>
      <author>Melanchthon, Philipp, 1497-1560.</author>
      <author>Bucer, Martin, 1491-1551.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[616] p. : ill.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Imprinted [by <persName type="printer">John Daye]</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1547">in the yere of our Lorde. 1547. the. xxx. of October. I[ohn] D[aye]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of "Einfaltigs Bedencken, warauff ein christliche in dem Wort Gottes gegr&#252;nte Reformation an Lehr, Brauch der heyligen Sacramenten un Ceremonien, Seelsorg und anderem Kirchendienst, biss auff eines freyen, christlichen, gemeinen oder nationals Concilii, oder dess Reichs Teutscher Nation Stende, im Heyligen Geyst versamelt, Verbesserung, bei denen so unserer Seelsorge befohlen, anzurichten seye", a compilation by Martin Bucer and Philipp Melanchthon.</note>
      <note>Printer's name from colophon.</note>
      <note>Signatures: a-y 2A-2Q 2R&#8308;.</note>
      <note>A8r has a woodcut of St. John the Evangelist. Variant: woodcut is of the Last Supper.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in Cambridge University Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>John Daye]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
