<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The vertuose boke of distyllacyon of the waters of all maner of herbes with the fygures of the styllatoryes, fyrst made and compyled by the thyrte yeres study and labour of the moste co[n]nynge and famous mayster of phisyke, Master Iherom bruynswyke. And now newly translate[d] out of Duyche into Englysshe Nat only to the synguler helpe and profyte of the surgyens, phisycyens, and pothecaryes, but also of all maner of people, parfytely and in dewe tyme and ordre to lerne to dystyll all maner of herbes, to the profyte, cure, and remedy of all maner dysseases and infirmytees apparant and nat apparant. And ye shall vnderstande that the waters be better than the herbes, as Auicenna testefyeth in his fourthe conon saynge that all maner medicynes vsed with theyr substance, febleth and maketh aged, and weke. Cum gratia et preuilegio regali.</title>
      <title>Liber de arte distillandi. English</title>
      <author>Brunschwig, Hieronymus, ca. 1450-ca. 1512.</author>
      <author>Andrew, Laurence, fl. 1510-1537.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[278] p. : ill.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>In the flete strete by <persName type="printer">me Laurens Andrewe</persName>, in <placeName>the sygne of the golden Crosse</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Imprynted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date>In the yere of our lorde. M.ccccc.xxvii. the xviii daye of Apryll. [1527] [i.e. 1528?]]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Translation of a German version of: Liber de arte distillandi.</note>
      <note>Translated by Laurence Andrew, whose name appears in the heading to the prologue on [par.]2r.</note>
      <note>First three words of title are xylographic.</note>
      <note>Title page in red and black.</note>
      <note>Imprint from colophon; actual publication date conjectured by STC.</note>
      <note>Signatures: [par.]&#8308; a-b&#8310; c-d&#8308; e-f&#8310; A&#8308; B-S&#8308;&#183;&#8310; T&#8308; U-X&#8310; (X6 blank).</note>
      <note>"The prologue of this present boke of dystyllacyon.s" [sic], caption title, A1r.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>me Laurens Andrewe</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the sygne of the golden Crosse</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
