<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Hollandi posthuma A funerall elegie of King Iames: With a congratulatory salve to King Charles. An elegie of the magnanimous Henry Earle of Oxford. A description of the late great, fearefull and prodigious plague: and divers other patheticall poemes, elegies, and other lines, on divers subiectes. The post-humes of Abraham Holland, sometimes of Trinity-Colledge in Cambridge. The authors epitaph, made by himselfe.</title>
      <author>Holland, Abraham, d. 1626.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[128] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>[Printed by <persName type="printer">B. Alsop</persName> and <persName type="printer">T. Fawcet] Impensis</persName>, <persName type="printer">Henrici Holland</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Cantabrigi&#230; [i.e. London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1626">1626.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A collection, mostly in verse, by Abraham Holland. Privately printed in a limited impression at Holland's expense--National Union Catalog.</note>
      <note>The place of publication is false; actual place of publication and printer's names from STC.</note>
      <note>Includes the following (each with a 1626 separate dated title page): An elegie: or, some post-hume teares, vpon the the royall hearse of our late sovereigne Iames; An elegie vpon the death of the right noble and magnanimous Hero&#235;, Henry Earle of Oxford, Vnto these post-humes is added: Naumachia. Or, a poeticall description of the cruell and bloudie sea-fight or battaile of Lepanto. Also includes a poem on the plague (with caption title: "The description of the late great memorable and prodigious plague. 1625") that was reprinted in STC 6175.</note>
      <note>Signatures: [par.]&#178;  (a)&#8308; B-M&#8308; &#178; A&#178;  &#178; B-D&#8308;.</note>
      <note>Imperfect; the British Library copy lacks M3 (M3 and other leaves supplied at end from the University of Illinois (Urbana-Champaign Campus). Library copy and Folger Shakespeare Library copy).</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>B. Alsop</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Henrici Holland</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>T. Fawcet] Impensis</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
