<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The treasury of healthe conteynyng many profitable medycines gathered out of Hypocrates, Galen and Auycen, by one Petrus Hyspanus [and] translated into Englysh by Humfre Lloyde who hath added therunto the causes and sygnes of euery dysease, wyth the Aphorismes of Hypocrates, and Iacobus de Partybus redacted to a certayne order according to the membres of mans body, and a compendiouse table conteynyng the purginge and confortatyue medycynes, wyth the exposicyo[n] of certayne names [and] weyghtes in this boke contayned wyth an epystle of Diocles vnto kyng Antigonus.</title>
      <title>Thesaurus pauperum. English</title>
      <author>John XXI, Pope, d. 1277.</author>
      <author>Llwyd, Humphrey, 1527-1568.</author>
      <author>Diocles, of Carystus. Epistola de secunda valetudine tuenda. English.</author>
      <author>Hippocrates.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[456] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>In Fletestreate at <placeName>the sygne of the Rosegarland</placeName> by <persName type="printer">Wyllyam Coplande</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Imprynted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date>[not before 23 Aug. 1553]]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Petrus Hyspanus = Pope John XXI.</note>
      <note>A translation of: Thesaurus pauperum.</note>
      <note>The "epystle of Diocles vnto kyng Antigonus" is a translation of "Epistola de secunda valetudine tuenda" by Diocles of Carystus.</note>
      <note>Printer's name and place of publication from colophon; date of publication from STC.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A&#8308; B-Y a-g.</note>
      <note>The last leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>A reissue of STC 14651.5, with quire A reprinted omitting mention of Henry, Lord Stafford and the Duchess of Northumberland on the title page and in the preliminaries. A4r and the first part of the foreword are in the same setting of type as the first issue.</note>
      <note>Identified as STC 14652a on UMI microfilm.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Wyllyam Coplande</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the sygne of the Rosegarland</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
