<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A nevv orchard and garden, or, The best way for planting, grafting, and to make any ground good for a rich orchard particularly in the nor[th] and generally for the whole kingdome of England, as in nature, reason, situation and all probabilitie, may and doth appeare : with the country housewifes garden for hearbes of common vse, their vertues, seasons, profits, ornaments, varietie of knots, models for trees, and plots for the best ordering of grounds and walkes : as also the husbandry of bees, with their seuerall vses and annoyances, being the experience of 48 yeares labour ... / by William Lawson ; whereunto is newly added the art of propagating plants, with the tree ordering manner of fruits in their gathering, carring home &amp; preseruation.</title>
         <author>Lawson, William, fl. 1618.</author>
         <author>Harward, Simon, fl. 1572-1614. Most profitable newe treatise from approued experience of the art of propagating plants.</author>
         <author>Markham, Gervase, 1568?-1637.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <editionStmt>
         <edition>And now the second time corrected and much enlarged.</edition>
      </editionStmt>
      <extent>[8], 134 p. : ill.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by Nicholas Okes for Iohn Harison, at the Golden Vnicorne in Pater-noster-row,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1631">1631.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>"The country house-wifes garden" has special t.p.; it is sometimes erroneously attributed to Gervase Markham.</note>
         <note>Includes "A most profitable newe treatise from approued experience of the art of propagating plants, by Simon Harward."</note>
         <note>Statement of responsibility follows edition statement.</note>
         <note>T.p. contains illustration.</note>
         <note>Signatures: A&#8308; B-I&#8312; K&#8308; (last leaf blank).</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the University of Illinois (Urbana-Champaign Campus). Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
