<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A treatise tovvching the right, title, and interest of the most excellent Princess Marie, Queene of Scotland, and of the most noble king Iames, her Graces sonne, to the succession of the croune of England VVherein is conteined asvvell a genealogie of the competitors pretending title to the same croune: as a resolution of their obiections. Compiled and published before in latin, and after in Englishe, by the right reuerend father in God, Iohn Lesley, Byshop of Rosse. VVith an exhortation to the English and Scottish nations, for vniting of them selues in a true league of amitie.</title>
      <title>Defence of the honour of the right highe, mightye and noble Princesse Marie Quene of Scotlande and dowager of France. Selections</title>
      <author>Leslie, John, 1527-1596.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>12, [1], 13-71 leaves, folded plate (woodcut) : genealogical table  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">G. L'Oyselet]</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Rouen :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1584">An 1584.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A reprinting of part 2 of the enlarged edition of: A defence of the honour of the right highe, mightye and noble Princesse Marie Quene of Scotlande and dowager of France.</note>
      <note>Translated from a Latin translation of STC 15506.</note>
      <note>Place of publication and printer's name from STC.</note>
      <note>With an additional title page (C1) lacking an imprint.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: Of the title of succession to the croune of England.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>G. L'Oyselet]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
