<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The totall discourse, of the rare adventures, and painefull peregrinations of long nineteene yeares travailes from Scotland, to the most famous kingdomes in Europe, Asia, and Affrica Perfited by three deare bought voyages, in surveying of forty eight kingdomes ancient and modern; twenty one rei-publicks, ten absolute principalities, with two hundred islands. ... divided into three bookes: being newly corrected, and augmented in many severall places, with the addition of a table thereunto annexed of all the chiefe heads. Wherein is contayed an exact relation of the lawes, religions, policies and governments of all their princes, potentates and people. Together with the grievous tortures he suffered by the Inquisition of Malaga in Spaine ... And of his last and late returne from the Northern Isles, and other places adjacent. By William Lithgow.</title>
      <title>Most delectable, and true discourse, of an admired and painefull peregrination from Scotland, to the most famous kingdomes in Europe, Asia and Affricke</title>
      <author>Lithgow, William, 1582-1645?</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[16], 444, 447-514, [8] p. : ill.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">I. Okes</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1640">1640.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A revised and enlarged edition, with a new dedication and prologue, of: A most delectable, and true discourse, of an admired and painefull peregrination from Scotland, to the most famous kingdomes in Europe, Asia and Affricke.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: The 19 yeares travells of William Lithgow, by 3 voyages in Europe, Asia, and Affrica.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>I. Okes</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
