<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The second booke of the English husbandman Contayning the ordering of the kitchin-garden, and the planting of strange flowers: the breeding of all manner of cattell. Together with the cures, the feeding of cattell, the ordering both of pastures and meddow-ground: with the vse both of high-wood and vnder-wood. Whereunto is added a treatise, called Good mens recreation: contayning a discourse of the generall art of fishing, with the angle, and otherwise; and of all the hidden secrets belonging thereunto. Together vvith the choyce, ordering, breeding, and dyeting of the fighting cocke. A worke neuer written before by any author. By G.M.</title>
      <title>English husbandman. Part 2-3</title>
      <author>Markham, Gervase, 1568?-1637.</author>
      <author>Dennys, John, d. 1609. Secrets of angling.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[16], 56, 59-205 [i.e. 105], [1]; [2], 51, [3] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">T[homas] S[nodham]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Iohn Browne</persName>, and are to be sould at <placeName>his shop in S. Dunstanes Church-yard in Fleetstreet</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1614">1614.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>G.M. = Gervase Markham.</note>
      <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
      <note>"The pleasures of princes, or Good mens recreations", a prose paraphrase with additions of "The secrets of angling" by John Dennys, has separate dated title page, pagination, and register.</note>
      <note>The first leaf is blank except for signature-mark "A"; the last leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>P. 105 misnumbered 205.</note>
      <note>A variant (STC 17356a) has title pages dated 1615.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Iohn Browne</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>T[homas] S[nodham]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop in S. Dunstanes Church-yard in Fleetstreet</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
