<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Oh read ouer D. Iohn Bridges, for it is worthy worke: or an epitome of the fyrste booke, of that right worshipfull volume, written against the puritanes, in the defence of the noble cleargie, by as worshipfull a prieste, Iohn Bridges, presbyter, priest or elder, doctor of Diuillitie, and Deane of Sarum Wherein the arguments of the puritans are wisely prevented, that when they come to answere M. Doctor, they must needes say some thing that hath bene spoken. Compiled for the behoofe and overthrow of the vnpreaching parsons, fyckers, and currats, that haue lernt their catechismes, and are past grace: by the reverend and worthie Martin Marprelat gentleman, and dedicated by a second epistle to the terrible priests. In this epitome, the foresaide fickers, [et]c. are very insufficiently furnished, with notable inabilitie of most vincible reasons, to answere the cauill of the puritanes. ...</title>
      <title>Oh read over D. John Bridges. Epitome</title>
      <author>Marprelate, Martin, pseud.</author>
      <author>Throckmorton, Job, 1545-1601, attributed name.</author>
      <author>Penry, John, 1559-1593, attributed name.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[48] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed on <placeName>the other hand of some of the priests [</placeName>by <persName type="printer">Robert Waldegrave</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Fawsley, Northants.] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1588">Nov. 1588]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Martin Marprelate has been identified with John Penry and, more probably, with Job Throckmorton.</note>
      <note>A reply to: Bridges, John.  A defence of the government established in the Church of Englande for ecclesiasticall matters.</note>
      <note>The epitome only; the epistle was published earlier the same year.</note>
      <note>The imprint is false; actual imprint from STC.</note>
      <note>Signatures: [A]&#178;  B-F&#8308; G&#178; .</note>
      <note>The last leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Robert Waldegrave</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the other hand of some of the priests [</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
