<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Vnhappy prosperitie expressed in the histories of &#198;lius Seianus and Philippa the Catanian&#183; Written in French by P: Mathieu and translated into English by Sr. Th: Hawkins</title>
      <title>Aelius Sejanus, histoire romaine. English</title>
      <author>Matthieu, Pierre, 1563-1621.</author>
      <author>T. H. (Thomas Hawkins), Sir, d. 1640.</author>
      <author>Matthieu, Pierre, 1563-1621. Histoire des prosperitez malheureuses d'une femme cathenoise, grande seneschalle de Naples. English. aut</author>
      <author>Boccaccio, Giovanni, 1313-1375. De casibus virorum illustrium.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[6], 299, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Io: Hauiland</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Godfrey Emondson</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1632">1632.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of: Aelius Sejanus, histoire romaine.</note>
      <note>The title page is engraved.</note>
      <note>Translated as a satire on the fall of George Villiers, Duke of Buckingham. The translation differs from STC 17664 and 17665, but appears to be from the same French text as the former version.</note>
      <note>"Vnhappie prosperitie: or, Philippa the Catanian. VVritten in French by P. Mathieu; and translated into Engli sh [sic] by Sr. Th. Hawkins" has separate dated title page; pagination and register are continuous. It is a translation of "Histoire des prosperitez malheureuses d'une femme cathenoise, grande seneschalle de Naples", based on a story from "De casibus illustrium virorum" by Giovanni Boccaccio.</note>
      <note>Both works are supposed to have been written by Matthieu originally to represent the rise and fall of Concino Concini and his wife, L&#233;onora Galiga&#239;.</note>
      <note>Variant: with letterpress title page in place of engraved title page.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Godfrey Emondson</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Io: Hauiland</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
