<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The Mahumetane or Turkish historie containing three bookes: 1 Of the originall and beginning of the Turkes, and of the foure empires which are issued and proceded out of the superstitious sect of Mahumet. 2 Of their conquests and the succession of the house of Ottoman, vntill the present reigning of Mahumet the third. 3 Of the warres and seege of Malta, which Solyman the great made to the great maister and brothers of that order. Heerevnto haue I annexed a briefe discourse of the warres of Cypres, at what time Selimus the second, tooke from the Venetians the possession of that iland, and by reason thereof I haue adioyned a finall discourse conteining the causes of the greatnesse of the Turkish Empire. Translated from the French &amp; Italian tongues, by R. Carr, of the middle Temple in London, Gentleman. Dedicated to the three worthy brothers Robert Carr, William Carr and Edward Carr, in the county of Lincolne, Esquires.</title>
      <author>Carr, Ralph, of the Middle Temple.</author>
      <author>Foglietta, Uberto, 1518-1581. De causis magnitudinis imperii Turcici. English.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[6], 122 leaves   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Thomas Este</persName>, dwelling in <placeName>Aldersgate streete</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1600">1600.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Original title not traced.</note>
      <note>The final discourse is a translation of: Foglietta, Umberto.  De causis magnitudinis imperii Turcici.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Thomas Este</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Aldersgate streete</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
