<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Ioyfull newes out of the newfound world wherein are declared the rare and singular vertues of diuers and sundrie herbs, trees, oyles, plants, [and] stones, with their applications, aswell to the vse of phisicke, as chirurgery: which being wel applied, bring such present remedy for all diseases, as may seeme altogether incredible: notwithstanding by practize found out, to be true. Also the portrature of the sayde herbes, very aptly described: Englished by Iohn Frampton merchant. Newly corrected as by conference with the olde copies may appeare. Wherevnto are added three other bookes treating of the Bezaar stone, the herbe escuer&#231;onera, the properties of yron and steele, in medicine and the benefite of snowe.</title>
      <title>Historia medicinal de las cosas que se traen de nuestras Indias Occidentales que sirven en medicina. English</title>
      <author>Monardes, Nicol&#225;s, ca. 1512-1588.</author>
      <author>Frampton, John, fl. 1577-1596.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 181, [1] leaves : ill. (woodcuts)  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>In Paules Churchyard at <placeName>the signe of the Quenes Armes</placeName>, by <persName type="printer">[Thomas Dawson</persName> for<persName type="publisher">] William Norton</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1580">1580.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>By Nicol&#225;s Monardes, whose name appears on *3r.</note>
      <note>A translation of: La historia medicinal de las cosas que se traen de nuestras Indias Occidentales que sirven en medicina.</note>
      <note>Colophon reads: Imprinted at London at the three Cranes in the Vintree by Thomas Dawson, for William Norton ..</note>
      <note>The first leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>In this uncorrected state page 2S3v has catchword: the.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>] William Norton</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>[Thomas Dawson</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the signe of the Quenes Armes</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
