<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The abridgement or summarie of the Scots chronicles with a short description of their originall, from the comming of Gathelus their first progenitor out of Gr&#230;cia into Egypt. And their comming into Portingall and Spaine, and of their kings and gouernours in Spaine, Ireland and Albion, now called Scotland, (howbeit the whole number are not extant) with a true chronologie of all their kings. Their reignes, deaths and burials, from Fergusius the first king of Scotland, vntill his Royall Maiestie, now happily raigning ouer all Great Brittaine and Ireland, and all the isles to them appertaining. With a true description and diuision of the whole realme of Scotland, and of the principall cities, townes, abbies, fortes, castles, towers and riuers, and of the commodities in euery part thereof, and of the isles in generall, with a memoriall of the most rare and wonderfull things in Scotland. By Iohn Monipennie.</title>
      <author>Monipennie, John.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 100, [20] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed at <placeName>Brittaines Bursse</placeName> by <persName type="printer">Iohn Budge</persName> [and <persName type="printer">Simon Stafford]</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1612">1612.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"A short description of the vvesterne iles of Scotland .." (caption title) has separate register, and colophon reading: Printed at London by Simon Stafford.</note>
      <note>Some copies have the imprint date altered by hand to 1614. Copy at reel 996:12 has altered date.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of originals in: Harvard University Library (reel 996:12) and Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery (reel 1999:11).</note>
      <note>Imperfect: reproduction on reel 1999:11 lacks all after p. 100.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Iohn Budge</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Simon Stafford]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Brittaines Bursse</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
