<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The encounter against M. Parsons, by a revievv of his last sober reckoning, and his exceptions vrged in the treatise of his mitigation. Wherein moreouer is inserted: 1. A confession of some Romanists, both concerning the particular falsifications of principall Romanists, as namely, Bellarmine, Suarez, and others: as also concerning the generall fraude of that curch, in corrupting of authors. 2. A confutation of slaunders, which Bellarmine vrged against Protestants. 3. A performance of the challenge, which Mr. Parsons made, for the examining of sixtie Fathers, cited by Coccius for proofe of Purgatorie ... 4. A censure of a late pamphlet, intituled, The patterne of a Protestant, by one once termed the moderate answerer. 5. An handling of his question of mentall equiuocation (after his boldnesse with the L. Cooke) vpon occasion of the most memorable, and feyned Yorkeshire case of equiuocating; and of his raging against D. Kings sermon. Published by authoritie</title>
      <author>Morton, Thomas, 1564-1659.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[16], 272; 176, [4] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed [by <persName type="printer">W. Stansby</persName> at <placeName>Eliot's Court Press]</placeName> for <persName type="publisher">Iohn Bill</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1610.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Dedication signed: Th. Morton.</note>
      <note>A reply to: Parsons, Robert.  A quiet and sober reckoning with M. Thomas Morton.</note>
      <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: An encounter against Mr. Parsons his reckoning.</note>
      <note>With a final errata leaf; the last leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>Variant: title page undated.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Iohn Bill</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>W. Stansby</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Eliot's Court Press]</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
