<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The Popes funerall Containing a plaine, succinct, and pithy reply, to a pretensed answere of a shamelesse and foolish libell, intituled, The forerunner of Bels downfall. VVhich is nothing else indeede, (as the indifferent reader shall preceiue by the due peruse thereof,) but an euident manifestation of his owne folly; with the vtter confusion of poperie, and all popish vassals throughout the Christian world.</title>
         <author>Bell, Thomas, fl. 1593-1610.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[132] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by T[homas] C[reede] [, S. Stafford, and T. Purfoot] for William Welby, and are to be sold at his shop in Paules Church-yard, at the signe of the Grayhound,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1605">1605.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Dedication signed: Tho. Bels, i.e. Thomas Bell.</note>
         <note>A reply to: Woodward, Philip.  The fore-runner of Bels downefall.</note>
         <note>Signatures: A&#8308; *2 B-F&#8308;; A-I&#8308;; 2A&#8308;.</note>
         <note>The first leaf is blank.</note>
         <note>In two books, the second with separate register.</note>
         <note>The last four leaves contain "A caueat, or Christian admonition to the reader", a reply to the second edition of Woodward's "The fore-runner of Bels downefall".</note>
         <note>In book 2, Stafford printed quires A-F, Purfoot G-I (STC).</note>
         <note>"A fresh larum or new challenge", leaves I2-4, was given separate entry 1821 in STC (1st ed).</note>
         <note>Book 2 identified as STC 1821 on UMI microfilm reel 1195.</note>
         <note>Reproductions of the originals in Cambridge University Library and Emmanuel College (University of Cambridge).</note>
         <note>Appears at reel 828 (Cambridge University Library copy) and at reel 1195 (Emmanuel College (University of Cambridge copy).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
