<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Ciuill considerations vpon many and sundrie histories, as well ancient as moderne, and principallie vpon those of Guicciardin Containing sundry rules and precepts for princes, common-wealths, captaines, coronels, ambassadours and others, agents and seruants of princes, with sundry aduertisements and counsels concerning a ciuill life, gathered out of the examples of the greatest princes and common-wealths in Christendome. Handled after the manner of a discourse, by the Lord Remy of Florence, and done into French by Gabriel Chappuys, Tourangeau, and out of French into English, by W.T.</title>
      <title>Considerationi civili sopra l'historie di Francesco Guicciardini e d'altri historici. English</title>
      <author>Nannini, Remigio, 1521?-1581?</author>
      <author>Traheron, W., attributed name.</author>
      <author>W. T., fl. 1601.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[20], 252, [12] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Imprinted by <persName type="printer">F[elix] K[ingston]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Matthew Lownes</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop vnder S. Dunstons Church in the west</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1601">1601.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>W.T. = W. Traheron?.</note>
      <note>A translation of: Considerationi civili sopra l'historie di Francesco Guicciardini e d'altri historici.</note>
      <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
      <note>The first leaf and the last leaf are blank.</note>
      <note>Includes index.</note>
      <note>C1.2 are a cancel bifolium, with chapter heading, C1r, "The aduise and counsell ..". Variant: with cancellanda C1,2; chapter heading, C1r, "To bring a secret enterprise ..".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      <note>Lacking Y2,5; p. 230-52 from the British Library copy spliced at end.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Matthew Lownes</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>F[elix] K[ingston]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop vnder S. Dunstons Church in the west</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
