<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The mecographie of ye loadstone Tat is to say ane description of the lenthes or longitudes, quhikis ar son be ye obseruations of ye loadstone: this moyen is verse certain &amp; and neuhe fond ond and schauis phou meikil ye nidil or guideymant goir a fide or fleis from yelyn meridional, in qual part of ye land, or of ye sie yt he at in and also quihikis, ye lenthe geographique from degre to degre be tables. It is ane vork necessaire for ye admirals, cosmographer, astrologues, geographes, hydrographes, skippers, geometriens, or archivctes, and to tais that makis ye horologes for ye sone and other instruments of ye mathematiques ye dou passe be ye lodeflune. Invented and maid ve Vnilham Nautonier Lord off Casteliranck in Langedoc. [...]</title>
         <title>Mecometrie de leymant. Part 2. English</title>
         <author>Nautonier, Guillaume de, sieur de Castelfranc, fl. 1603.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 6, [2], 3-16 p., 195 leaves   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>par Raimond Colomies, imprimeur en l'Vniuersiti&#233; de Tolose, &amp; par Antoine de Courteneusue, aux frais de l'autheur.,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>Imprim&#233; &#224; Tolose, &amp; &#224; Venez :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1603">M.DC.III. [1603]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Title repeated in French and Latin; text in Scottish, French and Latin.</note>
         <note>Title within architectural frame.</note>
         <note>Pages 1-6, 9 and 15 misnumbered 11-16, 11 and 12.</note>
         <note>Part 2 of the French edition of 1609, Mecometrie de leymant.</note>
         <note>Identified as STC 18415a on UMI microfilm.</note>
         <note>Some print show-through.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
