<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A new handling of the planisphere diuided into three sections. In the first is a plaine and sensible explication of the circles of the sphere, and such termes as appertaine vnto the doctrine de primo mobili ... The second sheweth how vpon any plaine ... hauing one circle diuided into degrees, and crossed vvith tvvo diameters at right angles, most conclusions of the astrolabe may for all latitudes or countries be readily and exactly performed onely vvith ruler and compasses. In the third, being a supplement organicall, is contained the making of certaine easie instruments for the perfecter working the former conclusions, as to know what degrees and minutes be in any circumference giuen ... Pleasant and profitable generally for all men, but especially such as vvould get handines in vsing the ruler and compasse ... vvithout being at the charge of costly instruments. Inuented for the most part, and first published in English by Thomas Olyuer.</title>
      <author>Oliver, Thomas, d. 1624.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>79, 82-99, [3] p. : ill. (woodcuts)  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Imprinted by <persName type="printer">Felix Kyngston</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">Simon Waterson</persName> and <persName type="publisher">Rafe Iacson</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1601">1601.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>The last leaf contains an illustration intended to cancel that on p. 35.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Rafe Iacson</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Simon Waterson</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Felix Kyngston</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
