<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A true historie of the memorable siege of Ostend and what passed on either side, from the beginning of the siege, vnto the yeelding vp of the towne. Conteining the assaults, alarums, defences, inuentions of warre, mines, counter-mines and retrenchments, combats of galleys, and sea-fights, with the portrait of the towne: and also what passed in the Ile of Cadsant, and at the siege of Sluice, after the comming of Count Maurice. Translated out of French into English, by Edward Grimeston.</title>
      <title>Histoire remarquable et veritable de ce qui c'est pass&#233; par chacun jour au siege de la ville d'Ostende. English.</title>
      <author>Grimeston, Edward.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8], 152, 145-224, [8] p., [2] folded plates : maps  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed [by <persName type="printer">George Eld]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Edward Blount</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1604">1604.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of: Histoire remarquable et veritable de ce qui c'est pass&#233; par chacun jour au siege de la ville d'Ostende.</note>
      <note>Printer's name from STC addendum.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: The historie of the siege of Ostend.</note>
      <note>2G1-2 contain "Articles agreed upon by the Lord Marquis Ambrosio Spignola"; 2G3 contains "An explanation of the figure of the retrenchments of Ostend"; 2G4 is blank. Variant: in place of this quire is one leaf signed "Gg"; recto contains "An explanation of the figure of the retrenchments of Ostend".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Edward Blount</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>George Eld]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
