<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The secrets of physick and philosophy divided into two bookes: in the first is shewed the true and perfect order to distill, or draw forth the oyles of all manner of gummes, spices, seedes, roots, and hearbs, with their perfect taste, smell and vertues. In the second is shewed the true and perfect order to prepare, calcine, sublime, and dissolue all manner of minerals, and how ye shall draw forth their oyles and salts, which are most wonderfull in their operations, for the health of mans bodie. First written in the German tongue by the most learned Theophrastus Paraselsus, and now published in the English tongue, by Iohn Hester, practitioner in the art of distillation.</title>
         <title>True and perfect order to distill oyles out of al maner of spices.</title>
         <author>Paracelsus, 1493-1541, attributed name.</author>
         <author>Hermanni, Philippus. Constich distillierboeck.</author>
         <author>Hester, John, d. 1593.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[24], 196, [16] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by A[ugustine] M[athewes] for William Lugger, and are to bee sold at the Posterne Gate at Tower Hill,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1633">1633.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Not in fact by Paracelsus.</note>
         <note>An enlarged edition of: The true and perfect order to distill oyles out of al maner of spices.</note>
         <note>"Secrets of phisicke and philosophie. The second booke ..", an adaptation of "Een constich distillierboeck" by Philippus Hermanni, has separate dated title page; register and pagination are continuous.</note>
         <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
         <note>The first leaf is blank.</note>
         <note>With a final colophon leaf.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
