<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Theatrum botanicum: = The theater of plants. Or, An herball of a large extent containing therein a more ample and exact history and declaration of the physicall herbs and plants that are in other authours, encreased by the accesse of many hundreds of new, rare, and strange plants from all the parts of the world, with sundry gummes, and other physicall materials, than hath beene hitherto published by any before; and a most large demonstration of their natures and vertues. Shevving vvithall the many errors, differences, and oversights of sundry authors that have formerly written of them; and a certaine confidence, or most probable conjecture of the true and genuine herbes and plants. Distributed into sundry classes or tribes, for the more easie knowledge of the many herbes of one nature and property, with the chiefe notes of Dr. Lobel, Dr. Bonham, and others inserted therein. Collected by the many yeares travaile, industry, and experience in this subject, by Iohn Parkinson apothecary of London, and the Kings herbarist. And published by the Kings Majestyes especial</title>
         <author>Parkinson, John, 1567-1650.</author>
         <author>Marshall, William, fl. 1617-1650, engraver.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[22], 1755, [3] p. : ill. (woodcuts)  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by Tho. Cotes,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1640.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>With an additional title page, engraved, "Theatrum botanicum, the theater of plantes. ..", signed: W· Marshall sculpsit.</note>
         <note>The first leaf is blank.</note>
         <note>Includes indexes.</note>
         <note>With a final errata leaf.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
