<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A true reporte, of the late discoueries, and possession, taken in the right of the Crowne of Englande, of the new-found landes: by that valiaunt and worthye gentleman, Sir Humfrey Gilbert Knight Wherein is also breefely sette downe, her highnesse lawfull tytle therevnto, and the great and manifolde commodities, that is likely to grow thereby, to the whole realme in generall, and to the aduenturers in particular. Together with the easines and shortnes of the voyage. Seene and allowed.</title>
         <author>[Peckham, George], Sir.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[74] leaves   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by I[ohn] C[harlewood] for Iohn Hinde, dwelling in Paules Church-yarde, at the signe of the golden Hinde,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
         <date>Anno. 1583.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Dedication signed: G.P., i.e. Sir George Peckham.</note>
         <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
         <note>The book exists in three states of the preliminaries and final leaves; contents are given here in presumed chronological order from F.S. Ferguson's notes. State 1: collates *⁴ B-G⁴ H²  (-H1 or 2), with commendatory verses on *4 only. State 2: collates *⁴ [sec.]²  B-G⁴ H²  (-H1 or 2); quire [sec.] contains additional verses. State 3 (pagination given above): collates *⁴ [sec.]⁴ B-G⁴ H²  (-H1 or 2) I²  [K]² . Quire [sec.] contains additional verses, some printed from the standing type of state 2 quire [sec.]. Leaves I1-[K]1 contain "The contentes of the articles of assurance"; [K]2, a table of contents, is often usually bound in or after quire *.</note>
         <note>In all states *2 is missigned "*.i.". The two leaves of H²  were printed with the same text set in duplicate, intended to be divided and one leaf or the other to be bound into each copy. One setting is signed "H.", the other "H.i.".</note>
         <note>Quire I comes in two states: I1r line 1 of text has (1) "aduentured with" or (2) "aduentured in money".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
