<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The Spanish pilgrime: or, An admirable discouery of a Romish Catholicke Shewing how necessary and important it is, for the Protestant kings, princes, and potentates of Europe, to make warre vpon the King of Spaines owne countrey: also where, and by what meanes, his dominions may be inuaded and easily ruinated; as the English heretofore going into Spaine, did constraine the kings of Castile to demand peace in all humility, and what great losse it hath beene, and still is to all Christendome, for default of putting the same in execution. Wherein hee makes apparant by good and euident reasons, infallible arguments, most true and certaine histories, and notable examples, the right way, and true meanes to resist the violence of the Spanish King, to breake the course of his designes, to beate downe his pride, and to ruinate his puissance.</title>
      <title>Traicte paraenetique. English.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[16], 128, 131-136, [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">B[ernard] A[lsop]</persName> and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Thomas Archer</persName> at <placeName>his shop in Popes head Alley, ouer against the signe of the Horse-shooe</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1625">1625.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of "Traicte paraenetique", a French translation of an unpublished Spanish original erroneously attributed to Antonio P&#233;rez and to Jos&#233; Teixeira.</note>
      <note>French translator's note signed "I.D. Dralymont", i e. Jean de Montlyard.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: The Spanish pilgrime, or A Romish Catholickes discouerie.</note>
      <note>The last leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>Identified as STC 23863 on UMI microfilm.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      <note>Lacks dedication.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>B[ernard] A[lsop]</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Thomas Archer</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop in Popes head Alley, ouer against the signe of the Horse-shooe</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
