<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Ane oration made by Master Theodore de Beze, minister of the word of God, accompanyed with. xi. other ministers and. xx. deputies of the refourmed churches of the realme of Fraunce, in the presence of the king, ... Tuesday the ix. day of September, 1561, in the noonnery of Poyssy. Truely gathered and set forth in suct sort as it was spoken by the said de Beze. Whereunto is added a brief declaration exhibited by the said Beze, to the Quene the mother, the next morowe after the making of the said oration, touching certain poyntes conteyned in the same</title>
         <title>Harangue faicte par M. Théodore de Bèze. English.</title>
         <author>Bèze, Théodore de, 1519-1605.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[80] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>By Robet [sic] Lekprewik. Cum priuilegio,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[Imprinted at Edinburgh :</pubPlace>
         <date>1561]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A translation of: Bèze, Théodore de.  La harangue faicte par M. Théodore de Bèze, .. accompagné d'autres unze ministres, et de vingt députez des églises réformées du royaume de France, devant le roy, .. The brief declaration is a translation of: Sommaire déclaration de Théodore de Besze, sur certains poinctz par luy proposez en l'assemblée .. à Poissy, le 9 de septembre mil cinq cens soixante et un.</note>
         <note>D7v is a separate title page, reading: A briefe writing, exhibited by Master Theodore de Beze, to the Quene Mother at Poissy, the x. day of September .."; register is continuous.</note>
         <note>Signatures: a-e.</note>
         <note>Imprint from colophon.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the University of Edinburgh. Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
