<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The schoole of honest and vertuous lyfe profitable and necessary for all estates and degrees, to be trayned in: but (cheefely) for the pettie schollers, the yonger sorte, of both kindes; bee they men or women. by T.P. Also, a laudable and learned discourse, of the worthynesse of honorable wedlocke, written in the behalfe of all (aswell) maydes as wydowes, (generally) for their singuler instruction, to choose them vertuous and honest husbandes: but (most specialy) sent writte[n] as a iewell vnto a worthy gentlewoman, in the time of her widowhood, to direct &amp; guide her in the new election of her seconde husband. By her approoued freend and kinseman. I.R.</title>
         <author>Pritchard, Thomas, fl. 1579.</author>
         <author>Wied, Hermann von. Brefe and a playne declaratyon of the dewty of maried folkes.</author>
         <author>Kingsmill, Andrew, 1538-1569. Viewe of mans estate. Selections.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>88 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>By [William How for] Richard Iohnes, and are to be solde at his shop ouer against S. Sepulchers Church without Newgate,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1579">[1579]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Dedication signed: Tho. Pritchard.</note>
         <note>Actual printer's name and publication date from STC.</note>
         <note>The discourse of wedlock is erroneously attributed to John Rogers. It is actually a revised excerpt of "A viewe of mans estate" by Andrew Kingsmill (STC 15003). "The glasse of godly loue", a reprint of Hermann von Wied's "A brefe and a playne declaratyon of the dewty of maried folkes" (STC 13208), has separate divisional title.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
