<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The treasure of trueth touching the grounde worke of man his saluation, and chiefest pointes of Christian religion: with a briefe summe of the comfortable doctrine of God his prouidence, comprised in .38. short aphorismes. VVritten in Latin by Theodore Beza, and nevvly turned into English by Iohn Stockvvood. VVhereunto are added, these godly treatises. One of the learned and godlie Father. Maister I. Foxe. In the which the chiefest poyntes of the doctrine of God his election, are so plainely set foorth, as the verie simplest may easily vnderstand it, and reape great profite thereby. The other of Maister Anthonie Gylbie, wherein the doctrine of God his election and reprobation, is both godly and learnedlie handeled. Seene and alovved, according to the order appoynted.</title>
      <title>Summa totius Christianismi. English</title>
      <author>B&#232;ze, Th&#233;odore de, 1519-1605.</author>
      <author>Stockwood, John, d. 1610.</author>
      <author>Foxe, John, 1516-1587.</author>
      <author>Gilby, Anthony, ca. 1510-1585. Briefe treatyse of election and reprobacion.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[280] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>[By <persName type="printer">J. Charlewood]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Woodcocke</persName>, dwelling in <placeName>Paules Church yarde, at the sygne of the blacke beare</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1576">[1576]]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of: Summa totius Christianismi.</note>
      <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A&#8308; B-S.</note>
      <note>Includes a reprint of: Gilby, Anthony.  A briefe treatyse of election and reprobacion.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in Cambridge University Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Woodcocke</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>J. Charlewood]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Paules Church yarde, at the sygne of the blacke beare</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
