<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Purchas his pilgrimage. Or Relations of the vvorld and the religions obserued in all ages and places discouered, from the Creation vnto this present Contayning a theologicall and geographicall historie of Asia, Africa, and America, with the ilands adiacent. Declaring the ancient religions before the Floud ... The fourth edition, much enlarged with additions, and illustrated with mappes through the whole worke; and three whole treatises annexed, one of Russia and other northeasterne regions by Sr. Ierome Horsey; the second of the Gulfe of Bengala by Master William Methold; the third of the Saracenicall empire, translated out of Arabike by T. Erpenius. By Samuel Purchas, parson of St. Martins by Ludgate, London.</title>
         <author>Purchas, Samuel, 1577?-1626.</author>
         <author>Makīn, Jirjis ibn al-ʻAmīd, 1205-1273. Taŕikh al-Muslimin. English.</author>
         <author>Methold, William, 1590-1653.</author>
         <author>Horsey, Jerome, Sir, d. 1626.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[42], 242, 241-636, 635-1047, [37] p., folded plate : maps (metal cuts)  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by William Stansby for Henrie Fetherstone, and are to be sold at his shop in Pauls Church-yard at the signe of the Rose,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1626.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>The first leaf is blank.</note>
         <note>"Tvvo relations, one of the northeasterne parts, extracted out of Sir Ierome Horsey Knight .. The other, of the southeasterne parts .. written by Mr. William Methold" and "The Saracenical historie" each have separate dated title pages; pagination and register are continuous.</note>
         <note>"The Saracenical historie" is a translation by Purchas from Erpenius's translation of: Makin, Jirjis ibn al-ʻAmid. Taŕikh al-Muslimin.</note>
         <note>Includes index.</note>
         <note>Another state of STC 20508 with the first quire reset; title begins "Purchas"; includes an added dedication to King Charles.</note>
         <note>Often found as v. 5 of "Purchas his pilgrimes"; they are, however, entirely different works.</note>
         <note>Identified as STC 20508 on UMI microfilm.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
