<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Two fruitfull exercises the one: A Christian discourse vpon the 16. and 17. verses of the 16. chapter of the booke of Iudges, wherin are handled these three principal heads: The portreature of Dalila. The bridle of lust. The seale of secrets. The other: A godly meditation vpon the 41. and 42. verses of the 10. chapter of Saint Luke, containing especially The profit of repreoofe, togither with the necessitie and excellencie of Gods word. Also a brief discourse intituled A buckler against a Spanish brag: Written vpon the first rumor of the intended inuasion, and now not altogither ynmeete to be published. By E.R.</title>
      <author>E. R., fl. 1588.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[10], 176 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>[Eliot's Court Press] Impensis <persName type="publisher">G. Bishop</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Londini :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1588">1588.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Press from STC.</note>
      <note>Recto of final page contains list of errata.</note>
      <note>Sig. F8r is a separate title page, reading: A Godlie meditation vpon the 41.42 verses of the 10.chapter of S. Lukes Gospell, containing especially the profit of reproofe, togither with the necessitie and excellencie of the word of God. Londini, Impensis G. Bishop. 1588.</note>
      <note>Sig. K5r is a separate title page, reading: A briefe discourse intituled A Buckler against a Spanish brag: Written vpon the first rumor of the intended inuasion, and now not altogither vnmeet to be published. 1588.</note>
      <note>Some pages closely cropped.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>G. Bishop</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
