<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A briefe relation, of what is hapned since the last of August 1598. by comming of the Spanish campe into the dukedom of Cleue: and the bordering free countries, which with most odious and barbarous crueltie they take as enemies, for the seruice of God, and the King of Spaine (as they say). Heerunto is adioyned a translation out of Latin, of a letter of the Emperours embassadour, to the admirant of Arragon, the generall of the said army: with his answere. Together with a description of the vvhale of Berckhey, or the great fish which stranded or came on shoare at Berckhey in Holland, the third of February 1598. ... Also a letter of the Emperour of Germany, to the admirant of Arragon ... With the admirants answere. ... Faithfully translated out of the Dutch coppy printed at Roterdam.</title>
      <title>Walvisch van Berkhey. English.</title>
      <author>Rudolf II, Holy Roman Emperor, 1552-1612.</author>
      <author>Mendoza, Francisco de, 1549-1623.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 28; [2], 13, [1] p., folded plate : map  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">[Edward Allde</persName> for<persName type="publisher">] Iohn VVolfe</persName>, and are to be solde at <placeName>his shop in Popes head Alley, neere vnto the Exchange</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1599">1599.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of: Walvisch van Berkhey.</note>
      <note>Actual printer's name from STC.</note>
      <note>"The letter of the Emperour of Germanie, to the admirant of Arragon" has separate dated title page, pagination, and register.</note>
      <note>The map has letterpress title: The scituation of the lands of Cleue and Munster, where the Spanish forces now are.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>] Iohn VVolfe</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>[Edward Allde</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop in Popes head Alley, neere vnto the Exchange</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
