<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Two treatises of the Lord his holie Supper the one instructing the seruants of God how they should be prepared when they come to the holy Supper of our onely Sauiour Iesus Christ: whereunto is annexed a dialogue conteining the principall points necessarie to be knowne and vnderstood of all them that are to be partakers of the holy Supper: the other setting forth dialoguewise the whole vse of the Supper: whereunto also is adioyned a briefe and learned treatise of the true Sacrifice and true priest. Written in the French tongue by Yues Rouspeau and Iohn de l'Espine ministers of the word of God, and latelie translated into English.</title>
         <author>Rouspeau, Yves.</author>
         <author>L'Espine, Jean de, ca. 1506-1597. Dialogue de la C&#232;ne de N.S. Jesus-Christ. aut</author>
         <author>Rouspeau, Yves. Traitt&#233; de la pr&#233;paration &#224; la saincte cene.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>58 [i.e. 56], 70 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Imprinted by Thomas Thomas printer to the Vniuersitie of Cambridge,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[Cambridge] :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1584">1584.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>In two parts. The first treatise is a translation of: Rouspeau, Yves. Traitt&#233; de la pr&#233;paration &#224; la saincte cene de nostre seul sauveur .. Plus un dialogue contant les poincts principaux que ceux qui veulent recevoir la cene doivent savoir et entendre. The second is a translation of: L'Espine, Jean de. Dialogue de la C&#232;ne de N.S. Jesus-Christ. Plus un traitt&#233; du vray sacrifice..</note>
         <note>Numerous errors in pagination of first sequence; correct pagination deduced from signature collation.</note>
         <note>Signatures: A-C D&#8308; [2d]B-E F&#8308;.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Folger Shakespeare Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
