<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A prophecie vttered by the daughter of an honest countrey man, called Adam Krause Who on the eighteene of Ianuary, betweene three and foure of the clock in the afternoone gaue vp the ghost, and beeing esteemed for dead, was laide out to be buryed. The next day betweene one and two of the clock, when men came to haue buryed her: she came againe to her selfe, and receiued bothe life and strengthe, as in former state before: hauing so lyen in the forme of a dead corps for the space of two and twenty howres: and being so come to her perfect speeche, shee prophesied of many plagues to ensue, with worthy admonitions that after happened according to her speeche. This happened at a towne called Rostorff a mile from Melwing: written for a worthy remembrance of Gods omnipotency, by the worshipfull, Maister Eyriak Schlictenberger, superintendent at Melwing. 1580.</title>
      <title>Prophecey eines Bawren Tochter, welche den 18. Jenner. English</title>
      <author>Schlichtenberger, Eyriak.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[14] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">Iohn Charlewood</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">William Wright</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[First printed in Dansk, next at Lubick, then at Hambrough: and nowe at London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1580]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>By Eyriak Schlichtenberger.</note>
      <note>Imprint from colophon.</note>
      <note>A translation from the German: Prophecey eines Bawren Tochter, welche den 18. Jenner.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: The prophesie of a poore countrey mans daughter.</note>
      <note>At end: "Translated according to the highe Dutch".</note>
      <note>Signatures: A (-A8).</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Folger Shakespeare Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>William Wright</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Iohn Charlewood</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
