<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The perfect vse of silk-vvormes, and their benefit With the exact planting, and artificiall handling of mulberrie trees whereby to nourish them, and the figures to know how to feede the wormes, and to winde off the silke. And the fit maner to prepare the barke of the white mulberrie to make fine linnen and other workes thereof. Done out of the French originall of D'Oliuier de Serres Lord of Pradel into English, by Nicholas Geffe Esquier. With an annexed discourse of his owne, of the meanes and sufficiencie of England for to haue abundance of fine silke by feeding of silke-wormes within the same; as by apparent proofes by him made and continued appeareth. For the generall vse and vniuersall benefit of all those his countrey men which embrace them. Neuer the like yet here discouered by any.</title>
         <title>Theatre d'agriculture et mesnage des champs. Part 5. Chapter 15. English</title>
         <author>Serres, Olivier de, 1539-1619.</author>
         <author>Geffe, Nicholas.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8], 81 [i.e. 97], [5], 14, [4] p. : ill. (woodcuts)  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Imprinted by Felix Kyngston, and are to be sold by Richard Sergier and Christopher Purset, with the assignment of William Stallenge,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1607.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A translation of part 5, chapter 15 of: Le theatre d'agriculture et mesnage des champs.</note>
         <note>At foot of title: Cum privilegio.</note>
         <note>P. 97 misnumbered 81.</note>
         <note>With a final leaf bearing "To the reader" on recto and errata on verso; the last leaf is blank.</note>
         <note>"A discourse of his ovvne" by Nicholas Geffe has separate divisional title and pagination; register is continuous.</note>
         <note>Verso of title page blank. Variant: with royal arms on verso.</note>
         <note>An imprint variant of STC 22249.3.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
         <note>Only title page of "A discourse of his owne" filmed.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
