<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The true travels, adventures, and observations of Captaine Iohn Smith, in Europe, Asia, Affrica, and America, from anno Domini 1593. to 1629 His accidents and sea-fights in the straights; his service and stratagems of warre in Hungaria, Transilvania, Wallachia, and Moldavia, against the Turks, and Tartars ... After how he was taken prisoner by the Turks, sold for a slave ... and escaped ... Together with a continuation of his generall History of Virginia, Summer-Iles, New England, and their proceedings, since 1624. to this present 1629; as also of the new plantations of the great river of the Amazons, the iles of St. Christopher, Mevis, and Barbados in the West Indies. All written by actuall authours, whose names you shall finde along the history.</title>
      <author>Smith, John, 1580-1631.</author>
      <author>Cecil, Thomas, fl. 1630, engraver.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[12], 60 p., [1] folded plate : b ill., coats of arms. ill. (metal cut), coat of arms.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">I[ohn] H[aviland]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Slater</persName>, and are to bee sold [by <persName type="bookseller">Michael Sparke]</persName> at <placeName>the Blew Bible in Greene Arbour</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1630">1630.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Printer's and publisher's names from STC.</note>
      <note>With a coat of arms on title page verso signed "T Cecill scul". A variant has this illustration printed on a separate leaf.</note>
      <note>The plate has imprint: London printed by James Reeue.</note>
      <note>Head- and taipieces, initials.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A6, B-G4, H6.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in: Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery (reel 939:15) and Folger Shakespeare Library (reel 2343:2b).</note>
      <note>Bound and filmed with, at reel 2343:2b: STC (2nd ed.) 22790c.5, Smith, J. The generall historie of Virginia [etc.]. London, 1631.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Slater</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>I[ohn] H[aviland]</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Michael Sparke]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Blew Bible in Greene Arbour</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
