<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A map of Virginia VVith a description of the countrey, the commodities, people, government and religion. VVritten by Captaine Smith, sometimes governour of the countrey. Whereunto is annexed the proceedings of those colonies, since their first departure from England, with the discourses, orations, and relations of the salvages, and the accidents that befell them in all their iournies and discoveries. Taken faithfully as they were written out of the writings of Doctor Russell. Tho. Studley. Anas Todkill. Ieffra Abot. Richard Wiefin. Will. Phettiplace. Nathaniel Povvell. Richard Pots. And the relations of divers other diligent observers there present then, and now many of them in England. By VV.S.</title>
         <author>Smith, John, 1580-1631.</author>
         <author>Symonds, William, 1556-1616?</author>
         <author>Abbay, Thomas.</author>
         <author>Hole, William, d. 1624, engraver.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8], 39, [1]; [4], 110, [2] p., folded plate : map  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by Joseph Barnes,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>At Oxford :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1612">1612.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>W.S. = William Symonds.</note>
         <note>Edited by Thomas Abbay, who initials the introduction to part 1 and signs that to part 2.</note>
         <note>The map has title "Virginia" and is signed "grauen by William Hole 1606". For the various states see Sabin 82832 and 82823.</note>
         <note>"The proceedings of the English colonie in Virginia" has separate dated title page, pagination, and register.</note>
         <note>The last leaf is blank.</note>
         <note>Variant: with an additional leaf of dedication to (1) the Earl of Hereford by Smith, or (2) to T. Watson and J. Bingley by "Philip Fote" (possibly a pun on the heading "To the hand" on *2r in all copies).</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in Harvard University. Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
