<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Virginia richly valued, by the description of the maine land of Florida, her next neighbour out of the foure yeeres continuall trauell and discouerie, for aboue one thousand miles east and west, of Don Ferdinando de Soto, and sixe hundred able men in his companie. Wherin are truly obserued the riches and fertilitie of those parts, abounding with things necessarie, pleasant, and profitable for the life of man: with the natures and dispositions of the inhabitants. Written by a Portugall gentleman of Eluas, emploied in all the action, and translated out of Portugese by Richard Hakluyt.</title>
      <title>Rela&#231;am verdadeira dos trabalhos que ho governador dom Fernando de Souto e certos fidalgos portugueses passarom no descobrimento da Frolida. English.</title>
      <author>Hakluyt, Richard, 1552?-1616.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8], 180 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Felix Kyngston</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Matthew Lownes</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>the signe of the Bishops head in Pauls Churchyard</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1609">1609.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of the anonymous: Rela&#231;am verdadeira dos trabalhos que ho governador dom Fernando de Souto e certos fidalgos portugueses passarom no descobrimento da Frolida.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: The discouerie of Florida, next adioyning to Virginia.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Matthew Lownes</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Felix Kyngston</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the signe of the Bishops head in Pauls Churchyard</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
