<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Honour and vertue, triumphing over the grave Exemplified in a faire devout life, and death, adorned with the surviving perfections of Edward Lord Stafford, lately deceased; the last baron of that illustrious family: which honour in him ended with as great lustre as the sunne sets within a serene skye. A treatise so written, that it is as well applicative to all of noble extraction, as to him, and wherein are handled all the requisites of honour, together with the greatest morall, and divine vertues, and commended to the practise of the noble prudent reader. By Anth. Stafford his most humble kinsman. This worke is much embelish'd by the addition of many most elegant elegies penned by the most accute wits of these times.</title>
         <author>Stafford, Anthony.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[20], 88, 91-92, [44] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by J. Okes [and Thomas Cotes?], for Henry Seile at the Tigres Head in Fleet-street, over against St. Dunstans Church,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1640">1640.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>"Edward Lord Stafford" is an error for "Henry Lord Stafford".</note>
         <note>Includes verses by various authors.</note>
         <note>"Quires P-V may have been pr[inted]. by a different printer, possibly T. Cotes"--STC.</note>
         <note>With a preliminary errata leaf.</note>
         <note>Leaves N2-O4, probably containing elegies, are cancelled in all copies.</note>
         <note>A variant of the edition with "Henry Lord Stafford" on title and Richard Lownes as bookseller in imprint.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the University of Illinois (Urbana-Champaign Campus). Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
