<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>XI. choice sermons preached upon selected occasions, in Cambridge. Viz. I. The preachers dignity, and duty: in five sermons, upon 2. Corinth. 5. 20. II. Christ crucified, the tree of life: in six sermons, on 1. Corinth. 2. 2. By John Stoughton, Doctor in Divinity, sometimes fellow of Immanuel Colledge in Cambridge, late preacher of Aldermanburie, London. According to the originall copie, which was left perfected by the authour before his death.</title>
         <author>Stoughton, John, d. 1639.</author>
         <author>Burgess, Anthony, d. 1664.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[14], 104; [8], 131, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by R. B[adger] for Iohn Bellamie, Henry Overton, Iohn Rothwell, and Ralph Smith,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1640.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
         <note>Dedication signed: A.B.</note>
         <note>In two parts, each with separate title page.</note>
         <note>A1 is a separate title page, with same imprint, reading: Five sermons, on II Cor. V.XX. Preached at Cambridge, by John Stoughton, ..</note>
         <note>[2d] A2 is a separate title page, with same imprint, reading: Sixe sermons, on I Cor. II.II. Preached at Cambridge, by John Stoughton, ..</note>
         <note>[2d] A1 is a blank, included in pagination.</note>
         <note>Also issued as parts 2 and 3 of STC 23306, XV choice sermons, preached upon selected occasions, published in 1640.</note>
         <note>Part 2 possibly issued separately as STC 23312. Sixe sermons, on I Cor. II.II.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the Union Theological Seminary (New York, N.Y.). Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
