<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>An assertion for true and Christian church-policie VVherein certaine politike obiections made against the planting of pastours and elders in every congregation, are sufficientlie aunswered. And wherein also sundrie projectes are set downe, how the discipline by pastors &amp; elders may be planted, without any derogation to the Kings royal prerogatiue, any indignitie to the three estates in Parleament, or any greater alteration of the laudable lawes, statutes, or customes of the realme, then may well be made without damage to the people.</title>
         <author>Stoughton, William, fl. 1584.</author>
         <author>Knollys, Francis, Sir, d. 1643.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[16], 439, [9] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by Richard Schilders],</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[Middelburg :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1604">1604.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>With eight leaves of dedication "To the apprentices and students of the Innes of Court", signed by William Stoughton, inserted after the title page. The signature is defaced or deleted in at least the Oxford copies. The first of these leaves is signed "*". Variant 1: lacking these leaves.</note>
         <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
         <note>Running title reads: An assertion for true and Christian church policy.</note>
         <note>"Speaches vsed in the Parleament by Sir Francis Knolles: and after written to my L. Treasurer, Sir William Cecill", [4] leaves at end.</note>
         <note>Line 6 of title has "Pastours". Variant 2: quires A-L in a different setting, with "Pastors"; lacking the dedication leaves.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
         <note>Some leaves tightly bound.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
