<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The survey of London containing the original, increase, modern estate and government of that city, methodically set down : with a memorial of those famouser acts of charity, which for publick and pious vses have been bestowed by many worshipfull citizens and benefactors : as also all the ancient and modern monuments erected in the churches, not only of those two famous cities, London and Westminster, but (now newly added) four miles compass / begun first by the pains and industry of John Stow, in the year 1598 ; afterwards inlarged by the care and diligence of A.M. in the year 1618 ; and now compleatly finished by the study &amp; labour of A.M., H.D. and others, this present year 1633 ; whereunto, besides many additions (as appears by the contents) are annexed divers alphabetical tables, especially two, the first, an index of things, the second, a concordance of names.</title>
      <author>Stow, John, 1525?-1605.</author>
      <author>Munday, Anthony, 1553-1633.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[14], 939 [i.e. 943], [29] p. : ill., coats of arms.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Nicholas Bourn</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop at the south entrance of the Royal-Exchange</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1633">1633.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"The remaines or remnants of divers worthy things, which should have had their due place and honour in this worke, if promising friends had kept their words" has special t.p.</note>
      <note>"A. M., H. D. and others" [i.e. Anthony Munday, Henry Dyson, and others]--Cf. STC (2nd ed.) and NUC pre-1956 imprints.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A&#8312;(-A1) B-2X&#8310; 2Y&#8309; (2Y)&#8309; 2Z-4K&#8310; 4L-4M&#8308; 4N&#8310;.</note>
      <note>Numerous errors in paging.</note>
      <note>Includes indexes.</note>
      <note>Marginal notes.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Harvard University Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Nicholas Bourn</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop at the south entrance of the Royal-Exchange</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
