<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A challenge concerning the Romish Church, her doctrine &amp; practises, published first against Rob. Parsons, and now againe reuiewed, enlarged, and fortified, and directed to him, to Frier Garnet, to the archpriest Blackevvell and all their adh&#230;rents, by Matth. Sutcliffe. Thereunto also is annexed an answere vnto certeine vaine, and friuolous exceptions, taken to his former challenge, and to a certeine worthlesse pamphlet lately set out by some poore disciple of Antichrist, and entituled, A detection of diuers notable vntrueths, contradictions, corruptions, and falsifications gathered out of M. Sutcliffes new challenge, &amp;c.</title>
      <author>Sutcliffe, Matthew, 1550?-1629.</author>
      <author>Sutcliffe, Matthew, 1550?-1629. Briefe replie to a certaine odious and slanderous libel.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[26], 72, 93-210; 230, [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Arnold Hatfield [</persName>, <persName type="printer">John Windet</persName>, and <persName type="printer">J. Harrison]</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1602">1602.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>The "detection of divers notable untrueths" is by Philip Woodward.</note>
      <note>The "challenge" was first published in Sutcliffe's "A briefe replie to a certaine odious and slanderous libel".</note>
      <note>Hatfield printed part 1; in part 2 Windet apparently printed A-D and E outer sheet; Harrison printed E inner sheet and the rest (STC).</note>
      <note>"An answere first vnto such exceptions, as by a certaine namelesse, and worthlesse fellow are taken to the challenge precedent" (caption title) has separate pagination and register.</note>
      <note>The last leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Union Theological Seminary (New York, N.Y.). Library.</note>
      <note>Part 1: title page torn, A7 and pages 149-50 stained; part 2: pages 98, 129-30 stained and 197-204 lacking. Title page of part 1 and pages 190-215 of part 2 from the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery copy filmed at end.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Arnold Hatfield [</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>J. Harrison]</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>John Windet</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
