<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The historie of the Church since the dayes of our Saviour Iesus Christ, vntill this present age. Devided into foure bookes. 1. The first containeth the whole proceedings and practises of the emperours ... 2. The second containeth a breefe catalogue of the beginnings, and proceedings; of all the bishops, popes, patriarchs, doctors, pastors, and other learned men ... 3. The third containeth a short summe of all the heretiques ... 4. The fourth containeth a short compend of all the councels generall, nationall, and provinciall ... Devided into 16. centuries. ... Collected out of sundry authors both ancient and moderne; by the famous and worthy preacher of Gods word, Master Patrick Symson, late minister at Striueling in Scotland.</title>
      <title>Historie of the Church. Part 1</title>
      <author>Simson, Patrick, 1556-1618.</author>
      <author>Simson, Patrick, 1556-1618. Short compend of the historie of the first ten persecutions moved against Christians.</author>
      <author>Symson, Andrew.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[16], 243, 246-438, 438-466, 468-770 [i.e. 700], [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">I[ohn] D[awson]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Iohn Bellamie</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop, at the three Golden Lions in Corne-hill neere the Royall Exchange:</placeName> and for <persName type="publisher">William Sheffard</persName>, at <placeName>the entering in of Popes-head Alley, out of Lumbard streete</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1624">1624.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Editor's dedication signed: A. Symson.</note>
      <note>Includes rearranged extracts from the history of the first nine centuries of the Church from his: A short compend of the historie of the first ten persecutions moved against Christians.</note>
      <note>The last leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>P. 700 misnumbered 770.</note>
      <note>A second part was published in 1625.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Iohn Bellamie</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>William Sheffard</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>I[ohn] D[awson]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop, at the three Golden Lions in Corne-hill neere the Royall Exchange:</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the entering in of Popes-head Alley, out of Lumbard streete</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
