<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Three bookes of colloquies concerning the arte of shooting in great and small peeces of artillerie, variable randges, measure, and waight of leaden, yron, and marble stone pellets, minerall saltepeeter, gunpowder of diuers sortes, and the cause why some sortes of gunpower are corned, and some sortes of gunpowder are not corned: written in Italian, and dedicated by Nicholas Tartaglia vnto the Royall Prince of most famous memorie Henrie the eight, late King of England, Fraunce, and Ireland, defender of the faith &amp;c. And now translated into English by Cyprian Lucar Gent. who hath also augmented the volume of the saide colloquies with the contents of euery colloquie, and with all the corollaries and tables, that are in the same volume. Also the said Cyprian Lucar hath annexed vnto the same three books of colloquies a treatise named Lucar Appendix ...</title>
         <author>Tartaglia, Niccol&#242;, d. 1557.</author>
         <author>Lucar, Cyprian, b. 1544.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8], 80, [4], 120, [2] p. : ill.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>[by Thomas Dawson] for Iohn Harrison [the elder],</publisher>
         <pubPlace>Printed at London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1588">1588.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Printer's name and that Harrison is the elder from colophon.</note>
         <note>Original sub title page on G5 with device McKerrow 236 is sometimes replaced by cancel bifolium with sub title page with cut of mortar shooting and errata on verso of 2nd leaf; both varieties in Harvard University. Library copy. Harvard also has cancel G3,4 with G3r line 5 from bottom ending "saide" instead of "sayde" as in the British Library copy--STC.</note>
         <note>With a final errata leaf.</note>
         <note>With cancel.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
