<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Diuine epistles Dedicated. to right honble. &amp; worthy guests inuited to ye nuptialls of the great Kings sonne. &amp;c By Augustin. Taylor. preacher at Hawarden</title>
      <author>Taylor, Augustine.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[202] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Nicholas Okes</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1623">1623.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>In verse.</note>
      <note>The title page is engraved. The date appears to have been corrected in the plate from "1622".</note>
      <note>Signatures: pi&#185; A&#8308; B-N.</note>
      <note>"The epistle of the Lord, to his bride, vpon her creation", "The epistle of the Lord to his bride, vpon her election", "The epistle of the Lord to his bride, vpon her vocation", "The epistle of the Lord to his bride, vpon her preseruation", "The epistle of the Lord to his bride, vpon her redemption", "The epistle of the Lord to his bride, vpon her sanctification", "The epistle of the Lord to his bride, vpon her iustification", "The epistle of the Lord to his bride, vpon her glorification", "The epistle of the bride to her Lord, expressing her gratitude",.</note>
      <note>"The epistle of the bride to her Lord, containing her thankfulnesse", "The epistle of the bride to her Lord, expressing her gratitude", "The epistle of the bride to her Lord, declaring her confidence", "The epistle of the bride to her Lord, containing her petitions", "An epistle or a legacy for the vse of the Right Reuerend Father in God, Iohn, Lord Bishop, of the Isles of Man, &amp;c.", "A vvatch", and "The defence of diuine poesie" each has separate dated title page; register is continuous.</note>
      <note>The last leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      <note>Engraved title page not filmed.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Nicholas Okes</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
