<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A synopsis or compendium of the fathers, or of the most famous and ancient doctors of the Church, as also of the schoolmen Wherein is clearely shewed how much is to be attributed to them, in what severall times they lived, with what caution they are to be read, and which were their perfections, which their errors. A treatise most necessary, and profitable to young divines, and delightfull to all such whose studies in humanity take from them the leisure, though not the desire of reading the fathers; whose curiosity this briefe surveigh of antiquity will in part satisfie. Written in Latin by that reverend and renowned divine, Daniel Tossanus, chiefe Professor of Divinity in the University of Heidelberge, and faithfully Englished by A.S. Gent.</title>
      <title>Synopsis de patribus. English</title>
      <author>Tossanus, Daniel, 1541-1602.</author>
      <author>Stafford, Anthony.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[24], 87, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed [by <persName type="printer">John Beale]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Daniel Frere</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>the signe of the Red Bull in Little-Brittaine</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1635">1635.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of: Synopsis de patribus.</note>
      <note>Translator's dedication signed: A.S., i.e. Anthony Stafford.</note>
      <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
      <note>The first two leaves are blank.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: A synopsis or compendium of the fathers and schoolemen.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Daniel Frere</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>John Beale]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the signe of the Red Bull in Little-Brittaine</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
