<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The trial of trueth or a treatise vvherein is declared vvho should be iudge betvvene the Reformed Churches, and the Romish in which is shewed, that neither Pope, nor Councels, nor Fathers, nor traditions, nor succession, nor consent, nor antiquitie of custome: but the onely written worde of God, ought to determine the controuersies of religio[n]: wherin also is declared which is the true religion, and Catholick church. Written for the pleasure of the Popes, Cardinalles, prelates, abbots, monkes: and speciallie the Iesuites, which of late were driuen out of Transyluania, by the states there. Published in Latine by a certaine Hungarian, a fauourer of the trueth: and translated into English by Richard Smith.</title>
      <title>Oratio de constituendo iudice controversiorum religionis. English.</title>
      <author>Smith, Richard, tr.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 31, [1] leaves   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>[By <persName type="printer">Iohn Windet]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Robert Dexter</persName>, <persName type="publisher">&amp;</persName> are to be sold in <placeName>Pauls Churchyard, at the signe of the Brasen Serpent</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1591">1591.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation by Richard Smith of: Oratio de constituendo iudice controversiorum religionis (Basel, 1591).</note>
      <note>Printer's name from colophon.</note>
      <note>With a final errata and colophon leaf.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>&amp;</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Robert Dexter</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Iohn Windet]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Pauls Churchyard, at the signe of the Brasen Serpent</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
