<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The first and seconde partes of the herbal of William Turner Doctor in Phisick, lately ouersene, corrected and enlarged with the thirde parte, lately gathered, and nowe set oute with the names of the herbes, in Greke Latin, English, Duche, Frenche, and in the apothecaries and herbaries Latin, with the properties, degrees, and naturall places of the same. Here vnto is ioyned also a booke of the bath of Baeth in England, and of the vertues of the same with diuerse other bathes, moste holsom and effectuall, both in Almanye and England, set furth by William Turner Doctor in Phisick. God saue the Quene</title>
         <title>New herball</title>
         <author>Turner, William, d. 1568.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[12], 223, [5] p.; [2], 171, [3] leaves; [10], 81, [3] p.; [4], 17, [1] leaves : ill. (woodcuts)  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>By [the heirs of] Arnold Birckman,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>Imprinted at Collen :</pubPlace>
         <date>in the yeare of our Lorde M.D.LXVIII. [1568]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>At foot of title: Cum gratia &amp; priuilegio Reg. Maiest.</note>
         <note>Identification of printer from STC.</note>
         <note>In four parts (parts 1-3 of the herbal, and "A booke of the natures and properties, as well of the bathes in England as of other bathes in Germanye and Italye"); each has separate foliation or pagination and dated title page; parts 2 and 4 each begin new register.</note>
         <note>Part 1 reprints STC 24365; parts 2 and 4 are reissues with new preliminaries of STC 24366; part 3 is completely new.</note>
         <note>Errata for part 2 are retained from STC 24366. Further errata were prepared, but are usually not present (though included in pagination above). These consist of three leaves: ¹A² , "Peter Turner to the reader", with errata for the preliminaries and part 1; and one leaf marked "*.j." in the third part. Variant: the additional errata in an earlier form, with two leaves signed [par.] containing errata for the preface and parts 1 and 3.</note>
         <note>Includes indexes.</note>
         <note>The last leaf is blank.</note>
         <note>Often bound with: Brunschwig, Hieronymus.  A most excellent and perfecte homish apothecarye or homely physick booke: Collen, 1561.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
         <note>Part 4 not filmed.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
