<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Enchiridion medicum containing an epitome of the whole course of physicke: with the examination of a chirurgion, by way of dialogue betweene the doctor and the students. With a treatise contaning a definition of all those difenses that do chiefly affect the body of a man, and an antidotary of many excelllent and approued remedies for all diseases. Published for the benefit of young students in physicke, chirurgian, and apothecaries.</title>
      <author>Pomarius, Petrus.</author>
      <author>Hobbes, Stephen.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[6], 125, [2], 89, 70, [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Henry Ballard</persName> for <persName type="publisher">George Potter</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop at the North doore of Paules</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1609">1609.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>By Petrus Pomarius.</note>
      <note>Errata on recto of A2.</note>
      <note>"The examination of a chirugion, wherein is handled the whole course of chirurgerie by way of a dialogue betweene the doctor and the student. By S[tephen]. H[obbes]. " has separate dated title page and pagination; register is continuous.</note>
      <note>"The antidotary" has caption title and separate pagination; register is continuous.</note>
      <note>Title page stained and cropped, with some loss of imprint (supplied from Cambridge University Catalogue).</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the University of Nebraska-Lincoln, Love Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>George Potter</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Henry Ballard</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop at the North doore of Paules</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
