<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A Catalogue of all the kings ships, as also of all other ships, and pinnaces, together with their squadrons, captaines, burthen, seamen, and landmen, set forth in His Maiesties seruice, the 27 of Iune, 1627</title>
      <author>Buckingham, George Villiers, Duke of, 1592-1628.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>1 sheet ([1] p.) : ill.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Iohn Wright</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1627">[1627]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Place and date of publication from STC (2nd ed.).</note>
      <note>Contains an illustration of a mounted, armed knight.</note>
      <note>At head of sheet (possibly referring to the illustration): The right high and mightie Prince George Villiers, Duke, Marquis, and Earle of Buckingham, Earle of Coventry, Vicount [sic] Villiers, Baron of Whaddon, high Admirall of England, &amp; Ireland, and of the Principallitie of Wales. Gouernour of all the Castles and Sea Forts, and of the Royall Nauy, Master of the Horse to his Maiestie. Lord Warden, Chancellour, and Admirall of the Cinque Ports, and the members thereof: Constable of the Castle of Douer, Iustice in Eyre of all his Majesties Forests, Parkes, and Chases on this side the Riuer of Trent, Constable of the Royall Castle of Windesore. Gentleman of the Kings Bedchamber, Councellour of Estate of the Kingdomes of England, Scotland and Ireland. Knight of the most noble order of the Garter. Lord President of the Councel of Warre: and Chancellour of the Vniuersitie of Cambridge.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in: Society of Antiquaries.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Iohn Wright</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
