<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A iovrnall of all the proceedings of the duke of Buckingham his grace, in the isle of Ree, a part of France Whereunto is added the names of the French nobilitie that were slaine. Set forth by a gentleman of special note who was a spectator of all that hapned. Published by authoritie.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2, 14 [i.e. 16], [2], 19, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed [by <persName type="printer">A. Mathewes]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Walkley</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop at the Eagle</placeName> and Childe in <placeName>Britaines-Bursse</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1627">1627.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
      <note>Contains separate title page, with same imprint, reading: A continued iournal of all the proceedings of the duke of Buckingham: his Grace, in the isle of Ree, a part of France. In whom are combined religion, fortitude, and clemencie; being the true characters of a noble generall. Published by authoritie.</note>
      <note>Includes: Receiued at Yorke-house. August 15. The relation of Mr. Garetson, master of the shippe called the Bread and Beere-pott of Horne in Holland, made and taken at Plimmouth the 12. of August 1627. by Sit Iames Bagge, knight, who reporteth the same as followeth, with caption title.</note>
      <note>A variant, with additions to the title, of STC 24739.5.</note>
      <note>Pages 6-7 repeated in number only.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Walkley</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>A. Mathewes]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Britaines-Bursse</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop at the Eagle</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
