<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The mariners mirrour wherin may playnly be seen the courses, heights, distances, depths, soundings, flouds and ebs, risings of lands, rocks, sands and shoalds, with the marks for th'entrings of the harbouroughs, havens and ports of the greatest part of Europe: their seueral traficks and commodities: together wth. the rules and instrume[n]ts of navigation. First made &amp; set fourth in diuers exact sea-charts, by that famous nauigator Luke Wagenar of Enchuisen and now fitted with necessarie additions for the use of Englishmen by Anthony Ashley. Heerin also may be understood the exploits lately atchiued by the right Honorable the L. Admiral of Engla[n]d with her Maties. nauie and some former seruices don by that worthy knight Sr. Fra: Drake.</title>
      <title>Spieghel der zeevaerdt. English</title>
      <author>Waghenaer, Lucas Janszoon, 1534 or 5-1606.</author>
      <author>Ashley, Anthony, Sir, 1551-1628.</author>
      <author>Bry, Theodor de, 1528-1598, engraver.</author>
      <author>Hondius, Jodocus, 1563-1612, engraver.</author>
      <author>Ryther, Augustine, engraver.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[230] p. : maps (metal cuts)  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">John Charlewood</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1588" cert="low">1588?]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation by Ashley of: Spieghel der zeevaerdt.</note>
      <note>The title page is engraved and signed: Theodore de bry fecit.</note>
      <note>The plates are re-engraved by Bry, Jodocus Hondius, and Augustine Ryther.</note>
      <note>Printer's name from STC; the dedication is dated 20 Oct. 1588.</note>
      <note>Signatures: pi&#178;  [par.]&#178;  chi&#178;  A-C&#8310; (1)-(22)&#178; ; chi&#185; I-XXIII&#178; .</note>
      <note>The second part has separate divisional title and register.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>John Charlewood</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
