<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Theologicall questions, dogmaticall observations, and evangelicall essays, vpon the Gospel of Jesus Christ, according to St. Matthew Wherein, about two thousand six hundred and fifty necessary, and profitable questions are discussed; and five hundred and eighty speciall points of doctrine noted; and five hundred and fifty errours confuted, or objections answered: together with divers arguments, whereby divers truths, and true tenents are confirmed. By Richard VVard, sometimes student in the famous vniversities of Cambridge in England: St. Andrews in Scotland: and Master of Arts of both the kingdoms; and now a preacher in the famous city of London.</title>
         <author>Ward, Richard, 1601 or 2-1684.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 280, 289-364, 391-460, 463-466, 465-528, [2], 78, 81-226, 231-411, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed [by Marmaduke Parsons and others] for Peter Cole, and are to be sold at his shop in Cornhill, at the sign of the Glove and Lyon, neer the Royall Exchange,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1640">M.DC.XL. [1640]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Parsons printed quires 2P-3Y; others, possibly including Thomas Cotes and John Legat, did the rest (STC).</note>
         <note>The words "Theologicall .. essays,", "Cambridge .. St. Andrews", and "England .. Scotland:" are enclosed in brackets on the title page; the word "in" appears once only between the last two groupings.</note>
         <note>Chapter 10 begins new pagination on 3A1r.</note>
         <note>Includes index.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Union Theological Seminary (New York, N.Y.). Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
