<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The soules progresse to the celestiall Canaan, or heavenly Jerusalem By way of godly meditation, and holy contemplation: accompanied with divers learned exhortations, and pithy perswasions, tending to Christianity and humanity. Divided into two parts. The first part treateth of the divine essence, quality and nature of God, and his holy attributs: and of the creation, fall, state, death, and misery of an unregenerated man, both in this life and in the world to come: put for the whole scope of the Old Testament. The second part is put for the summe and compendium of the Gospell, and treateth of the Incarnation, Nativity, words, works, and sufferings of Christ, and of the happinesse and blessednesse of a godly man in his state of renovation, being reconciled to God in Christ. Collected out of the Scriptures, and out of the writings of the ancient fathers of the primitive Church, and other orthodoxall divines: by John Welles, of Beccles in the County of Suffolk.</title>
      <author>Welles, John, of Beccles.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[28], 304, [1], 308-372, [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">E[dward] G[riffin]</persName> and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Henry Shephard</persName> in <placeName>Chancery-lane, at the signe of the Bible, between Serjeants-Inne</placeName> and Fleetstreet, neere <placeName>the Kings-head-Taverne</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1639">1639.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
      <note>The page following 304 is numbered 317.</note>
      <note>With a final imprimatur leaf.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in Harvard University. Library.</note>
      <note>Pages 355-356 mutilated.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>E[dward] G[riffin]</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Henry Shephard</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Chancery-lane, at the signe of the Bible, between Serjeants-Inne</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Kings-head-Taverne</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
