<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Exercitations divine Containing diverse questions and solutions for the right understanding of the Scriptures. Proving the necessitie, majestie, integritie, perspicuitie, and sense thereof. As also shewing the singular prerogatiues wherewith the Lord indued those whom he appointed to bee the pen-men of them. Together with the excellencie and use of divinitie above all humane sciences. All which are cleared out of the Hebrew, and Greeke, the two originall languages in which the Scriptures were first written, by comparing them with the Samaritane, Chaldie, and Syriack copies, and with the Greeke interpretors, and vulgar Latine translation. By Iohn Weemse, of Lathocker in Scotland, preacher of Christs Gospell.</title>
      <author>Weemes, John, 1579?-1636.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[32], 188, [4] p. : ill. (woodcut)  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">T. Cotes</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Iohn Bellamie</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shoppe at the signe of the three Golden Lyons in Cornehill, neere the Royall Exchange</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1632">1632.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>The first leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>Includes indexes.</note>
      <note>With two final addenda leaves.</note>
      <note>Usually bound with STC 25207.5.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Iohn Bellamie</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>T. Cotes</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shoppe at the signe of the three Golden Lyons in Cornehill, neere the Royall Exchange</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
