<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>An ansvvere to the Ten reasons of Edmund Campian the Iesuit in confidence wherof he offered disputation to the ministers of the Church of England, in the controuersie of faith. Whereunto is added in briefe marginall notes, the summe of the defence of those reasons by Iohn Duræus the Scot, being a priest and a Iesuit, with a reply vnto it. Written first in the Latine tongue by the reuerend and faithfull seruant of Christ and his Church, William Whitakers, Doctor in Diuinitie, and the Kings Professor and publike reader of Diuinitie in the Vniuersitie of Cambridge. And now faithfully translated for the benefit of the vnlearned (at the appointment and desire of some in authoritie) into the English tongue; by Richard Stocke, preacher in London. ...</title>
         <title>Ad Rationes decem Edmundi Campiani Jesuitæ responsio. English</title>
         <author>Whitaker, William, 1548-1595.</author>
         <author>Campion, Edmund, Saint, 1540-1581. Rationes decem. English.</author>
         <author>Stock, Richard, 1569?-1626.</author>
         <author>Whitaker, William, 1548-1595. Responsionis ad Decem illas rationes.</author>
         <author>Durie, John, d. 1587. Confutatio responsionis Gulielmi Whitakeri ad Rationes decem. Selections.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[40], 326 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>By Felix Kyngston, for Cuthbert Burby and Edmund Weauer,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1606.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A translation of: Ad Rationes decem Edmundi Campiani Jesuitæ responsio.</note>
         <note>Includes a translation of: Campion, Edmund.  Rationes decem.</note>
         <note>Includes excerpts from Whitaker's "Responsionis ad Decem illas rationes, quibus fretus Edmundus Campianus certamen Ecclesiæ Anglicanæ ministris obtulit in causa fidei, defensio contra confutationem Joannis Duræi Scoti, presbyteri, Jesuitæ", which reprints and replies to: Durie, John. Confutatio responsionis Gulielmi Whitakeri ad Rationes decem.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
