<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>George, by the diuine prouidence, Bishop of London: to all and singuler archdeacons, deanes, and their officials, parsons, vicars, curates, churchwardens; and to all other ecclesiasticall officers and ministers, within my Diocesse of Winton, and the seuerall parishes thereof, greeting Whereas letters haue been lately addressed vnto vs from the most Reuerend Father in God, the Lord Archbishop of Canterburie his Grace, recommending ... the publication of a discourse written by Captaine Richard Whitbourne, concerning New-found-land ...</title>
         <author>Church of England. Diocese of London. Bishop (1621-1628 : Montaigne)</author>
         <author>Montaigne, George, 1569-1628.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>1 sheet ([1] p.)   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by Felix Kingston,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1622]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Signed: at London, the 16. of Septem. 1622. Geo. London, i.e. George Mountaigne, Bishop of London.</note>
         <note>Referring to Whitbourne's "A discourse containing a loving invitation for the advancement of his Majesties most hopefull plantation in the New-found-land", and instructing parishes to collect money for Whitbourne.</note>
         <note>Imprint from STC.</note>
         <note>One of five versions of this text, each printed from standing type with varying amounts of alteration. This version has the text in two paragraphs. For details on printing history see "Essays honoring Lawrence C. Wroth", p. 223-33.</note>
         <note>Usually found with STC 25372 and 25375a.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
         <note>MS. note signed by Whitbourne.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
