<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The enemie to vnthryftinesse publishing, by lawes, documents and disciplines. A right rule, for reformation of pride, and other prodigall and riotous disorders, in a common wealth: for the worthines of directions, a perfect mirrour for all maiestrates: (especially) of cities. And for sound counsels, and admonitions, a carde to compasse, or euery yong gentleman, honorablie and profitably to gouerne his actions. Partely, drawne out of the sage gouernme[n]t, of the most worthie emperour, Alexander Seuerus: and (generallye) discoueringe the vnsufferable abuses now raigning in our happie English co[m]mon wealth. By George Whetstons gent.</title>
      <title>Mirour for magestrates of cyties</title>
      <author>Whetstone, George, 1544?-1587?</author>
      <author>Whetstone, George, 1544?-1587? Addition: or touchstone for the time. aut</author>
      <author>Severus Alexander, Emperor of Rome, 208-235.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 36 leaves   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">Richard Jones</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Printed at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1586">Anno 1584 [i.e. 1586]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Actual date of publication from STC.</note>
      <note>Leaves 25 and 26 misnumbered 75 and 78.</note>
      <note>G2 is a separate title page, undated, with same imprint, reading: An addition: or touchstone for the time: exposyng the daingerous mischiefes, that the Dicyng howses (co[m]monly called) ordinarie tables, and other (like) sanctuaries of iniquitie, do dayly breede: within the bovvelles of the famous citie of London. By George Whetstones, gent.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: A mirour for magistrates of cities.</note>
      <note>Another issue (with A1-[par.] cancelled, and new title page and date) of STC 25341, published in 1584 with title: A mirour for magestrates of cyties.</note>
      <note>Identified as STC 25335 on UMI microfilm.</note>
      <note>Some print faded and show-through; some pages stained.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Richard Jones</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
