<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A sermon vpon the xii. xiij, and xiiij. verses of the xiiij. chapter of Ezechiel Wherein are chiefly shewed both the originall &amp; accidentall causes of euerie dearth and famine, and especially of this dearth in England now 1608. and 1609. With the effects and fruites of the same, as also the helpes &amp; remedies therof, if they be speedily and effectually practised. Preached at Strowd in the countrie of Glocester and published for the good of the church melitant. Whereunto is added a like meditation of the same author, vpon the 26. verse of the 11. chapter of Salomons Prouerbs, which may be called the Poore mans plea. By William Woodwall, minister and preacher of the word. 1609</title>
         <author>Woodwall, William.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[6], 68, [4] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by E. A[llde] for Ed. White, &amp; are to be solde at his shop neere the little North doore of S. Paules church at the Signe of the Gunne,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1609.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
         <note>G2r has caption title, reading: A prouerbe pronounced to all the cruell, couetous, and hard hearted corne-maisters, cloath-maisters, and al other olde pinching penny-fathers at this day amongst vs, who esteem more of their vnrighteous Mammon then of the counsell of Christ our beloved Sauiour, who aduertiseth them to make them friends therof in due time, that they might be receiued into euerlasting tabernacles and yet will not.</note>
         <note>H1 has caption title, reading: A meditation vpon the 26. verse of the 11. chap. of the Prouerbes; which may fitly be called, The poore-mans plea.</note>
         <note>print show-through, and some pages stained; leaf K1 is a facsimile.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Folger Shakespeare Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
