<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The light of navigation Wherein are declared and lively pourtrayed, all the coasts and havens, of the VVest, North and East seas. Collected partly out of the books of the principall authors which have written of navigation, (as Lucas Iohnson VVaghenaer and divers others) partly also out of manie other expert seafaring mens writings and verball declarations: corrected from manie faults, and inlarged with manie newe descriptions and cardes. Divided into tvvo bookes. Heerunto are added (beside an institution in the art of navigation) nevve tables of the declination of the sonne, according to Tycho Brahes observations, applied to the meridian of Amsterdam. Together with newe tables and instructions to teach men the right use of the North-starre, and other firme starres, profitable for all seafaring men. By William Iohnson.</title>
         <title>Licht der Zee-vaert. English</title>
         <author>Blaeu, Willem Janszoon, 1571-1638.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[54]; [2], 12, [2], 13-32, [2], 33-38, [2], 39-48, [2], 49-56, [2], 57-60, [2], 61-64, [2], 65-72, [2], 73-74, [2], 75-80, [2], 81-84, [2], 85-90, [2], 91-96, [2], 97-100, [2], 101-108, [2], 109-114, [2]; 4, [2], 5-18, [2], 19-26, [2], 27-30, [2], 31-36, [2], 37-42, [2], 43-46, [2], 47-52, [2], 53-56, [2], 57-62, [2], 63-70, [2], 71-76, [2], 77-80, [2], 81-84, [2], 85-100, [2], 101-106, [2], 107-112, [2], 113-114, [2], 115-118, [2] p., engr. maps : ill.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by VVilliam Iohnson [Blaeu], dvvelling upon the vvater, by the Old Bridge, at the signe of the Golden Son-dyal,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>At Amsterdam :</pubPlace>
         <date>Anno 1612.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Translation of: Licht der Zee-vaert.</note>
         <note>Printer's complete name from STC.</note>
         <note>The English general title page is pasted in the center of engraved Dutch title page.</note>
         <note>"The first book of the light of navigation" has separate dated title page and pagination; register is continuous. "The second book of the light of nauigation" has separate pagination, register and title page.</note>
         <note>At foot of title page: Cum privilegio.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
