<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The theoriques of the seuen planets shewing all their diuerse motions, and all other accidents, called passions, thereunto belonging. Now more plainly set forth in our mother tongue by M. Blundeuile, than euer they haue been heretofore in any other tongue whatsoeuer, and that with such pleasant demonstratiue figures, as euery man that hath any skill in arithmeticke, may easily vnderstand the same. ... VVhereunto is added by the said Master Blundeuile, a breefe extract by him made, of Maginus his Theoriques, for the better vnderstanding of the Prutenicall tables, to calculate thereby the diuerse motions of the seuen planets. There is also hereto added, The making, description, and vse, of two most ingenious and necessarie instruments for sea-men ... First inuented by M. Doctor Gilbert ... and now here plainely set downe in our mother tongue by Master Blundeuile.</title>
      <author>Blundeville, Thomas, fl. 1561.</author>
      <author>Magini, Giovanni Antonio, 1555-1617. aut</author>
      <author>Gilbert, William, 1540-1603. Making, description and use of two most ingenious and necessarie instruments for seamen. aut</author>
      <author>Wright, Edward, 1540-1603. aut</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[6], 278, 279-292, [2] p., folded plate : ill. (woodcuts)  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Adam Islip</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1602">1602.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"The making, description and vse of two most ingenious and necessarie instruments for seamen" has separate dated title page; "A short appendix annexed to the former treatise by Edward Wright, at the motion of the right worshipfull M. Doctor Gilbert" has caption title.</note>
      <note>The "plate" is a woodcut.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Adam Islip</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
