<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A pronostication for diuers yeares ryght vtyle and profytable to al sortes of people, wherin is declared what persons hath mooste and leaste dominacions ouer the starres and elementes, whereby the iudgementes of the astrologiens be scarsely true, geuynge together great consolation to those who muche fear the constellations. Also of the fourth and laste monarchie, the whiche Charles the. v. ryghte victorious Emperoure of the Romaynes, and Edwarde the. vi. mooste noble Emperoure of great Bryttayne, by the grace of God, gouerneth, comprehendynge also brieflye some words of the last age of the world, gathered together by Master Arnold Bogarde doctour in medecyne, resident in Bruxels and translated into Englysh oute of Frenche by Iohn Coke, clarcke of the Recognysances, or vulgerly called clark of the Statutes.</title>
         <title>Prognostication pour plusieurs années. English</title>
         <author>Bogaert, Arnould.</author>
         <author>Coke, John, clarke of the Kynges recognysaunce.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[54] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>In Paules churcheyarde by [R. Jugge for] Wyllyam Awen],</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[Imprynted at London :</pubPlace>
         <date>The yeare of oure Lorde God. M.D.LIII. [1553]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A translation, by Sir John Coke, of: Bogaert, Arnould. Prognostication pour plusieurs années.</note>
         <note>Place of publication and printer's name from colophon. Actual printer's name from STC.</note>
         <note>Identified as STC 3204a on UMI microfilm, reel 737.</note>
         <note>Signatures: A-C D⁴ (-D4, blank?).</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Folger Shakespeare Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
