<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A solemne ioviall disputation, theoreticke and practicke; briefely shadowing the lavv of drinking together, with the solemnities and controversies occurring: fully and freely discussed according to the civill lavv. Which, by the permission, priviledge and authority, of that most noble and famous order in the Vniversity of Goddesse Potina; Dionisius Bacchus being then president, chiefe gossipper, and most excellent governour, Blasius Multibibus, aliàs Drinkmuch ... hath publikely expounded to his most approved and improved fellow-pot-shots; touching the houres before noone and after, usuall and lawfull. ... Faithfully rendred according to the originall Latine copie.</title>
         <title>Disputatio inauguralis theoretico-practica jus potandi breviter adumbrans. English</title>
         <author>Multibibus, Blasius.</author>
         <author>Brathwaite, Richard, 1588?-1673. aut</author>
         <author>Marshall, William, fl. 1617-1650, ill.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8], 80, [6], 87-194, [6] p., 2 leaves of plates   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>At the signe of Red-eyes [i.e. printed by E. Griffin],</publisher>
         <pubPlace>Oenozphthopolis [i.e. London] :</pubPlace>
         <date>MDCXVII [1617]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>The imprint is fictitious; in fact printed in London by E. Griffin (STC).</note>
         <note>The "ph" in "Oenozphthopolis" is a Greek letter phi. The place name is probably a mistranscription of "Oenozytholpoli" in a Latin edition.</note>
         <note>The roman numeral date is made with turned C's.</note>
         <note>"The smoaking age, or, the man in the mist" has separate dated title page with imprint "Oenozphthopolis. At the signe of Teare-nose. MDCXVII."; pagination and register are continuous.</note>
         <note>"A solemn joviall disputation" is sometimes attributed to Richard Brathwait, but is in fact his translation, with additions, of the pseudonymous "Disputatio inauguralis theoretico-practica jus potandi breviter adumbrans" by Blasius Multibibus (pseudonym). "The smoaking age" is apparently Brathwait's alone.</note>
         <note>The plates, signed by William Marshall, bear the titles "The lawes of drinking." and "The smoaking age or the life and death of tobacco.".</note>
         <note>"At least 1 NY-Arents copy has a leaf of letterpress explanation preceding each frontispiece, lacking in most (all other?) copies."--STC. These are not included in pagination above.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in Cambridge University Library (second part only).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
