<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Tvvo epistles vnto great men of Britanie, in the yeare 1599 Requesting them to put their neckes unto the work of theyr Lord: to break the bread of the soule unto the hungry Iewes, by theyr writinges, or by theyr charges, through such as be ready to declare all that theyr necessity doth require. Printed now the second time, in the yeare synce the creation of the world 5532. Or yeare of the Lord 1606. Translated by the auctour for the use of such as would &amp; should know what in this cause ought to be performed.</title>
      <title>Two epistles unto great men of Britanie, in the yeare 1599.</title>
      <author>Broughton, Hugh, 1549-1612.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[20] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>s.n.],</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Amsterdam? :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1606">1606.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Dedication signed: Hugh Broughton.</note>
      <note>Date of publication conjectured by STC.</note>
      <note>Two letters. The first letter is to the Privy Council and dated 29 July 1599 at the end. The second letter is to Archbishop Whitgift, undated. Both letters refer to Broughton's "An epistle of an ebrew willinge to learne Christianity--Cf. STC.</note>
      <note>Title page plus A&#178;  (first leaf signed Aij) chi&#185; B&#8308; C&#178;  (British Library copy). Chi&#185; to end has initial "u" (e.g. 'unto') and may have been printed by G. Thorp since the initial 'F' on C1v seems to be identical to that in STC 239. A&#178;  has initial "v" (e.g. 'vnto') and also the same initial 'I' as in STC 3849, possibly printed in Amsterdam by by J. Theunisz. The title page has initial "v" twice and initial "u" twice--Cf. STC.</note>
      <note>Signatures: pi&#185; A&#178;  chi&#185; B&#8308; C&#178; .</note>
      <note>Imperfect; tightly bound and trimmed, affecting text.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
