<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>An harmony of the confessions of the faith of the Christian and Reformed Churches which purelie professe the holy doctrine of the Gospell in all the chiefe kingdomes, nations, and prouinces of Europe: the catologue and order whereof the pages following will declare. There are added in the ende verie shorte notes: in which both the obscure thinges are made plaine, &amp; those thinges which maie in shew seeme to be contrarie each to other, are plainelie and verie modestlie reconciled, and if anie points doe as yet hang in doubt, they are sincerelie pointed at. All which things, in the name of the Churches of Fraunce and Belgia, are submitted to the free and discrete iudgement of all other Churches. Newlie translated out of Latine into English. Also in the end is added the confession of the Church of Scotland. Alowed by publique authoritie.</title>
      <title>Harmonia confessionum fidei orthodoxarum &amp; reformatarum ecclesiarum. English</title>
      <author>Salnar.</author>
      <author>Goulart, Simon, 1543-1628.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[36], 111, 202-593 [i.e. 609], [41]; 24, [4] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Imprinted by <persName type="printer">Thomas Thomas</persName>, printer to <persName type="patron">the Vniuersitie of Cambridge</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Cambridge] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1586">1586.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>By Salnar, i.e. J.F. Salvart.</note>
      <note>A translation of: Harmonia confessionum fidei orthodoxarum &amp; reformatarum ecclesiarum.</note>
      <note>With notes by Simon Goulart.</note>
      <note>"A general confession of the true Christian faith and religion .. At Edinborough", 24, [4] p. at end, has separate register.</note>
      <note>P. 609 misnumbered 593.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Thomas Thomas</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="patron">
      <persName>the Vniuersitie of Cambridge</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
