<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The Christen rule or state of all the worlde from the hyghest to the lowest and how euery man shulde lyue to please God in hys callynge. Item, the Christian state of matrimony: and how ma[n] and wife shuld kepe house together with loue. Item, the maner oe [sic] saynge grace after the holy scrypture.</title>
         <author>Tyndale, William, d. 1536. Obedience of a Christen man and how Christen rulers ought to governe. aut</author>
         <author>Bullinger, Heinrich, 1504-1575. Christlich Eestand. aut</author>
         <author>Coverdale, Miles, 1488-1568. Christen exhortacion unto customable swearers. aut</author>
         <author>Bale, John, 1495-1563, attributed name. aut</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>44, 72, 71-78, 81-91, [5], 33 leaves   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>T. Raynalde and William Hill,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[London? :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1548" cert="low">1548?]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Sometimes attributed, in error, to Miles Coverdale. Part 1 in fact compiled from: Tyndale, William.  The obedience of a Christen man and how Christen rulers ought to governe. Part 2 is a translation of: Bullinger, Heinrich.  Der Christlich Eestand (cf. STC 4048.5). Part 3 is an edition of: Coverdale, Miles (cf. STC 1280.5).  A Christen exhortacion unto customable swearers. This (often attributed to John Bale) is attributed to Coverdale in DNB, NUC, Folger catalogue, Davies, W.T. A bibliography of John Bale. Oxford Bib. Soc. Proc. &amp; Papers 5 (1939): 4; attributed to John Bale in STC 1 and 2).</note>
         <note>Imprint from STC.</note>
         <note>Running title of part 1 reads: The Christen rule of the whole worlde.</note>
         <note>Text is continuous despite pagination.</note>
         <note>Identified as STC 5887 (former STC number) at reel 33:2.</note>
         <note>Imperfect: copy at reel 2059:20 has part 1 only.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the British Library (reel 33), University of Illinois (Urbana-Champaign Campus). Library (reel 2022), and Folger Shakespeare Library (reel 2059).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
