<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A prooued practise for all young chirurgians, concerning burnings with gunpowder, and woundes made with gunshot, sword, halbard, pyke, launce, or such other Wherein, is deliuered with all faithfulnesse, not onely the true receipts of such medicines as shall make them bolde, but also sundry familiar examples, such, as may leade them as it were by the hand, to the doyng of the lyke. Heereto is adioyned a treatise of the French or Spanish pockes, written by Iohn Almenar, a Spanish physition. Also, a commodious collection of aphorismes both English and Latin, taken out of an old written coppy. Published for the benefyte of his countrey, by Wylliam Clowes, mayster in chirurgery. Seene, and allowed, according to the order appoynted.</title>
      <title>Prooved practise for all young chirurgians, concerning burnings with gunpowder</title>
      <author>Clowes, William, ca. 1540-1604.</author>
      <author>Almenar, Juan de. De morbo Gallico. English. aut</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[32], 93, [60], 97-200, [4] p. : ill.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Thomas Orwyn</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Cadman</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1588">1588.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>The work on syphilis is a translation of: Almenar, Juan de.  De morbo Gallico.</note>
      <note>Signatures: [par.]&#8308; A-P&#8308; P.ii&#8308; P.iii&#8308; P.iiii&#8308; P.iiiii&#8308; P.iiiiii&#8308; P.iiiiiii&#8308; P.iiiiiiii&#8308; Q&#178;  &#178; Q-2E&#8308; 2F&#178; .</note>
      <note>Includes index.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: To all the young practizers of chirurgerie.</note>
      <note>Quire P is a cancel, containing extra case histories beginning with Maister Buckland's on P3r line 7 and continuing through the next seven unpaginated quires. Variant: collates [par.]&#8308; A-P&#8308; Q&#178;  &#178; Q-2E&#8308; 2G&#178; ; quire P is the cancellandum; the case histories are lacking.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Cadman</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Thomas Orwyn</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
