<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The life and death of Hector One, and the first of the most puissant, valiant, and renowned monarches of the world, called the nyne worthies. Shewing his jnvincible force, together with the marvailous, and most famous acts by him atchieved and done in the great, long, and terrible siege, which the princes of Greece held about the towne of Troy, for the space of tenne yeares. And finally his vnfortunate death after hee had fought a hundred mayne battailes in open field against the Grecians: the which heerein are all at large described. Wherein there were slaine on both sides fourteene hundred, and sixe thowsand, fourscore, and sixe men. VVritten by Iohn Lidgate monke of Berry, and by him dedicated to the high and mighty prince Henrie the fift, King of England.</title>
         <author>Colonne, Guido delle, 13th cent. Historia destructionis Troiae.</author>
         <author>Beno&#238;t, de Sainte-More, 12th cent. Roman de Troie.</author>
         <author>Lydgate, John, 1370?-1451? Troy book.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[12], 131, 126-318, [2] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by Thomas Purfoot,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1614">Anno. Dom. 1614.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A modernized verse paraphrase of the "Troy book" of John Lydgate, which was in turn ".. a very much amplified version .. of the prose Latin 'Historia destructionis Troiae' of Guido delle Colonne (about 1287) .. in turn a condensed version of the 'Roman de Troie' of Beno&#238;t de Sainte More (about 1160)"--Lydgate, J. Lydgate's Troy book. Early English Text Society, extra series 97, p. ix.</note>
         <note>Misattributed to Thomas Heywood.</note>
         <note>The first leaf and the last leaf are blank.</note>
         <note>Running title reads: The historie of the life, and death of Hector.</note>
         <note>Identified as STC 13346a on UMI microfilm.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
