<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The country-mans recreation, or the art of planting, graffing, and gardening in three bookes. The first declaring divers wayes of planting, and graffing ... also how to cleanse your grafts and cions, how to helpe barren and sicke trees, how to kill wormes and vermin and to preserve and keepe fruit, how to plant and proyne your vines, and to gather and presse your grape ... how to make your cider and perry ... The second treateth of the hop-garden, with necessary instructions for the making and the maintenance thereof ... Whereunto is added, the expert gardener, containing divers necessary and rare secrets belonging to that art ...</title>
      <author>Mascall, Leonard, d. 1589. Booke of the arte and maner, howe to plant and graffe all sortes of trees. aut</author>
      <author>Scot, Reginald, 1538?-1599. Perfite platforme of a hoppe garden. aut</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[16], 127, [1]; [2], 54 p. : ill.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">B. Allsop</persName> and <persName type="printer">T. Favvcet</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Michael Young</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop in Bedford-street in Coven-garden neere the New Exchange</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1640">1640.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Book 1 is an anonymous reprint of "A booke of the art and maner, howe to plante and graffe all sortes of trees" by Leonard Mascall. Book 2 is an anonymous reprint of "A perfite platforme of a hoppe garden" by Reginald Scot, with separate dated title page; pagination and register are continuous. Book 3 is a reissue of "The expert gardener: or, A treatise containing certaine necessary, secret, and ordinary knowledges in grafting and gardening" (STC 11562) with its original title page with imprint "London, printed by Richard Herne, 1640". This last work is an enlarged version of "A short instruction verie profitable and necessarie for all those that delight in gardening".</note>
      <note>The expert gardener also appears separately at reel 1098:16.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Michael Young</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>B. Allsop</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>T. Favvcet</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop in Bedford-street in Coven-garden neere the New Exchange</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
