<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Certain most godly, fruitful, and comfortable letters of such true saintes and holy martyrs of God, as in the late bloodye persecution here within this realme, gaue their lyues for the defence of Christes holy gospel written in the tyme of their affliction and cruell imprysonment.</title>
         <author>Coverdale, Miles, 1488-1568.</author>
         <author>Bradford, John, 1510?-1555, Exhortacion to the carienge of Chrystes crosse. Selections.</author>
         <author>Cranmer, Thomas, 1489-1556. Copy of certain lettres sent to the Quene, and also to doctour Martin and doctour Storye. Selections.</author>
         <author>Hooper, John, d. 1555. Soveraigne cordial for a Christian conscience.</author>
         <author>Hooper, John, d. 1555. Whether Christian faith maye be kepte secret in the heart, without confession therof openly to the worlde as occasion shal serve.</author>
         <author>Ridley, Nicholas, 1500?-1555. Frendly farewel.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8], 46, 49-689, [5] p. : ill.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>By Iohn Day, dwelling ouer Aldersgate, beneath Saint Martines,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1564.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Compiled by Miles Coverdale, whose name appears on leaf A2.</note>
         <note>At foot of title: Cum gratia &amp; priuilegio Regiæ Maiestatis.</note>
         <note>Leaves D8 and K6 are cancelled; text is continuous.</note>
         <note>With two final contents leaves.</note>
         <note>Includes letters by John Bradford (a partial reprint of "An exhortacion to the carienge of Chrystes crosse", STC 3480.5); John Careless; Thomas Cranmer (a partial reprint of "The copy of certain lettres sent to the Quene, and also to doctour Martin and doctour Storye" (STC 5999); John Hooper (a reprint of "A soveraigne cordial for a Christian conscience", STC 5157, possibly not by Hooper, and "Whether Christian faith maye be kepte secret in the heart, without confession therof openly to the worlde as occasion shal serve", STC 5160.3); John Philpot; and Nicholas Ridley (a reprint of "A frendly farewel", STC 21051).</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
