<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>An aunsvvere by the Reuerend Father in God Thomas Archbyshop of Canterbury, primate of all England and metropolitane, vnto a craftie and sophisticall cauillation, deuised by Stephen Gardiner Doctour of Law, late Byshop of Winchester agaynst the true and godly doctrine of the most holy sacrament, of the body and bloud of our sauiour Iesu Christ Wherein is also, as occasion serueth, aunswered such places of the booke of Doct. Richard Smith, as may seeme any thyng worthy the aunsweryng. Here is also the true copy of the booke written, and in open court deliuered, by D. Stephen Gardiner ...</title>
      <title>Answer of the Most Reverend Father in God Thomas Archebyshop of Canterburye, primate of all Englande and metropolitane unto a crafty and sophisticall cavillation devised by Stephen Gardiner doctour of law, late byshop of Winchester, agaynst the trewe and godly doctrine of the moste holy sacrament of the body and bloud of our saviour Jesu Christe</title>
      <author>Cranmer, Thomas, 1489-1556.</author>
      <author>Cranmer, Thomas, 1489-1556. Defence of the true and catholike doctrine of the sacrament of the body and bloud of our saviour Christ. Selections.</author>
      <author>Gardiner, Stephen, 1483?-1555. Explication and assertion of the true catholique fayth, touchyng the moost blessed sacrament of the aulter.</author>
      <author>Foxe, John, 1516-1587. Actes and monuments.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <editionStmt>
      <edition>Reuised, and corrected by the sayd archbyshop at Oxford before his martyrdome: wherein hee hath beautified Gardiners doynges, with asmuch diligence as might be, by applying notes in the margent, and markes to the doctours saying: which before wanted in the first impression. Hereunto is prefixed the discourse of the sayd archbyshops lyfe, and martyrdome, briefly collected out of his hystory of the actes and monumentes, and in the end is added certaine notes, wherein Gardiner varied, both from him selfe, and other papistes, gathered by the sayd archbyshop.</edition>
    </editionStmt>
    <extent>[28], 428, [4] p., [2] folded woodcut plates   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Iohn Daye</persName>, dwellyng ouer Aldersgate beneath S. Martines,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1580">Anno. 1580. Cum gratia &amp; priuilegio, Regi&#230; Maiestatis.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Thomas Archbishop of Canterbury = Thomas Cranmer.</note>
      <note>A reply to "An explication and assertion of the true catholique fayth, touchyng the moost blessed sacrament of the aulter" by Stephen Gardiner and "A confutation of a certen booke, called a defence of the true, and catholike doctrine of the sacrament, &amp;c. sette fourth of late in the name of Thomas Archebysshoppe of Canterburye" by Richard Smith.</note>
      <note>Reprints Gardiner's work and portions of Cranmer's "A defence of the true and catholike doctrine of the sacrament of the body and bloud of our saviour Christ".</note>
      <note>The woodcuts are from blocks used in Foxe's "Book of martyrs", and Cranmer's life is in part compiled from the same.</note>
      <note>Includes index.</note>
      <note>With a final colophon leaf.</note>
      <note>"The Latin headlines in rules appearing upside down at the foot of several versos in some copies indicate unused sheets of [STC] 11239 were employed in the printing"--STC.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Iohn Daye</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
