<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The confutation of the. xiii. articles, wherunto Nicolas Shaxton, late byshop of Salilburye [sic] subscribed and caused to be set forth in print the yere of our Lorde. M.C.xlvi. [sic] whe[n] he recanted in Smithfielde at London at the burning of mestres Anne Askue, which is liuely set forth in the figure folowynge. In the nexte page shalt thou finde the contentes of thys little boke.</title>
      <author>Crowley, Robert, 1518?-1588.</author>
      <author>Shaxton, Nicholas, 1485?-1556.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[160] p., folded woodcut plate   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">[S. Mierdman?</persName> for<persName type="publisher">] Iohn Day</persName>, and <persName type="publisher">William Seres</persName>, dwellynge in <placeName>Sepulchres parish, at the signe of the Resurrection, a litle aboue Holbourne conduite. Cum gratia &amp; priuilegio ad imprimendum solum</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date>[1548]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>The author's name, Robert Crowley, appears on A2r.</note>
      <note>Includes the text of Shaxton's submission, of which no separate printing survives.</note>
      <note>Actual printer's name conjectured and publication date supplied by STC.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A-K.</note>
      <note>The plate shows the burning of Anne Askew.</note>
      <note>Running title, which is split and transposed recto to verso, reads: The confutation of Shaxtons articles.</note>
      <note>Quire B inner forme has side-notes. Variant 1: title page misprints "cause be set forthe"; variant 2: quire B inner forme lacks side-notes.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>William Seres</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>] Iohn Day</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>[S. Mierdman?</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Sepulchres parish, at the signe of the Resurrection, a litle aboue Holbourne conduite. Cum gratia &amp; priuilegio ad imprimendum solum</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
