<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The tenor mornyng and euenyng prayer and communion, set forthe in foure partes, to be song in churches, both for men and and children wyth dyuers other godly prayers &amp; anthems, of sundry mens doynges.</title>
      <title>Bassus certaine notes set forth in foure and three parts to be song at the morning communion, and evening praier.</title>
      <author>Caustun, Thomas, d. 1569, attributed name.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[304] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">Iohn Day</persName>, dwelling ouer Aldersgate, beneath Saint Martins. These bookes are to be sold, at <placeName>hys shop vnderneath the gate</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1565.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Four partbooks tenor, contra tenor, medius, bassus), each with a separate title page. Partbook 1 previously published as STC 6418.</note>
      <note>Partbook 1 perhaps compiled by Thomas Caustun (Causton or Cawston), the only person credited in any way in STC 6418, which is included here.  He and many other persons are given credit for the arrangements here. For evidence concerning the printing and further details of individual copies see "The British Library Journal", X (1984), pp. 1-31--STC.</note>
      <note>The cancel title page of STC 6418 and quires N-T of the bassus and quires A-T of the 3 other partbooks were printed at this time--STC.</note>
      <note>At the foot of the first title page (and subsequent title pages): Cum gratia &amp; pruilegio reg&#230; maiestatis.</note>
      <note>At foot fo title page: Cum gratia &amp; priuilegio Regi&#230; Maiestatis.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A-T&#178;  &#178; A-T&#178;  &#179;A-T&#178;  &#8308;A-T&#178; .</note>
      <note>Formerly also STC 16443.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Iohn Day</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>hys shop vnderneath the gate</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
