<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Every-dayes sacrifice Wherein are comprehended many comfortable prayers and meditations, very necessary for all Christians. Also, many comforts for the sicke which are afflicted by the sight of their sins and the terrour of death; written by D. M. Luther, a little before his end. With most true comforts out of holy Scripture of the knowledge we shall haue of one another in the world to come. Translated by, W.R.S.</title>
      <author>W. R. S., fl. 1624.</author>
      <author>Luther, Martin, 1483-1546, attributed name.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[6], 276 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Humfrey Lownes</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">Iohn Parker</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shopin Paules Church yard at the sign of the three Pigeons</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1624">1624.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>An edition of: Every dayes sacrifice, attributed to Martin Luther but probably not in fact by him.</note>
      <note>The translator's initials are transposed only in this edition to: W.R.S.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: Euery-daies sacrifice.</note>
      <note>Includes, with separate dated title page: A comfort against the fear and terror of death, and the graue; being an exposition of Doctor Martin Luther, written a little before his end.</note>
      <note>Register and pagination continuous.</note>
      <note>Imperfect; leaf M1 torn, with loss of print.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Cambridge University Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Iohn Parker</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Humfrey Lownes</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shopin Paules Church yard at the sign of the three Pigeons</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
