<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Ten sermons tending chiefely to the fitting of men for the worthy receiuing of the Lords Supper VVherein amongst many other holy instructions: the doctrines of sound repentance and humiliation, and of Gods speciall fauours vnto penitent sinners, and worthy communicants are largely and effectually handled. The six first, by I. Dod. The foure last, by R. Cleauer. Whereunto is annexed, a plaine and learned metaphrase on the epistle to the Collossians, written by a godly and iudicious preacher. There is also set before the sermons, a short dialogue of preparation: containing the chiefe points that concerne the worthy receiuing of the Lords Supper, taken for the most part, out of the sermons following: and collected into a method for the benefit and ease of those that desire direction in this matter.</title>
      <author>Dod, John, 1549?-1645.</author>
      <author>Cleaver, Robert, 1561 or 2-ca. 1625. aut</author>
      <author>Winston, John, fl. 1614-1634.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8], 170 [i.e. 168], 105 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">William Hall</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Roger Iackson</persName>, and are to bee sold at <placeName>his shop, neere the Conduit in Fleet-street</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1610.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Editor's dedication signed: Iohn Winston.</note>
      <note>A variant of the edition with imprint date 1610.</note>
      <note>imperfect; pages 113-114 missing in number only.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Cambridge University Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Roger Iackson</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>William Hall</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop, neere the Conduit in Fleet-street</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
