<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Rams little Dodeon [sic] A briefe epitome of the new herbal, or histoy of plants. Wherein is contayned the disposition and true declaration of the phisike helpes of all sortes of herbes and plants, vnder their names and operations, not onely of those which are here in this our Countrey of England growing but of all others also of other realmes, countreyes and nations vsed in phisike: Collected out of the most exquisite newe herball, or history of plants, first set forth in the Dutch or Almayne tongue, by ... D. Reinbert Dodeon, ... and lately translated into English by Henry Lyte, ... and now collected and abridged by William Ram, Gent. Pandit oliua suos Ramos.</title>
      <title>Cruydenboeck. English. Abridgments</title>
      <author>Dodoens, Rembert, 1517-1585.</author>
      <author>Lyte, Henry, 1529?-1607.</author>
      <author>Ram, William.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[43], 213 [i.e. 229] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">Simon Stafford</persName>, dwelling in <placeName>the Cloth Fayre, at the signe of the three Crownes</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1606">1606.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Extracts of the medical applications, with additions, by William Ram, of a translation of the French translation by Charles de l'Ecluse of: Dodoens, Rembert. Cruydeboeck.</note>
      <note>Numerous errors in pagination; actual pagination derived from signature collation.</note>
      <note>Six leaves of manuscript bound in at end of Cambridge University Library copy include an index and a folded table.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A-C&#8308;, D-R, S&#8308;.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Cambridge University Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Simon Stafford</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Cloth Fayre, at the signe of the three Crownes</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
