<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A remonstrance of the directors of the Netherlands East India Company presented to the Lords States Generall of the vnited Provinces, in defence of the said Companie, touching the bloudy proceedings against the English merchants, executed at Amboyna. Together, with the acts of the processe, against the sayd English. And the reply of the English East India Company, to the said remonstrance and defence. Published by authority.</title>
         <author>Nederlandsche Oost-Indische Compagnie.</author>
         <author>East India Company.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8], 29, [3]; [2], 38; 47, [1] p., plate   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>By John Dawson, for the East India Company,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>Printed at London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1632">1632.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Signatures: A-E&#8308;; &#178; A-E&#8308;; &#179;B-G&#8308;.</note>
         <note>"An authentick copy of the confessions and sentences, against M. Tovverson, and complices .." has separate dated title page, pagination, and register. "A reply to the remonstrance of the bewinthebbers or directors of the Netherlands East-India Companie .." (caption title) has separate pagination and register beginning on &#179;B1.</note>
         <note>&#185;E4 is blank. Variant: &#185;E4 printed as title page, "An authentick copy of the acts of the processe against the English at Amboyna"; original title to part 2 is cancelled. This is the case with all copies of STC 7450a.</note>
         <note>In this edition, &#185;B1r has catchword "afore-"; &#179;B1r last line has "discouerie". Quire &#185;A and part 2 are in the same setting as STC 7450a.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
