<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>My the King. Letters patents, commanding that no greater or other customes, imposts, fees, entrie-siluer, or other dueties whatsoeuer, shalbe hereafter taken, extracted or receiued, by any officers or subiects of England and Ireland, from Scottish-men, or Scottish ships or any goods or merchandizes imported or exported by them or their ships, then is vsually receiued from English and Irish men, English and Irish ships, or any goods imported or exported by them or their ships, to or from England and Ireland, in all respects: and that Scottish ships bee no more reputed or accompted strangers bottomes, but free bottomes, paying no more customes, impositions or other dueties for goods imported, or exported by them, then if they were imported or exported in English or Irish bottomes, to or from England or Ireland.</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Sovereign (1603-1625 : James I)</author>
      <author>James I, King of England, 1566-1625.</author>
      <author>Suffolk, Thomas Howard, Earl of, 1561-1626. aut</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[3] sheets   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">Robert Barker</persName>, printer to <persName type="patron">the Kings most excellent Maiestie</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1615">Anno 1615]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Caption title.</note>
      <note>Addressed to Thomas Howard, Earl of Suffolk and others.</note>
      <note>Dated at end: Westminster the twelfth day of April, in the thirteenth yeere of our reigne ..</note>
      <note>Imprint from colophon.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Robert Barker</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="patron">
      <persName>the Kings most excellent Maiestie</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
