<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>By the King. A proclamation for the preuenting of the exportation of woolles, vvoolle-fels, yarne, fullers earth, and vvoad-ashes, and for the better vent of cloth, and stuffe made of vvooll, within this kingdome</title>
         <title>Proclamations. 1622-07-28</title>
         <author>England and Wales. Sovereign (1603-1625 : James I)</author>
         <author>James I, King of England, 1566-1625.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>3 sheets (versos blank)   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>by Bonham Norton and Iohn Bill, printers to the Kings most excellent Maiestie,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1622">MDC.XXII. [1622]]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>The Privy Council has appointed a committee of twelve to inquire into the decay of the wool trade. They find that the export of wool, wool-fells, year, fuller's earth, and 'woad-ashes' assist foreign makers of cloth. Prohibits the exportation of any of these on pain of Star Chamber and such other, &amp;c. No officer is to allow the exportation of wool, nor to certify that it is landed unless he sees the actual quantity named in the 'cocket' landed. All licences for export of wool are revoked. Blacks and Mournings at Funerals to be made of English woollen cloth. No person to use logwood or 'blockwood' in dyeing. The Wardens of the Dyers to make search. All officers to assist in carrying out this Proclamation. A Commission will be appointed for the furtherance of trade." -- Steele.</note>
         <note>Caption title.</note>
         <note>Dated at end: Otelands, the eight and twentieth day of Iuly, in the twentieth yeere of our reigne ... .</note>
         <note>Imprint from colophon.</note>
         <note>Steele notation: seuerall them, 2)meanes 3)equall and; Arms 12.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the originals in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery (Early English books) and the British Library (Misc. Brit. tracts).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
