<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The badges of Christianity. Or, A treatise of the sacraments fully declared out of the word of God Wherein the truth it selfe is proued, the doctrine of the reformed churches maintained, and the errors of the churches of Rome are euidently conuinced: by pervsing wherof the discreet reader may easily perceiue, the weak and vnstable grounds of the Roman religion, and the iust causes of our lawfull separation. Diuided into three bookes: 1. Of the sacraments in generall. 2. Of Baptisme. 3. Of the Lords Supper. Hereunto is annexed a corollarie or necessary aduertisement, shewing the intention of this present worke, opening the differences among vs about the question of the supper, discouering the idolatry and diuisions of the popish clergy, ... By William Attersoll, minister of the Word of God.</title>
         <author>Attersoll, William, d. 1640.</author>
         <author>Attersoll, William, d. 1640. Principles of Christian religion. aut</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[22], 395 [i.e. 392], [52] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by W. Iaggard, dwelling in Barbican,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1606">1606.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>In three books, each with caption title.</note>
         <note>Includes, with caption title: "The principles of Christian religion, set downe in questions and answers, shortly for the remembrance, and plainely for the vnderstanding of all persons, requisite to be learned and knowne before they be admitted to the Lords Supper", also published separately as STC 899.</note>
         <note>Page 392, final numbered page, misnumbered 395.</note>
         <note>Some print show-through; some pages marked and stained.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
