<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Certaine statutes especially selected, and commanded by his Maiestie to be carefully put in execution by all iustices, and other officers of the peace throughout the realme with his Maiesties proclamation for further direction for executing the same. Also certaine orders thought meete by his Maiestie and his Priuie Counsell, to bee put in execution, together with sundry good rules, preseruatiues, and medicines against the infection of the plague, set downe by the Colledge of the Physicians vpon his Maiesties speciall command: as also a decree of the Starre-Chamber, concerning buildings and in-mates.</title>
         <title>Laws, etc.</title>
         <author>England and Wales.</author>
         <author>England and Wales. Sovereign (1625-1649 : Charles I)</author>
         <author>Royal College of Physicians of London.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[148] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by Robert Barker and Iohn Bill, printers to Kings [sic] most excellent Maiestie,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1630">Anno Dom. M.DC.XXX. [1630]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Includes the proclamation of 23 April 1630.</note>
         <note>Signatures: pi&#8308; A&#8308; [par.]A&#8308; B-Q&#8308; R&#178; . Variant: mostly composed of a reissue or reimposition of sheets or pages from "Foure statutes, specially selected and commanded by his Majestie to be carefully put in execution by all justices and other officers of the peace throughout the realme" (STC 9341); collation pi&#8308; A&#8308;, "A5", B-I&#8308;, K1-2, K2-N4, M1-N3, P&#8308; Q&#178; ; pagination [18], 68, [16], 85-95, [1], 107-117, [1] p. For derivation of all sheets of this see STC.</note>
         <note>Reproductions of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery and Bodleian Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
