<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The amours of Messalina, late queen of Albion in which are briefly couch'd secrets of the imposture of the Cambrion prince, the Gothick league, and other court intrigues of the four last years reign, not yet made publick / by a woman of quality, a late confident of Q. Messalina.</title>
      <author>Woman of quality, fl. 1689-1690.</author>
      <author>Leti, Gregorio, 1630-1701.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>34, 4, 42 [i.e. 32], 55 [i.e. 63] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">John Lyford</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London:</pubPlace>
      <date when="1689">1689.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A satire on Mary of Modena, Queen consort of James II.  Cf. pt. 4, p. [32].</note>
      <note>Purported to be a translation from a French work printed in Cologne under title Les amours de Messalina, derni&#232;re reine d'Albion (pt. 1, p. [4]); the French work, however, states that it is "traduit de l'anglais."  Cf. Graesse.</note>
      <note>French original attributed to Gregorio Leti.  Cf. J.M. Qu&#233;rard, Supercheries litt&#233;raires d&#233;voill&#233;s, t. 3, p. 84.</note>
      <note>Part 2 has title: The second part of The amours of Messalina, late Queen of Albion : wherein the secret court intrigues of the four last years reign are further pursued, particularly the imposture of the child.  Part 3 has title: The third part of The amours of Messalina : wherein the secret intrigues of the four last years reign are compleated and the love adventures of Polydorus, King of the Gauls, and the late Queen of Albion, made publick.  Part 4 has title: The amours of the French king with the late Queen of Albion : being the fourth and last part of the history of Messalina.</note>
      <note>A so-called second volume, treating the same material in briefer form, was published in 1690 under title: The royal wanton : containing the Gallick intriegues [sic] with Lycogenes, late king of Albion, his expedition for Hibernia : being the second volume of The amours of Messalina with Polydorus, K. of the Goths.</note>
      <note>Part 2 appears separately as Wing S2299 on reel 475:15, and part 3 as Wing T912 on reel 478:9.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>John Lyford</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
