<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The bloody assizes, or, A compleat history of the life of George Lord Jefferies, from his birth to this present time ... to which is added Major Holmes's excellent speech, with the dying speeches and prayers of many other eminent Protestants : none of which were ever before publish'd ...</title>
         <author>Bent, James.</author>
         <author>Holmes, Abraham, d. 1685.</author>
         <author>Tutchin, John, 1661?-1707.</author>
         <author>Oates, Titus, 1649-1705.</author>
         <author>Dunton, John, 1659-1733.</author>
         <author>J. S. (John Shirley), fl. 1680-1702.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>70 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for J. Dunton ... :</publisher>
         <publisher>and sold by R. Janeway ...,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1689">1689.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Attributed to James Bent; cf. BM.  According to Halkett &amp; Laing (v. 9, p. 32), the original work was by John Shirley with contributions by Pitts (i.e. John Tutchin) and probably by Titus Oates and John Dunton. Dunton (Life and errours of John Dunton, 1818, v. 1, p. 184-5) mentions that Mr. Shirley wrote Lord Jeffrey's Life; he adds also that Mr. Pitts was, in part, author of The bloody assizes. S. Parks (John Dunton and the English book trade, 1976, p. 40) states that most writers consider James Bent to be the pseud. of John Dunton. Since Dunton has already attributed the authorship of The bloody assizes to Shirley and Pitts, it is most probable that James Bent (Dunton) and Titus Oates were only minor contributors to this work.</note>
         <note>"A poem to the memory of George Lord Jefferies," by John Carter: p. [5]-[8]</note>
         <note>Advertisement  on p. 70.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in Union Theological Seminary Library, New York.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
