<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A book of the continuation of forreign passages That is, of the peace made between this Common-wealth, &amp; that of the united Provinces of the Netherlands, with all the articles of that peace. Apr. 5. 1654. And the articles of peace, friendship and entercourse agreed between England and Sweden, in a treaty at Usall. May 9. 1654. As also the substance of the articles of the treaty of peace betwixt England and France. Given at White Hall the 20 of Novemb: 1655. From Generall Blakes fleet, the Turks in Argier do consent to deliver up all the English slaves, and desire a firme peace for ever: and in Tunnis road we battered their castle of Porta-ferina, and set on fire their fleet in the harbour. Apr. 9. 1655. Moreover, an attempt on the island of Jamaica, and taking the town of St. Jago de la viga, beating the enemy from their forts and ordnance, being a body of 3000 men, and so took possession of the island, May 10 1655. With a full description thereof. With a true narrative of the late successe ... against the King of Spains West India </title>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 60+ : ill., port., map (metalcuts)  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">M.S.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Jenner</persName> at <placeName>the south entrance of the Royall Exhange</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1657">1657.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Copy has print show-through; lacks all after p. 60.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Harvard University Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Jenner</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>M.S.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the south entrance of the Royall Exhange</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
