<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The history of the Turkish War with the Rhodians, Venetians, Egyptians, Persians, and other nations being a compact series of the memorable battels, sieges, and progress of the Ottoman armies in Europe, Asia, and Africa, for near an hundred years, with their various success by sea and land : but a relation more particularly of the first bloody siege of Rhodes in the reign of Mahomet the Great ... and the last under the command of Solyman the Magnificent, who ... totally subdued that famous city and island, defended by the valour of the renowned Peter Aubusson ... / written by Will. Caoursin and Rhodgia Afendy.</title>
      <author>Caoursin, Guillaume, d. 1501.</author>
      <author>Sinan Pa&#351;a, 1440-1486.</author>
      <author>Bouhours, Dominique, 1628-1702.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[6], 506 [i.e. 509] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Will. Whitwood, next to the George Inn</persName> in <placeName>Little Brittain</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1683">1683.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Formerly identified as Wing C464 (number cancelled); Wing (2nd ed., 1994) attributes this work to Dominique Bouhours and assigns number B3824D.</note>
      <note>Reissue with new title page of Wing B3827 The Life of the Renowned Peter D'Aubisson.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of originals in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery and British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Will. Whitwood, next to the George Inn</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Little Brittain</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
