<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A Collection of papers relating to the present juncture of affairs in England</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <editionStmt>
      <edition>The third edition.</edition>
    </editionStmt>
    <extent>34 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed and are to be sold by <persName type="printer"><persName type="bookseller">Richard Janeway</persName></persName> ...,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1689">1689.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>First in a series of 12 collections issued in 1688-1689 under title: A collection of papers relating to the present juncture of affairs in England; and reissued in 1689 under title: A compleat collection of papers, in twelve parts, relating to the great revolutions in England and Scotland.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Harvard University Library.</note>
      <note>The humble petition of seven bishops to His Majesty -- Articles recommended by the Archbishop of Canterbury -- Proposals of the Archbishop, with some other bishops to His Majesty -- Petition of the lords spiritual and temporal for calling a free Parliament : with His Majesty's gracious answer --Vindication of the aforesaid petition -- Extract of the States General, their resolution -- The Prince of Orange, his letter to the English army -- Account of a design to poison the Prince of Orange before he came out of Holland -- A relation of a strange meteor, representing a crown of light, seen in the air near the city of Orange -- Lord Delamere's speech to his tenants -- The Prince of Denmark's letter to the King -- The Lord Churchil's letter to the King --Princess Anne's letter to the Queen -- A memorial of the Protestants of England to the Prince and Princess of Orange -- Prince of Orange, his declaration of Novemb. 28, 1688 for Sherborn Castle.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Richard Janeway</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Richard Janeway</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
