<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>England's interest asserted, in the improvement of its native commodities; and more especially the manufacture of wool plainly shewing its exportation un-manufactured, amounting unto millions of loss to His Majesty, and kingdom. With some brief observations of that worthy author Sir Walter Rawley, touching the same. All humbly presented to His Majesty, and both Houses of Parliament. By a true lover of His Majesty, and native country. Licensed by Roger L'estrange.</title>
      <title>Englands glory.</title>
      <author>Carter, W. (William)</author>
      <author>Raleigh, Walter, Sir, 1552?-1618.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 34, 13-36 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">Francis Smith</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>the Elephant</placeName> and Castle without Temple-Bar; and by <persName type="publisher">Henry Mortlock</persName> at <placeName>the White Horse in Westminster-Hall</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1669.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A true lover of His Majesty = William Carter.</note>
      <note>A reissue, with added title page and quires &#178; C-&#178; E, and with colophon (&#185;B2) cancelled, of the 1669 edition of: Englands glory.</note>
      <note>Formerly Wing C674.</note>
      <note>"Some collections of Sir Walter Rawleys presented to King James, taken out of his remains, discovering Englands loss for want of due improvement of its native commodities" has caption title; pagination begins with 13, and register begins with &#178; C1.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Francis Smith</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Henry Mortlock</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Elephant</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the White Horse in Westminster-Hall</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
