<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Lex custumaria, or, A treatise of copy-hold estates in respect of the lord, copy-holder wherein the nature of customs in general, and of particular customs, grants and surrenders, and their constructions and expositions in reference to the thing granted or surrendred, and the uses or limitations of estates are clearly illustrated : admittances, presentments, fines and forfeitures are fully handled, and many quaeries and difficulties by late resolution setled : leases, licences, extinquishments of copy-hold estates, and what statutes extend to copy-hold estates are explained : and also of actions by lord or tenant, and the manner of declaring and pleading, either generally or as to particular customs, with tryal and evidence holder may recieve relief in the Court of Chancery : to which are annexed presidents of conveyances respecting copy-holds, releases, surrenders, grants presentmets, and the like : as also presidents of court rolls, surrenders, admittances, presentments, &amp;c. / by S.C., Barister at Law.</title>
      <author>Carter, Samuel, barrister at law.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[24], 384, [24] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by the assigns of <persName type="assigns">Richard</persName> and <persName type="assigns">Edward Atkins</persName> ... for <persName type="publisher">John Walthoe</persName> and are to be sold in <placeName>his shop</placeName> ...,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1696">1696.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Written by Samuel Carter.  Cf. BM.</note>
      <note>Advertisements on p. [2] at beginning and p. [21-24] at end.</note>
      <note>Includes index.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in Huntington Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>John Walthoe</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="assigns">
      <persName>Edward Atkins</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="assigns">
      <persName>Richard</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
