<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Art and nature joyn hand in hand. Or, The poor mans daily companion Wherein is shew'd for two pence charge, how you may cure any distempers incident to humane bodys: as first, the magical and physical vertues of beasts and birds, of trees and herbs, ... for curing of most diseases astrologically; a brief treatise of urines, as well of mens as of womens, to judge by the colour ... also a charme to know whether the sick party shall live or die; also to cure the Kings evil, ... against wry-necks, quartane agues, for one that cannot make water; how to make the true antidote powder called, the orvietane of Rome: to take away pearls, and films from the eyes; elixir vit&#230;, or, elixir of life, Gascoynes powder, the royal styptich water, which stops blood in an instant, also good for watery eyes, rheumatick eyes, inflamations in your eyes, pin, or web, and strengthens them to admiration; with many other things worthy of note. By John Durant, student in physick...</title>
      <author>Durant, John, student in physick.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">Sam. Clark</persName>, in <placeName>George-yard, in Lombard-street</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1697">1697.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the British Library, London, England.</note>
      <note>With a final advertisement leaf.</note>
      <note>Print show-through; title page stained and mutilated with some loss of print.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Sam. Clark</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>George-yard, in Lombard-street</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
