<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>An exact table of fees, of all the courts at Westminster, as they were delivered in Parliament by the persons following. Viz. The chancery, by Sir Miles Cook, Samuel Keck, Esquire, and others. The Kings-bench, on the plea-side, by W. Turbill and Nicholas Harding. On the Crown side, by R. Seyhard, and Richard Horton. The common-pleas, by W. Farmerie, Silv. Petyt, and H. Clift. The Exchequer, on the plea-side, by R. Beresford Tho. Arden, &amp;c. On the inquiry-side, by Butler Buggins, Esq; the second edition, corrected. With the additions of the fees of the clerks of the peace of Middlesex and Surrey, the clerk of the assize of the home circuit, the fees of the cursitors, and the abstract of the Act of vellum and parchment, &amp;c.</title>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8], 116, [4], 24, 16 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by the assigns of Richard and Edward Atkins, Esquires; for John Walthoe, at his shop in Vine-Court Middle-Temple,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1694">M DC XCIV. [1694]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Order to print dated 14 November 1693.</note>
         <note>The words "The chancery, .. Butler Buggins, Esq;" are bracketed together on title page.</note>
         <note>With two preliminary contents leaves, and two advertisement leaves bound before "A table of fees now taken".</note>
         <note>"A table of fees now taken, and which have been anciently taken in the office of the clerk of the peace and goal delivery of the county of Middlesex" has caption title, separate register and pagination.</note>
         <note>"An abstract of the Act made in the 5th and 6th years of Their Majesties reign, for granting to Their Majesties several duties upon vellum, parchment, and paper, for four years, towards carrying on the war against France" (also published separately as Wing (2nd ed., 1994) E960) has separate dated title page, register and pagination.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
