<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Eleventh collection of papers relating to the present juncture of affairs in England and Scotland</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 34 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller"><persName type="printer">Richard Janeway</persName></persName> ...,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1689.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Eleventh in a series of 12 collections issued in 1688-1689 under title: A collection of papers relating to the present juncture of affairs in England; and reissued in 1689 under title: A compleat collection of papers, in twelve parts, relating to the great revolutions in England and Scotland.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Huntington Library.</note>
      <note>(from t.p.) I. An answer to the desertion discuss'd, being a defence of the late and present proceedings -- II. Satisfaction tendred to all that pretend conscience for non-submission to our present governours, and refusing of the new oaths of fealty and allegiance -- III. Dr. Oates his petition to the Parliament, declaring his barbarous sufferings by the papists -- IV. An account of the Convention of Scotland -- V. A speech made by a member of the Convention of the Estates in Scotland -- VI. The grounds on which the Estates of Scotland declared the right of the crown of Scotland forfaulted, and the throne become vacant -- VII. The opinion of two eminent Parliament-men, justifying the lawfulness of taking oaths of allegiance to King William and Queen Mary.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Richard Janeway</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Richard Janeway</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
