<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Three letters, from the Right Honourable Sir Thomas Fairfax, Lieut. Gen. Crumwell and the committee residing in the army. Wherein all the particulars of the great victory obtained by our forces against His Majesties, is fully related, fought the 14 of Iune, 1645. With a list of the names of such colonels, captaines, lieutenants, ensignes, and other officers, both of horse and foot there taken prisoners. And the resolution of both Houses upon the same. Die Lun&#230;, 16 Iune, 1645. Ordered by the Lords and Commons assembled in Parliament, that these letters, with the list of the prisoners, be forthwith printed and published, with the order of both Houses concerning the same. Io. Brown. Cler. Parliament.</title>
      <author>Fairfax, Thomas Fairfax, Baron, 1612-1671.</author>
      <author>Cromwell, Oliver, 1599-1658.</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament. House of Commons.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 10 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Iohn Wright</persName> at <placeName>the signe of the Kings-head in the Old-baily.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1645">1645.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: on title page, after 'Crumwell': "wch is a false letter in ye conclusion of it"; "June 17th"; on page 3: text is circled beginning with 'Honest men served you faithfully ..', and annotated "all this is added and not his owne" [Thomason was wrong; the conclusion is Cromwell's. See Abbott, "Writings and speeches of Oliver Cromwell", v.1, p.360; for letter without conclusion see "An ordinance of the Lords and Commons assembled in Parliament" (Wing E2072)].</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Iohn Wright</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the signe of the Kings-head in the Old-baily.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
