<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Instruction concerning penance and holy communion the second part fo the instruction of youth, containing the means how we may return to God by penance, and remain in his grace by the good and frequent use of the sacraments. By Charles Gobinet, Doctor of Divinity, of the house and Society of Sorbon, principal of the college of Plessis-Sorbon.</title>
      <title>Instruction de la jeunesse en la pi&#233;t&#233; chr&#233;tienne. Part 2. English</title>
      <author>Gobinet, Charles, 1614-1690.</author>
      <author>Gobinet, Charles, 1614-1690. Instruction sur la p&#233;nitence et sur la sainte communion. English.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <editionStmt>
      <edition>The last edition in French; new render'd into English.</edition>
    </editionStmt>
    <extent>[20], 396, [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">J.B.</persName> and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Mathew Turner</persName>, at <placeName>the Lamb in High Holborn</placeName>, and <persName type="bookseller">John Tootell</persName>, at <placeName>Mr. Palmers the bookbinder in Silverstreet in Bloomsbury: together with the first part of the instruction of youth in Christian Piety</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1689">1689.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"The instruction of youth in Christian piety" is an English translation of: Gobinet, Charles.  Instruction de la jeunesse en la pi&#233;t&#233; chr&#233;tienne.</note>
      <note>Originally published in French as: Instruction sur la p&#233;nitence et sur la sainte communion.</note>
      <note>With a final advertisment leaf.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>J.B.</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>John Tootell</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Mathew Turner</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Mr. Palmers the bookbinder in Silverstreet in Bloomsbury: together with the first part of the instruction of youth in Christian Piety</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Lamb in High Holborn</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
