<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Gods justice against murther, or The bloudy apprentice executed Being an exact and true relation of a bloudy murther committed by one Thomas Savage an apprentice to a vinter at the ship tavern in Ratliffe upon the maid of the house his fellow servant, being deluded thereunto by the instigations of a whore. How and in what sort he performed the same, how he robbed his master, and was persued and taken by hue and cry at Coome farm betwixt Greenwich and VVoolwich. Sent to Newgate, afterwards arrained and cast at Justice Hall in the Old Bayly, condemned to be hanged over against the place where he committed the fact, and being once hanged and cut down afterwards reviving again, was the second time hanged till he was dead, on Wednesday October 28 1668.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[3], 13 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">John Clarke</persName> at <placeName>the Harp</placeName> and Bible in <placeName>West Smith-Field</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1668">[1668]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Date of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>With a frontispiece woodcut.</note>
      <note>Text begins on verso of title page, [A]2.</note>
      <note>"Thomas Savage the principal in the murther, according to the sentence aforesaid was Wednesday, October the 28 conveyed in a cart from Newgate to the place of execution appointed for him, being over against his master's house, at the sign of the ship in Ratcliff-cross, ..".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>John Clarke</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>West Smith-Field</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Harp</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
