<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A seasonable vindication of the supream authority and jurisdiction of Christian kings, lords, parliaments, as well over the possessions as persons of delinquent prelates and churchmen, or, An antient disputation of the famous Bohemian martyr John Hus, in justification of John Wickliffs 17 article proving by 43 arguments taken out of fathers, canonists, school-men, the supream authority and jurisidiction of princes, parliaments, temporal lords, and other lay-men, who have endowed the church with temporalities, to take away and alien the temporal lands and possessions of delinquent bishops, abbots and church-men, by way of medicine or punishment, without any sacrilege, impiety or injustice : transcribed out of the printed works of Iohn Hus, and Mr. Iohn Fox his acts and monuments printed London 1641, vol. I, p. 585, &amp;c : with an additional appendix thereunto of proofs and domestick presidents in all ages, usefull for present and future times / by William Prynne ...</title>
      <title>Determinatio de ablatione temporalium a clericis. English</title>
      <author>Hus, Jan, 1369?-1415.</author>
      <author>Foxe, John, 1516-1587. Actes and monuments.</author>
      <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8], 118 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">T. Childe</persName>, and <persName type="printer">L. Parry</persName>, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Edward Thomas</persName> ...,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1660.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"The second disputation in the University of Prague, upon the seventeenth article of John Wickliffe," p. 3-37, is a translation, taken in part from the 1641 edition of John Foxe's "Actes and monuments", of Hus' "De ablatione temporalium a clericis determinatio."</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in Thomason Collection, British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Edward Thomas</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>L. Parry</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>T. Childe</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
