<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Clavis apocalyptica, or, A prophetical key by which the great mysteries in the revelation of St. John and the prophet Daniel are opened : it beeing made apparent that the prophetical numbers com to an end with the year of our Lord, 1655 : in two treatises: 1. Shewing what in these our times hath been fulfilled, 2. At this present is effectually brought to pass, 3. And henceforth is to bee expected in the year neer at hand : with an introductorie preface / written by a Germane D. ; and now translated out of High-Dutch.</title>
      <author>Hartlib, Samuel, d. 1662.</author>
      <author>Dury, John, 1596-1680.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[6], 79, [3], 163, [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">William Du-Gard</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Matthewes</persName>, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Giles Calvert</persName> ...,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1651">1651.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Based on the Clavis apocalyptica of Joseph Mede - cf. preface.</note>
      <note>Epistole dedicatory addressed : "To the Right Honourable Oliver St-John, Lord Chief Justice of the Court of Common-Pleas."</note>
      <note>Includes: "An epistolical discours from Mr. John Durie to Mr. Sam. Hartlib, concerning this exposition of the revelation, by way of preface thereunto."</note>
      <note>Includes: "A list of things which are shortly to com to pass, collected out of the XI and XVI chapters of the Revelation."</note>
      <note>Includes: Apocalypsis reserata, or, the revelation of St. John opened ..., with special t.p.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Harvard University Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Matthewes</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>William Du-Gard</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Giles Calvert</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
