<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The wonderful, and most deplorable history of the latter times of the Jews with the destruction of the city of Jerusalem. Which history begins where the Holy Scriptures do end. By Josephus Ben Gorion whereunto is added a brief of the ten captivities; with the pourtrait of the Roman rams, and engines of battery, &amp;c. As also of Jerusalem; with the fearful, and presaging apparitions that were seen in the air before her ruins. Moreover, there is a parallel of the late times and crimes in London, with those in Jerusalem.</title>
      <title>Josippon. English. Abridgments.</title>
      <author>Joseph ben Gorion, ha-Kohen, attributed name.</author>
      <author>Howell, James, 1594?-1666.</author>
      <author>Ibn Daud, Abraham ben David, Halevi, ca. 1110-ca. 1180.</author>
      <author>Fuller, Thomas, 1608-1661.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[18], 272, 269-376, [12] p., 3 leaves of plates : ports.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">John Sims</persName>, at <placeName>the sign of the Kings head at Sweethings Alley end in Cornhil, next the Royal Exchange</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1671">1671.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of Abraham ben David, ha-Levi's abstract, in book 3 of his "Sefer ha-Kabalah", of the anonymous "Josippon" or "Yosippon". The latter has been misattributed to a Joseph ben Gorion, usually identified with Joseph ben Gorion ha-Kohen but occasionally with Flavius Josephus.</note>
      <note>Dedication to the City of London signed: James Howel.</note>
      <note>Dedication to Sir John Robinson signed: J.S.</note>
      <note>The portrait of Josephus Ben-Gorion is signed: W Sherwin fe.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: The wars of the Jews.</note>
      <note>Quire 2C contains a character of the Jews, and a prayer by Thomas Fuller.</note>
      <note>Includes index.</note>
      <note>Text continuous despite pagination.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Cambridge University Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>John Sims</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the sign of the Kings head at Sweethings Alley end in Cornhil, next the Royal Exchange</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
