<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Usury stated overthrown: or, usuries champions with their auxiliaries, shamefully disarmed and beaten by an answer to its chief champion, which lately apeared in print to defend it. And Godliness epitomized by Christopher Jelinger, M.A. Beza upon Matth. May a man with a safe conscience lend upon usury? No surely. And holy Usher, Arch-Bishop of Armagh, in his Body of divinity, pag. 300. Q. What is that which we call usury? It is lending in expectation of certain gain. So he well stateth it against usury ill stated by T. P. Q. What do you think of it? If we speak of that properly, which the scripture condemneth, it is a most wicked and unlawful contract; which if we live and die in, without repentance, we are excluded out of the Kingdom of Heaven. Psal. 15.1,5. Ezek. 18.12,13. and chap. 22. But there is much questioning, which is that usury which the scripture  condemneth. Therefore it will be our wisdom wholly to forbear it, and not to put our souls, which are of more value than the whole world, upon nice discourses, and subtil distinctions. Thus this holy man.</title>
      <author>Jelinger, Christopher.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[30], 242, 161-285, [3] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">J. Wright</persName>, at <placeName>the Crown on Ludgate-Hill</placeName>, and <persName type="publisher">J. Sampson, next the Wonder-Tavern</persName> in <placeName>Ludgate-Street</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1679" cert="low">[1679?]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A reply to: T. P.'s "Usury stated" of 1679, which in turn was an attack on Jelinger's original treatise against usury, "Usury cast", published in 1676 as part of his "Three treatises". Cf. Wing P122 and Wing J547.</note>
      <note>Publication date conjectured by Wing.</note>
      <note>Last leaf blank.</note>
      <note>With an index, pp. 277-283.</note>
      <note>Lacking signatures S-Z; text apparently complete.</note>
      <note>Copy cataloged mis-printed: p. 283 between pp. 281-282.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Goldsmith's Company Library, University of London.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>J. Sampson, next the Wonder-Tavern</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>J. Wright</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Ludgate-Street</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Crown on Ludgate-Hill</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
