<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>An astrological speculation of the late prodigy. Or A clear discovery of the approaching miseries signified by that comet, or blazing star which hath so long been visible, to several countries and nations in November, December and January; in the year 1680. Being a full account of the manner or nature of its effects, and in what countries they'l be exhibited. Also the true way of judging the effects, of all other comets, and such apparitions, carefully collected from the best experimental judgments of the choicest aphorisms, and according to their fundamental, and methodical rules; now in a seasonable time manifested in a plain and homely stile; fit for the understanding of mean capacities. By Thomas Jones a lover of learning, and student in astrology; &amp; autodidactus.</title>
      <author>Jones, Thomas, 1648-1713.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[6], 10 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">the author</persName>, and are sold by <persName type="bookseller">him</persName>, in <placeName>Pauls Alley, in Redcross-Street</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1681">1681.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Caption title on p. 1: To know the significations or effects of comets or blazing stars by those following rules of art viz. ..</note>
      <note>With "Advertisements" for Jones's Welch almanacs on pp. 8-10.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in St. Davids University College Library, Lampeter, Wales.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>the author</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>him</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Pauls Alley, in Redcross-Street</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
