<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A list of both houses of Parliament summoned by his Majesty King James the second, to meet at Westminster the nineteenth day of May, 1685. In the first year of his Majesties reign. Note that such noble-men before whom this mark (*) is prefixt, are knights of the most noble Order of the Garter. That the Archbishop of Canterbury takes place next to the princes of the blood. That the Archbishop of York takes place above all the nobility and officers, except that the Lord Keeper. That the rest of the bishops take place next to the viscounts, and above temporal barons: whereof the bishops of London, Durham, and Winchester, do always precede the other bishops; the rest taking place according to the seniority of their consecrations. That the noble-men under age sit not in the House of Lords, unless called by his Majesties writ. That such of the Commons as have this mark () after them were members of the last Parliament.</title>
      <title>Lists. 1685.</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>1 sheet ([1] page)   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">A. Green</persName>, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">most booksellers</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1685">1685.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Caption title.</note>
      <note>In title the words "Note that noble-men before whom this mark (*) is prefixt, are knights of the most noble Order of the Garter" and the words "That the noble-men under age sit not in the House of Lords, unless called by his Majesties writ." are bracketed together on title page.  The last bracket is reversed.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Harvard University Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>A. Green</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>most booksellers</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
