<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A Leicester-shire frolick; or, The valiant cook-maid Being a merry composed jest of five taylors that had been at work till their wages came to 5 pounds; likewise a merry conceited cook-maid that lived in the house, went to her master and desired him to lend her a horse, and she would venture her skill to take the 5-pound from these five taylors, without either sword or pistol, in a jesting way, to make her master some sport and to show her valour: her master loving mirth more then sadness, agreed to it: so a horse was sadled, and other things to disguise her self, because she might not be known: away she went (it being in the evening) and met them before they got home, with nothing in her hand but a black pudding, the faint-hearted taylors delivered her their money very quietly, for fear they should a been shot through with a black pudding, and what followed after is expressed in this following ditty. Tune is, Ragged and torn. With allowance.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>1 sheet ([1] p.) : ill. (woodcut)  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">P. Brooksby</persName>, at <placeName>the Golden-Ball, in Pye-Corner, near West-smithfield</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1680" cert="low">[1680?]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Place of publication and suggested date of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>Verses in black letter; chorus lines in roman.</note>
      <note>Printed in four columns with a woodcut at head of first column of text.</note>
      <note>Verse - "I'lle tell you a pretty fine jest;".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>P. Brooksby</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Golden-Ball, in Pye-Corner, near West-smithfield</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
