<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Tutela sanitatis sive Vita protracta The protection of long life, and detection of its brevity, from di&#230;tic causes and common cutoms. Hygiastic pr&#230;cautions and rules appropriate to the constitutions of bodyes; and various discrasyes or passions of minde; dayly to be observed for the preservation of health and prolougation of life. With a treatise of fontinells or issues. Whereunto is annexed Bellum necessarium sive Medicus belligerans the military or practical physitian reveiwing [sic] his armory: furnished with medical weapons munition against the secret invaders of life; fitted for all persons and assaults; with their safe and regular use, according to medical art and discipline by Everard Maynwaring doctor in physick.</title>
      <author>Maynwaringe, Everard, 1628-1699?</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[28], 120 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">Peter Lillicrap. And</persName> sold by <persName type="bookseller">S. Thompson stationer</persName> at <placeName>the Bishops head in St. Pauls Church-yard: T. Basset stationer under St. Dunstans Church in Fleet-street</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1664">1664.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Imperfect; as filmed Bodleian Library copy only includes title page and final leaves.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the British Library and in the Bodleian Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Peter Lillicrap. And</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>S. Thompson stationer</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Bishops head in St. Pauls Church-yard: T. Basset stationer under St. Dunstans Church in Fleet-street</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
