<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Auctio Millingtoniana picturarum omnigenarum, &amp;c. A collection of extraordinary paintings &amp; limnings with variety of the finest Italian, French, and other prints, (several of them originals) by the best masters. With many curiosities of the China make, and other artificial rarities. Will be sold by auction, for the diversion and entertainment of the gentlemen, ladies, &amp;c. at Tunbridge-Wells, at the auction coffee-house, by the Lower Walks, near the Wells, on Thursday the 13th of this instant August, 1691. the sale beginning in the morning at eight, and continues till twelve in the forenoon) except Prayer-time.) By Edward Millington.</title>
      <author>Millington, Edward, d. 1703.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 2+ p   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Catalogues of the paintings and limnings, &amp;c. are given to all gentlemen, ladies, &amp;c. at <placeName>Mr. Pett's</placeName>, <placeName>Mr. Brett's</placeName>, <placeName>Mr. Westley's</placeName>, <placeName>Apothecaries; at Mr. Samuel Rose's shop, over against the music on the walks, at Mr. Thompsons's tavern near the walks</placeName>, and at <placeName>the above mentioned auction coffee house the place of sale</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date>1691.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Place of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>Imperfect. L copy incomplete with catchword "132AN" on p.2.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original at the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Apothecaries; at Mr. Samuel Rose's shop, over against the music on the walks, at Mr. Thompsons's tavern near the walks</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Mr. Brett's</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Mr. Pett's</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Mr. Westley's</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the above mentioned auction coffee house the place of sale</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
