<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Remarkable addresses by way of embassy from the East-India Company of the United Provinces, to the Emperor of Japan Containing a description of their several territories, cities, temples, and fortresses; their religions, laws, and customs; their prodigious vvealth, and gorgeous habits; the nature of their soil, plants, beasts, hills, rivers, and fountains: with the character of the ancient and modern Japanners. Collected out of their several writings and journals by Arnoldus Montanus. English'd, and adorn'd with a hundred several sculptures, by John Ogilby Esq; His Majesties cosmographer, geographick printer, and master of the revels in the Kingdom of Ireland.</title>
         <title>Gedenkwaerdige gesantschappen der Oost-Indische maatschappy in 't Vereenigde Nederland, aan de Kaiseren van Japan. English.</title>
         <author>Montanus, Arnoldus, 1625?-1683.</author>
         <author>Ogilby, John, 1600-1676.</author>
         <author>Nederlandsche Oost-Indische Compagnie.</author>
         <author>United Provinces of the Netherlands.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 488 p., [25] leaves of plated (folded) : ill., map  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by the author, and are to be had at his House in White Fryers,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>M. DC. LXXI. [1671]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>An English translation, by John Ogilby, of: Gedenkwaerdige gesantschappen der Oost-Indische maatschappy in 't Vereenigde Nederland, aan de Kaiseren van Japan.</note>
         <note>With engraved frontispiece, and engraved illustrations throughout.</note>
         <note>Title page printed in red and black.</note>
         <note>Caption title on p. 1 reads: A memorable embassy to the emperor of Japan.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Magdalen College Library, Oxford.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
