<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The commentaries of Messire Blaize de Montluc, mareschal of France wherein are describ'd all the combats, rencounters, skirmishes, battels, sieges, assaults, scalado's, the taking and surprizes of towns and fortresses, as also the defences of the assaulted and besieg'd : with several other signal and remarkable feats of war, wherein this great and renowned warriour was personally engag'd, in the space of fifty or threescore years that he bore arms under several kings of France : together with divers instructions, that such ought not to be ignorant of, as propose to themselves by the practice of arms to arrive at any eminent degree of honor, and prudently to carry on all the exploits of war.</title>
         <title>Commentaires de messire Blaise de Monluc. English. 1674</title>
         <author>Monluc, Blaise, seigneur de, 1500?-1577.</author>
         <author>Cotton, Charles, 1630-1687.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[18], 404 [i.e. 400], [12] p., [1] leaf of plates : port.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by Andrew Clark for Henry Brome ...,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>MDCLXXIV [1674]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Translation of the author's Commentaires de messire Blaise de Monluc.</note>
         <note>Translated by Charles Cotton. Cf. NUC pre-1956 imprints.</note>
         <note>Dedicatory poems by Cotton, Thomas Flatman, and R. Newcourt.</note>
         <note>Blaisii Monluci Franciæ mareschalli tumulus (French, Latin and Greek verse): [12] p. at end.</note>
         <note>Advertisement: p. [18]</note>
         <note>Errors in paging: p. 15, 117 misprinted 17, 107, p. 377-380 omitted in paging only.</note>
         <note>Errata: p. [17]</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the Cambridge University Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
