<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The third volume of letters writ by a Turkish spy who lived five and forty years undiscover'd at Paris : giving an impartial account to the Divan at Constantinople of the most remarkable transactions of Europe, and discovering several intrigues and secrets of the Christian courts (especially of that of France) continued from the year 1645 to the year 1682 / written originally in Arabick, translated into Italian, and from thence into English by the translator of the first volume.</title>
      <author>Marana, Giovanni Paolo, 1642-1693.</author>
      <author>Bradshaw, William, fl. 1700.</author>
      <author>Midgley, Robert, 1655?-1723.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[23], 360 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">J. Leake</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Henry Rhodes</persName> ...,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1691">1691.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>The first edition of this work began publication in 1684 when a volume in Italian entitled "L'esploratore Turco" and a French version entitled "L'esplou du grand seigneur" were published in Paris by C. Barbin. Authorship is disputed, but it is generally agreed that the first fifty letters (the original four volumes) were written by Marana. In the English editions, v. 1 contains the substance of the letters commonly ascribed to Marana. The continuation (i.e. v. 2-8), said to have appeared first in English, has been variously ascribed to Robert Midgley and William Bradshaw; Bradshaw has also been attributed as the translator (from Marana's Italian manuscripts) of the entire work under Dr. Midgley's editorship. cf. DNB; also Gentleman's magazine, 1841, p. 270.</note>
      <note>Engraved frontispiece: "Mahmut the Turkish spy."</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the University of Illinois (Urbana-Champaign Campus). Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Henry Rhodes</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>J. Leake</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
