<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The seaman's companion being a plain guide to the understanding of arithmetick, geometry, trigonometry, navigation, and astronomy. Applied chiefly to navigation: and furnished with a table of meridional parts, to every third minute: with excellent and easie ways of keeping a reckoning at sea, never in print before. Also, a catalogue of the longitude and latitude of the principal places in the world with other useful things. The third edition corrected and amended. By Matthew Norwood, mariner.</title>
      <author>Norwood, Matthew.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[10], 203, [1] p., [1] leaf of folding plate : ill., tables  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>[print]ed by <persName type="printer">Anne Godbid</persName>, and <persName type="printer">John Playford</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">William Fisher</persName>, at <placeName>the Postern-Gate near Tower-Hill; Robert Boulter, at the Turks-Head</placeName> and Ralph Smith, at the Bible in <placeName>Cornhill</placeName>; Thomas Passinger, at the Three Bibles on London-Bridge; and <persName type="publisher">Richard Northcot, next St. Peter's-Alley</persName> in <placeName>Cornhill</placeName>, and at <placeName>the Anchor</placeName> and Mariner, on <placeName>Fishstreet-Hill.</placeName></publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1678">[1678]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>With a table of contents.</note>
      <note>Divisional title on p. 147: A table of meridional parts.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original at the Trinity College Library, Cambridge.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Richard Northcot, next St. Peter's-Alley</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>William Fisher</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Anne Godbid</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>John Playford</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Cornhill</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Fishstreet-Hill.</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Anchor</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Bible in Cornhill; Thomas Passinger, at the Three Bibles on London-Bridge;</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Postern-Gate near Tower-Hill; Robert Boulter, at the Turks-Head</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
