<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The art of gunnery Wherein is described the true way to make all sorts of gunpowder, guu-match [sic], the art of shooting in great and small ordnance: excellent ways to take heights, depths, distances, accessible, or inaccessible, either single or divers distances at one operation: to draw the map or plot of any city, town, castle, or other fortified place. To make divers sorts of artificiall fire-works, both for war and recreation, also to cure all such wounds that are curable, which may chance to happen by gunpowder or fire-works. This treatise is composed for the help of all such gunners and others, that have charge of artillery, and are not well versed in arithmetick and geometry : all the rules and directions in this book, being framed both with and without the help of arithmetick. By Nathanael Nye mathematician, master gunner of the city of Worcester.</title>
      <author>Nye, Nathaniel, b. 1624.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[20], 88, 102 p., [2] leaves of plates : ill., tables, diagrams  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">William Leak</persName>, at <placeName>the signe of the Crown in Fleetstreet, between the two Temple Gates</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1647">1647.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"The art of gunnery. Chap. 38." begins 2nd pagination and register; text is continuous.</note>
      <note>"A treatise of artificiall fire-works for warre and recreation." has separate dated title page on p. [57] second sequence.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Cambridge University Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>William Leak</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the signe of the Crown in Fleetstreet, between the two Temple Gates</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
