<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>New-England's ensigne it being the account of cruelty, the professors pride, and the articles of their faith, signified in characters written in blood, wickedly begun, barbarously continued, and inhumanly finished (so far as they have gone) by the present power of darkness possest in the priests and rulers in New-England ... : this being an account of the sufferings sustained by is in New-England (with the Dutch) the most part of it in these two last yeers, 1657, 1658 : with a letter to Iohn Indicot, Iohn Norton, Governor, and chief priest of Boston, and another to the town of Boston : also, the several late conditions of a friend upon the Road-Iland, before, in, and after distraction : with some qu&#230;ries unto all sorts of people, who want that which we have, &amp;c. / vvritten at sea, by us whom the vvicked in scorn calls Quakers, in the second month of the yeer 1659 ; this being a confirmation of so much as Francis Howgill truly published in his book titled, The Popish inquisition newly erected in New-England, &amp;c.</title>
      <author>Norton, Humphrey, fl. 1655-1659.</author>
      <author>Rous, John, d. 1695.</author>
      <author>Copeland, John, 17th cent.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[3], 120, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">T.L.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">G. Calvert</persName> ...,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1659">1659.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Errata: prelim. p. [1].</note>
      <note>Relates the sufferings of the Quakers in New England.</note>
      <note>Attributed to Humphrey Norton, John Rous and John Copeland. cf. Smith, J. Friends' books.</note>
      <note>Signed: Humphrey Norton, John Rous, John Copeland, Robert Hodgshone, William Newland, Henry Howland, Edward Rawson, Christopher Holder, William Shattuck, Katherine Scot.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in Huntington Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>G. Calvert</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>T.L.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
