<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Matchlesse crueltie declared at large in the ensuing history of the Waldenses apparently manifesting unto the world the horrible persecutions which they have suffered by the papists, for the space of four hundred and fifty years : wherein is related their original and beginning, their piety and purity in religion, both for doctrine and discipline : likewise hereunto is added an exact narrative of the late bloody and barbarous massacres, murders and other unheard of cruelties committed on many thousands of the Protestants dwelling in the valleys of Piedmont, &amp;c. by the Duke of Savoy's forces, joyned with the French army and several bloody Irish regiments / published by command of His Highness the Lord Protector.</title>
      <title>Histoire des Vaudois. English. 1655</title>
      <author>Perrin, J. P. (Jean Paul)</author>
      <author>Stoppa, Giovanni Battista. Collection or narative sent to His Highness the Lord Protector ... concerning the bloody and barbarous massacres and other cruelties.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 66, [2], 144, 143, 103, [17], 43 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Edward Brewster</persName> ...,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1655">1655.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Second part has special t.p. and separate paging: A collection or narative sent to His Highness the Lord Protector ... concerning the bloody and barbarous massacres and other cruelties ... [London] : Printed for H. Robinson ..., 1655.</note>
      <note>"A collection or narative sent to His Highness the Lord Protector ..." was also published separately, and appears as Wing S5768 at reel 752:11.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Huntington Library.</note>
      <note>Includes bibliographical references.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Edward Brewster</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
