<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A relation of the great sufferings and strange adventures of Henry Pitman, chyrurgion to the late Duke of Monmouth, containing an account ...</title>
         <author>Pitman, Henry.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>38 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by Andrew Sowle, and are to be sold by John Taylor ...,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1689">1689.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>"An act for the governing and retaining within this island all such rebels convict as by His most sacred Majesties order or permit, have been or shall be transported from his European dominion to this place," dated: the fourth day of January, 1685, p. 6-11.</note>
         <note>"1. Of the occasion of his being engaged in the Dukes service, 2. Of his tryal, condemnation, and transportation to Barbadoes, with the most severe and unchristian acts made against him and his fellow-sufferers, by the governour and general assembly of that island, 3. How he made his escape in a small open boat with some of his fellow captives, namely Jo. Whicher, Peter Bagwell, William Woodcock, Jo. Cooke, Jeremiah Atkins, &amp;c., and how miraculously they were preserved on the sea, 4. How they went ashore on a uninhabitable island, where they met with some privateers that burnt their boat, and left them on that desolate place to shift for themselves, 5. After what manner they lived there for about three moneths, until the said Henry Pitman was taken aboard a privateer and at length arrived safe in England, 6. How his companions were received aboard another privateer that was afterwards taken by the Spaniards and they all made slaves, and how after six months captivity they were delivered and returned to England also."</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in Huntington Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
