<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Of trade 1. In general. 2. In particular. 3. Domestick. 4. Foreign. 5. The East-India. 6. The African. 7. The Turky. 8. The Spanish. 9. The Hamburgh. 10. The Portugal. 11. The Italian. 12. The Dutch. 13. The Russia. 14. The Greenland. 15. The Swedeland. 16. The Denmark. 17. The Irish. 18. The Scotland. 19. The plantation. 20. The French, &amp;c. Also, of coyn. Bullion. Of improving our woollen manufacture. To prevent exporting wooll. Of ways and means to increase our riches, &amp;c. By J.P. esq; to which is annex'd, the argument of the late Lord Chief Justice Pollexphen, upon an action of the case, brought by the East-India Company against Mr. Sands an interloper.</title>
         <author>Pollexfen, John, b. ca. 1638.</author>
         <author>Pollexfen, Henry, Sir, 1632?-1691. Argument of a learned counsel, upon an action of the case brought by the East-India-Company.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[6], 167, [1], 77, [3] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed for John Baker, near the Kings-Armes in Little Britain,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1700.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>J.P. = John Pollexfen.</note>
         <note>The words "1. In general. .. 10. The Portugal." and "11. The Italian. .. 20. The French, &amp;c." are printed in two columns on title page.</note>
         <note>Includes three preliminary contents pages and errata page.</note>
         <note>Caption title on p. 1: A discourse of trade and coyn.</note>
         <note>Includes a reissue of:  Pollexfen, Henry. The argument of a learned counsel, upon an action of the case brought by the East-India-Company; pagination and register are separate.</note>
         <note>The final three pages contain advertisements for B. Aylmer.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Goldsmiths' Library, University of London.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
