<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The first and second part of the signal loyalty and devotion of Gods true saints and pious Christians (as also of some idolatrous pagans) tovvards their kings, both before and under the law, and Gospel especially in this our island. Expressed in and by their private and publike private loyal supplications, prayers, intercession, thanksgiving, votes, acclamations, salutations, epistles, addresses, benedictions, options of long life, health, wealth, safety, victory, peace, prosperity, all temporal, spiritual, eternal blessings, felicities to their kings persons, families, queens, children, realms, armies, officers, chearfull subjections and dutifull obedience to them: whethe [sic] good, or bad, Christians, or pagans, orthodox, or heterodox, protectors, or persecutors of them. With the true reasons thereof from Scripture and policy. Evidenced by varieties of presidents, testimonies and authorities in al ages, ... Whereunto the several forms, ceremonies, prayers, collects, benedictions and consecrations, used at the coronations of Christian emperors, kings, queens (more particularly in England and Scotland, not formerly published) and of the Mahometan and &#198;gyptian kings, are annexed. By </title>
         <title>Signal loyalty and devotion of Gods true saints and pious Christians, towards their kings.</title>
         <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[10], 96, [4], 321, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by T. Childe, and L. Parry, and are to be sold by Edward Thomas at the Adam and Eve in Little-brittain,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1660">1660.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>"The second part of the signal loyalty" (also published separately as Wing (2nd ed.) P4075) has a separate dated title page, register and pagination.</note>
         <note>Both parts have final errata leaves.</note>
         <note>Imperfect; part 2 lacks pp. 261-262.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
