<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Hell reformed or A glasse for favorits Their falls and complaints also the complaints of princes against their favorits. With the dangerous mischiefes of state politicks, flatterers, suborners, secret accusers, false witnesses, &amp;c. Also the reasons of a devill, why he had rather continue in hell; then returne and live againe on earth. With the acclamations of a testator, for making his will before hee dyed: and his advice to others therein. Also the decree of Lucifer, for reformation. With many other notable passages, worthy observation. Discovered in a vision, by D:F:Q:V: A Spanish knight, of the Order of Saint Iames, and Lord of Ivan-Abad. Published by E:M: gent.</title>
      <title>Infierno enmendado. English.</title>
      <author>Quevedo, Francisco de, 1580-1645.</author>
      <author>Messervy, Edward.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[24], 112 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">E: Griffin</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Simon Burton</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop next the Miter Taverne within Algate</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1641">1641.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>D.F.Q.V. = Francisco de Quevedo; E.M. = Edward Messervy.</note>
      <note>A translation into English by Edward Messervy of Francisco de Quevedos&#768; &#200;l infierno enmendado,&#768; the first Spanish edition of which was published separately in Gerona in 1628, then subsequently added to the other six books of his S&#768;ue&#241;os.&#768;</note>
      <note>Dedication signed: Edvvard Messervy.</note>
      <note>With a preliminary table.</note>
      <note>Marginal notes.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Simon Burton</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>E: Griffin</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop next the Miter Taverne within Algate</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
