<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Synodicon in Gallia reformata, or, The acts, decisions, decrees, and canons of those famous national councils of the reformed churches in France being I. a most faithful and impartial history of the rise, growth, perfection and decay of the reformation in that kingdom, with its fatal catastrophe upon the revocation of the Edict of Nants in the year 1685 : II. the confession of faith and discipline of those churches : III. a collection of speeches, letters, sacred politicks, cases of conscience, and controversies in divinity, determined and resolved by those grave assemblies : IV. many excellent expedients for preventing and healing schisms in the churches and for re-uniting the dismembred body of divided Protestants : V. the laws, government, and maintenance of their colleges, universities and ministers, together with their exercise of discipline upon delinquent ministers and church-members : VI. a record of very many illustrious events of divine providence relating to those churches : the whole collected and composed out of original manuscript acts of those renowned synods : a work never be extant in any language.</title>
      <author>Quick, John, 1636-1706.</author>
      <author>Eglises r&#233;form&#233;es de France.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>2 v.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">T. Parkhurst</persName> and <persName type="publisher">J. Robinson</persName> ...,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1692">1692.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Added title page engraved.</note>
      <note>Vol. 2 has special t.p. with subtitle: The acts, decisions, decrees and canons of the seven last national councils of the reformed churches in France. -- London : Printed by J. Richardson for Thomas Parkhurst and for Jonathan Robinson, 1692.</note>
      <note>Second part of the 2nd vol. has special t.p.: Synodicon in Gallia reformata, or, The acts, canons, decisions, and decrees of the four last national synods of the reformed churches of France. -- London : Printed by J. D. for Thomas Parkhurst and Jonathan Robinson, 1691.</note>
      <note>Volume 2, page 573 has faded print in filmed copy.  Pages 560-85 photographed from Cambridge University Library copy and inserted at end.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in Union Theological Seminary Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>J. Robinson</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>T. Parkhurst</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
