<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A medicinal dispensatory, containing the vvhole body of physick discovering the natures, properties, and vertues of vegetables, minerals, &amp; animals: the manner of compounding medicaments, and the way to administer them. Methodically digested in five books of philosophical and pharmaceutical institutions; three books of physical materials galenical and chymical. Together with a most perfect and absolute pharmacopoea or apothecaries shop. Accommodated with three useful tables. Composed by the illustrious Renodæus, chief physician to the monarch of France; and now Englished and revised, by Richard Tomlinson of London, apothecary.</title>
         <title>Dispensatorium medicum. English</title>
         <author>Renou, Jean de.</author>
         <author>Tomlinson, Richard, Apothecary.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[52], 94, 97-174, 177-216, [8], 217-404, 377-738, [24] p., [1] leaf of plates   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by Jo: Streater and Ja: Cottrel; and are to be sold by Henry Fletcher at the three gilt Cups neer the west-end of Pauls,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1657.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>An English translation, by Richard Tomlinson, of: Renou, Jean de.  Translation of: Dispensatorium medicum.</note>
         <note>Includes index.</note>
         <note>"Three books of medicinal materials" has separate dated title page and register; pagination is more or less continuous.</note>
         <note>"The pharmaceutrical shop" has separate dated title page; register and pagination are continuous.</note>
         <note>Text and register are continuous despite pagination.</note>
         <note>Pagest stained; some print show-through.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
