<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The experienced farrier, or, Farring compleated In two books physical and chyrurgical. Bringing pleasure to the gentleman, and profit to the countrey-man. ... For here is contained every thing that belongs to a true horse-man, groom, farrier or horse-leach, viz. breeding; the manner how, the season when, ... and what are fit for generation; the feeder, rider, keeper, ambler and buyer; as also the making of several precious drinks, suppositories, balls, purgations, ... and directions how to use them for all inward and outward diseases. Also the paring and shooing of all manner of hoofes, ... The prices and vertues of most of the principal drugs, both simple and compound belonging to farring, ... also a large table of the virtues of most simples set down alphabetically, and many hundreds of simples placed one after another, for the cure of all ... diseases, ... with many new receipts of excellent use and value; never yet printed before in any author. By E.R. Gent.</title>
      <author>E. R., Gent.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <editionStmt>
      <edition>The second edition much enlarged and amended, and two new sheets of the prices and virtues of drugs added to the table of drugs, that was not in the former impression, with a caution to the farrier about his buying of them; also one hundred and fifty new receipts, and thirty directions for the physicking of horses, with about two thousand new simples, and an advertisement touching their usefulness; with many other new additions, too tedious here to rehearse.</edition>
    </editionStmt>
    <extent>[16], 418, [40] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">Richard Northcott adjoyning to S. Peters Alley</persName> in <placeName>Cornhill</placeName>, and at <placeName>the Marrier</placeName> and Anchor upon New-Fish street Hill, near <placeName>London-bridge</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1681">1681.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"The second part of The experienced farrier" has a separate title page, dated 1680; with continuous pagination and register.</note>
      <note>With errata on 3L8r and an advertisement on 3L8v.</note>
      <note>Imperfect; print is faded affecting legibility.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Richard Northcott adjoyning to S. Peters Alley</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Cornhill</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>London-bridge</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Marrier</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
