<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A looking-glass for England wherein is shewn God's mercies and judgments on this sinful nation; with an earnest invitation to poor sinners to repentance: wherein is set forth the great folly and madness of forsaking Christ their redeemer, and neglecting the care of their immortal souls, and setting their cares upon the vanities of this world; ... with some hints of the present judgments that now hangs over our heads, which will suddenly fall on us, if we neglect to return our thanks to almighty God for our late deliverances, and the speedy reforming of our lives. To which is added, the great joy and comfort of the godly that have harkened to the voice of the Lord, and have fasted and prayed to God for his blessings, and given thanks for all mercies received. By Robert Russel, in Sussex.</title>
      <author>Russel, Robert, fl. 1692.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>24 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">the author</persName>, and sold by <persName type="bookseller">J. Blare</persName>, at <placeName>the sign of the Looking-glass, on London-bridge</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>[1696?]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Imprint date suggested by Wing.</note>
      <note>Designed by the author as a sequel to his, "A warning to England: or, The nations looking-glass.".</note>
      <note>Copy stained; closely trimmed with slight loss of print.</note>
      <note>Incorrect title and Wing number in reel guide.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>J. Blare</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>the author</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the sign of the Looking-glass, on London-bridge</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
