<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Thirteen books of natural philosophy viz. I. Of the principles, and common adjuncts of all natural bodies. II. Of the heavens, the world, and elements. III. Of action, passion, generation, and corruption. IV. Of meteors. V. Of minerals and metals. VI. Of the soul in general, and of things vegetable. VII. Of animals or living creatures. VIII. Of man. Unto which is added five books more of natural philosophy in several discourses. IX. Discourses [illegible] principles of natural things. X. Dis. 2. Concerning the occult and hidden qualities. XI. Dis. 3. Of atomes and mixture. XII. Dis 4. Of the generation of live things. XIII. Dis. 5. Concerning the spontaneous generation of live things. Written in Latin and English. By Daniel Sennert, doctor of physick. Nicholas Culpeper, physitian and astrologer. Abdiah Cole, doctor of physick, and the liberal arts.</title>
         <author>Sennert, Daniel, 1572-1637.</author>
         <author>Culpeper, Nicholas, 1616-1654.</author>
         <author>Cole, Abdiah, ca. 1610-ca. 1670.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[16], 156, 341-530, 161-224 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by Peter Cole, printer and book-seller, and are to be sold at his shop, at the sign of the Printing press in Cornhill, neer the Royal Exchange,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1660">1660.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>The words "Of the principles, .. meteors.", "V. Of minerals .. man.", "IX. Discourse .. mixture", and "XII. Dis 4. .. things." are joined with separate brackets in the title; the authors names are also bracketed together.</note>
         <note>Includes preliminary contents and advertisement.</note>
         <note>Each book has a separate caption title.</note>
         <note>Text is continuous despite pagination.</note>
         <note>Signatures: pi1 A&#8308; C-Y&#8308; Z&#178;  2E-N&#8308; D-R&#8308; S&#178;  T1 2A-H&#8308; [-C4, G4].</note>
         <note>Title page stained, affecting text.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Edinburgh University Library, Edinburgh.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
