<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Discourses useful for the vain modish ladies and their gallants under these following heads, viz. I. Of some of the common ways many vertuous women take to lose their reputation, &amp;c. II. Of meer beauty-love, &amp;c. III. Of young mens folly in adoring young handsom ladies, &amp;c. IV. Of the power womens beauty exercises over most young men. V. Of the inconstancy of most ladies, especially such as are cry'd-up beauties, &amp;c. VI. Of marriage, and of wives who usurp a governing power over their husbands. VII. Of the inequality of many marriages, with the sad end that usually attend such matches. VIII. Against maids marrying for meer love, &amp;c. IX. Against widows marrying. X. Against keeping of misses. XI. Of the folly of such women as think to shew their wit by censuring of their neighbours. XII. Of the French fashions and dresses, &amp;c. XIII. Of worldly praises which all ladies love to receive, but few strive to deserve. XIV. Useful advices to the vain and modish ladies, for the well regulating their beauty and lives. By the right honourable Francis Lord Viscou</title>
      <author>Shannon, Francis Boyle, Viscount, 1623-1699.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[20], 60, 199, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">J. Taylor</persName>, at <placeName>the Ship in S. Paul's Church-yard</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1696">1696.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Place of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>With a preliminary contents leaf.</note>
      <note>Each discourse has caption title; register and pagination begin anew with the third discourse.</note>
      <note>Tightly bound.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>J. Taylor</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Ship in S. Paul's Church-yard</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
