<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Scotland illustrated, or, An essay of natural history in which are exquisitely displayed the nature of the country, the dispositions and manners of the inhabitants, and the various diseases incident to them, and likewise their proper method of cure resulting from their native medicines : and the manifold productions of nature in its three-fold kingdom, (viz.) vegetable, animal and mineral, dispersed throughout the northern part of Great Brittain, which makes up the most ancient kingdom of Scotland, are now exactly collected and published together, and their various uses, (especialy medicinal and mechanical, for the necessity as well as the accommodation of life) : clearly laid open to all : illustrated with near fifty copper plates, being the work of twenty years / published by the command of the Most Illustrious Monarch Charles II, King of Great Britain, &amp;c. by Sir R. Sibbald ...</title>
      <author>Sibbald, Robert, Sir, 1641-1722.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>368 p. in various pagings, [20] leaves of plates : ill.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">J.K.</persName>, <persName type="printer">J.S.</persName> and <persName type="printer">J.C.</persName>, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Dorman Newman</persName> ...,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Edinburgh :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1684">1684.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Text in Latin.</note>
      <note>Added t.p.: Scotia illustrata, sive, Prodromus histori&#230; naturalis.</note>
      <note>Each of the 3 parts has special t.p. and separate paging.</note>
      <note>Includes indices.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Cambridge University Library.</note>
      <note>[Pt. 1] Nuncius Scoto-Britannus, sive, Admonitio de Atlante Scotico seu descriptione Scoti&#230; antiqu&#230; et modern&#230;. 1683 -- Pt. 2, t. 1. De plantis Scoti&#230;. 1684 -- Pt. 2, t. 2. De animalibus Scoti&#230; tam feris quam domesticis et de mineralibus metallis et marinis Scoti&#230;. 1684.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>J.C.</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>J.K.</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>J.S.</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Dorman Newman</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
