<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A Solemn League and Covenant, for reformation, and defence of religion the honour and happinesse of the King, and the peace and safety of the three kingdoms of England, Scotland, and Ireland. Also, two speciall orders: viz. I. Concerning the taking of the League and Covenant in all churches and chappels in London and Westminster, upon the next Lords-day in the afternoon. II. Concerning divers lords, knights, gentlemen, colonels, officers, souldiers, and others, that are desirous to meet this present Friday in the forenoon, at Margarets-Westminster, and to take the said League and Covenant. Die Sabbathi, 30. Sept. 1643. It is this day ordered by the Commons in Parl. that this Covenant and Orders be forthwith printed &amp; published: H. Elsynge, Cl. Parl. D. Com.</title>
      <title>Solemn League and Covenant (1643)</title>
      <author>Church of Scotland. General Assembly.</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament. House of Commons.</author>
      <author>Westminster Assembly (1643-1652)</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>8 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">Edw. Husbands</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>Octob. 2. 1643.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>The covenant was formally accepted by the General Assembly of the Church of Scotland, the Westminster Assembly, and the English House of Commons.</note>
      <note>Another edition of: A solemn league and covenant, for reformation, and defence of religion, printed in Edinburgh by Evan Tyler, 1643.</note>
      <note>reproduction of original in the British Library, London, England.</note>
      <note>Imperfect; pages cropped and stained with some loss of text.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Edw. Husbands</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
