<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The gentleman's compleat jockey with the perfect horseman, and experienc'd farrier. Containing, I. The nature of horses; their breeding, feeding and management in all paces, to fit them for war, racing, travel, hunting, or other recreations and advantages. II. The true method, with proper rules and directions to order, diet and physick the running-horse, to bring him to any match, or race, with success. III. The methods to buy horses, and prevent being cheated; noting the particular marks of the good and bad horses, in all their circumstances. IV. How to make blazes, stars and snips: to fatten a horse with little charge, and to make him lively and lovely. V. The whole art of a farrier, in curing all diseases, griefs and sorrances incident to horses; with their symptoms and causes. VI. The methods of shooing, blooding, roweling, purging, and prevention of diseases, and many other things, from long experience and approved practice. by A. S. gent.</title>
         <author>A. S.</author>
         <author>Speed, Adolphus, fl. 1652-1659.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[4], 164, [12], p., [1] leaf of plates : ill. (metalcut)  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed for Henry Nelme, at the Leg and Star, over-against the Royal Exchange in Cornhil,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1697">1697.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Wrongly ascribed to Adolphus Speed.</note>
         <note>Contains engraved frontispiece depicting the anatomy of a horse.</note>
         <note>Caption title on p. 1 reads: The gentleman's compleat jockey: with the perfect horseman and farrier.</note>
         <note>Caption title on p. 23 reads: The compleat horseman: or, True art of horsemanship, in all its parts and perfections; ..</note>
         <note>With four final contents leaves and 2 final advertisement leaves.</note>
         <note>Tightly bound; some print show-through.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
