<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The perillous and most unhappy voyages of John Struys Through Italy, Greece, Lifeland, Muscovia, Tartary, Media, Persia, East-India, Japan, and other places in Europe, Africa and Asia. Containing, I. Most accurate remarks and observations of the distinct qualities, religion, politie, customs, laws and properties of the inhabitants: II. A due description of the several cities, towns, forts, and places of trust, as to their site and strength, fortifications by nature, or art, &amp;c. with other things worthy of note: and, III. An exact memorial of the most disastrous calamities which befell the author in those parts (viz) by ship-wrack, robberies, slavery, hunger, tortures, with other incommodities and hardships. To which are added 2 narrativs sent from Capt. D. Butler, relating to the taking in of Astrachan by the Cosacs. Illustrated with divers curious plates, first designed and taken from the life by the author himself. Rendered out of Nether-dutch by John Morrison·</title>
         <title>Reysen door Moscovien, Tartarijen, Oost-Indien. English</title>
         <author>Struys, Jan Janszoon, d. 1694.</author>
         <author>Morrison, John, 17th cent.</author>
         <author>Butler, David, Captain.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[16], 378, [10] p., [19] leaves of plates   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed for Samuel Smith, at the Princes Arms in S. Pauls Church-yard,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>MDCLXXXIII. [1683]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Title page in red and black.</note>
         <note>A translation, by John Morrison, of: Struys, Jan Janszoon. Reysen door Moscovien, Tartarijen, Oost-Indien.</note>
         <note>With running title: The voyages of John Struys.</note>
         <note>With an index and table of contents.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
