<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The mariners magazine, or, Sturmy's mathematical and practical arts containing the description and use of the scale of scales, it being a mathematical ruler, that resolves most mathematical conclusions, and likewise the making and use of the crostaff, quadrant, and the quadrat, nocturnals, and other most useful instruments for all artists and navigators : the art of navigation, resolved geometrically, instrumentally, and by calculation, and by that late excellent invention of logarithms, in the three principal kinds of sailing : with new tables of the longitude and latitude of the most eminent places ... : together with a discourse of the practick part of navigation ..., a new way of surveying land ..., the art of gauging all sorts of vessels ..., the art of dialling by a gnomical scale ... : whereunto is annexed, an abridgment of the penalties and forfeitures, by acts of parliaments appointed, relating to the customs and navigation : also a compendium of fortification, both geometrically and instrumentally / by Capt. Samuel Sturmy.</title>
         <author>Sturmy, Samuel, 1633-1669.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[37], 219, [3], 132, [6], 52, [52], 11, [3], [13] p., 11 leaves of plates (6 folded) : ill., port.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by E. Cotes for G. Hurlock, W. Fisher, E. Thomas, and D. Page ...,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1669">1669.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Errata: prelim. p. [35].</note>
         <note>Added t.p., engraved.</note>
         <note>"An index": prelm. p. [23]-[31].</note>
         <note>Advertisement: prelim. p. [33]-[34].</note>
         <note>Some parts have special t.p.</note>
         <note>"Canon triangulorum logarithmicus" has separate Wing number.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in Cambridge University Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
