<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The discovery of witchcraft proving that the compacts and contracts of witches with devils and all infernal spirits or familiars are but erroneous novelties and imaginary conceptions : also discovering, how far their power extendeth in killing, tormenting, consuming, or curing the bodies of men, women, children, or animals by charms, philtres, periapts, pentacles, curses, and conjurations : wherein likewise the unchristian practices and inhumane dealings of searchers and witch-tryers upon aged, melancholly, and superstitious people, in extorting confessions by terrors and tortures, and in devising false marks and symptoms, are notably detected ... : in sixteen books / by Reginald Scot ... ; whereunto is added an excellent Discourse of the nature and substance of devils and spirits, in two books : the first by the aforesaid author, the second now added in this third edition ... conducing to the compleating of the whole work, with nine chapters at the beginning of the fifteenth [sic] book of The discovery.</title>
      <title>Discoverie of witchcraft</title>
      <author>Scot, Reginald, 1538?-1599.</author>
      <author>Scot, Reginald, 1538?-1599. Discourse concerning the nature and substance of devils and spirits.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <editionStmt>
      <edition>Third edition.</edition>
    </editionStmt>
    <extent>[18], 292, [11], 72, [1] p. : ill.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Andrew Clark</persName> ...,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1665">1665.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"A discourse concerning the nature and substance of devils and spirits" (72, [1] p. at end) has special t.p.</note>
      <note>"A catalogue of authors used in this book": prelim. p. [17]-[18].</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in Huntington Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Andrew Clark</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
