<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Digitus dei: nevv discoveryes with sure arguments to prove that the Jews (a Nation) or people lost in the world for the space of near 200 years, inhabite now in America; how they came thither; their manners, customs, rites and ceremonies; the unparallel'd cruelty of the Spaniard to them; and that the Americans are of that race. Manifested by reason and scripture, which foretell the calling of the Jewes; and the restitution of them into their own land, and the bringing back of the ten tribes from all the ends and corners of the earth, and that great battell to be fought. With the removall of some contrary reasonings, and an earnest desire for effectuall endeavours to make them Christians. Whereunto is added an epistolicall discourse of Mr John Dury, with the history of Ant: Monterinos, attested by Manasseh Ben Israell, a chief rabby. By Tho: Thorowgood, B:D.</title>
      <author>Thorowgood, Thomas, d. ca. 1669.</author>
      <author>Dury, John, 1596-1680.</author>
      <author>Manasseh ben Israel, 1604-1657.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[44], 136, [4] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Slater</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop at the signe of the Angell in Duck-Lane</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1652">1652.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Includes an initial contents page.</note>
      <note>Caption title on p. 1: Jewes in America, or, Probabilities that the Americans are Jewes.</note>
      <note>Includes errata at foot of T2r.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Trinity College (University of Cambridge) Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Slater</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop at the signe of the Angell in Duck-Lane</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
