<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Three great victories I. obtained by Collonel Jones, and adjutant general Louthanie, in the entring of the town of Chester, where they took all the northeast part of the town, and the barres, and all the outworks, and works, as farre as the east gate, with all the particulars of the said fight, and the summons sent in, for the surrender of the city and castle : II. the taking of the devizes, by lieutenant generall Cromwell, with the aricles whereupon it was surrendred, on Tuesday the 24. of September, 1645, with all the particulars, about the same : III. the copie of a letter from lieutenant generall Leshley, to his excellency the Earl of Leven, of the glorious victory obtained in Scotland against Montrosse, 3 barons, killed upon the  place, 2500 also slain, 700 killed in persuit, 500 laid down their armes, 6 lords, and 1700 others taken prisoners, amongst which many of quality, and a list of the names of the chiefest of those were slain and taken, 4000 armes taken, and all Montrosses carriages and ammunition, bag and baggage : commanded to be printed ... publish'd according to order.</title>
      <author>Newark, David Leslie, Baron, d. 1682.</author>
      <author>Leven, Alexander Leslie, Earl of, 1580?-1661.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Iane Coe</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1645">1645.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Reproduction of original in Huntington Library.</note>
      <note>Caption title: The manner of the entring Chester, by Collonel Jones, and adjutant general Louthanie, with Sir William Brewertons forces, on Saturday the 20. of Sept. 1645 (also Wing M469)</note>
      <note>Parts II. and III. lacking in filmed copy.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Iane Coe</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
