<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Jesuits assassins, or, The Popish plot further declared and demonstrated in their murderous practices &amp; principles the first part ... / all extracted out of Dr. Tong's papers, written at his first discovery of this plot to his Majesty, and since in part augmented for publick satisfaction.</title>
      <author>Tonge, Ezerel, 1621-1680.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>2 pts, [4], 16 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">J. Darby to be</persName> sold by <persName type="bookseller">the Booksellers</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1680">1680.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Imperfect: the second part with title: "An answer to certain scandalous papers scattered abroad under colour of a Catholic admonition," is lacking in filmed copy.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in Huntington Library.</note>
      <note>I. A catalogue of our English popish assassins, swarming in all places, especially in the city of London. -- II. The history of the Mahometan old man of the mountains and his assassins; and a comparison of him and them with the pope and his emissaries, in doctrine and practice. -- III. The mysterious secret of the chamber of meditations amongst the Jesuits. -- IV. The examinations and depostions of Lund, and others, about the assasins and assassinations now practised, or endeavoured by the popish emissaries, against His Majesty, his nobles, and other his Protestant subjects. -- V. The Earl of Salisbury's answer to scandalous papers, wherein he was threatned to be assassinated by the confederates ofthe gunpowder traytors. -- VI. Proposals to authority, for the better extirpation of this bloody order. -- With reflections and observations upon the several relations.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>J. Darby to be</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>the Booksellers</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
