<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A true and impartial history of the wars of Ireland, Flanders, on the Rhine, and in Savoy,&amp;c More particularly what has happened in those countries since the late revolution in England, to the ending of the campaign, 1694. Relating to batt[e]ls, sieges, skirmishes, taking towns, castles, fortresses, capitulations, treaties, surrenders, brave enterprizes, noble exploits and atchievements, prisoners of note taken, and the numbers of the slain in each battel on either side. The imminent dangers and conspiracies against his Majesty's life; and by what providence and discoveries they were defeated. With the great victories at sea obtained over the French, by the English and Dutch naval forces. Also, the several descents on the coasts of France, and on the enemies territories in Flanders, &amp;c. With the burning of Diepe, Haver de grace, &amp;c. And Admiral Russel's proceedings with the royal navy in the straights. Also an account of the late defeat of the Turks, with other matters worthy of note. In two parts. Licensed according to order.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 192, 68 p., [2] leaves of plates (1 fold)   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">N. Boddington</persName> in <placeName>Duck-Lane</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1695">1695.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Frontis. = plate.</note>
      <note>Place of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>Register is continuous despite pagination.</note>
      <note>Copy stained; with print show-through.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>N. Boddington</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Duck-Lane</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
