<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The summe of Christian religion, delivered by Zacharias Ursinus first, by way of catechism, and then afterwards more enlarged by a sound and judicious exposition, and application of the same : wherein also are debated and resolved the questions of whatsoever points of moment have been, or are controversed in divinitie / first Englished by D. Henry Parry, and now again conferred with the best and last Latine edition of D. David Pareus, sometimes Professour of Divinity in Heidelberge ; whereunto is added a large and full alphabeticall table of such matters as are therein contained ; together with all the Scriptures that are occasionally handled, by way either of controversie, exposition, or reconciliation, neither of which was done before, but now is performed for the readers delight and benefit ; to this work of Ursinus are now at last annexed the Theologicall miscellanies of D. David Pareus in which the orthodoxall tenets are briefly and solidly confirmed, and the contrary errours of the Papists, Ubiquitaries, Antitrinitaries, Eutychians, Socinians, and Arminians fully refuted ; and now translated into English out of the originall Latine copie by A.R.</title>
      <author>Ursinus, Zacharias, 1534-1583.</author>
      <author>Parry, Henry, 1561-1616.</author>
      <author>Pareus, David, 1548-1622. Theologicall miscellanies.</author>
      <author>A. R.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[22], 844 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">James Young</persName>, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Steven Bowtell</persName> ...,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1645.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Theologicall miscellanies of Doctor Pareus ... / [translated] by A.R., London, 1645, has special t.p.</note>
      <note>A commentary on The Heidelberg Catechism.</note>
      <note>Signatures *6, Mmm2, pages 759 to 760, 799 to 800, 805 to 806 stained; 57 to 58 torn with loss of text; 250, 629 to 630 misnumbered; 819 print is faded in filmed copy. Pages beginning-65 and signatures Mmm1-end of book photographed from University of Illinois Library copy and inserted at end.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in Union Theological Seminary Library, New York.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Steven Bowtell</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>James Young</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
