<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The reports of Sir Peyton Ventris Kt., late one of the justices of the Common-pleas in two parts : the first part containing select cases adjudged in the Kings-Bench, in the reign of K. Charles II, with three learned arguments, one in the Kings-Bench, by Sir Francis North, when Attorney General, and two in the Exchequer by Sir Matthew Hale, when Lord Chief Baron : with two tables, one of the cases, and the other of the principal matters : the second part containing choice cases adjudged in the Common-pleas, in the reigns of K. Charles II and K. James II and in the three first years of the reign of His now Majesty K. William and the late Q. Mary, while he was a judge in the said court, with the pleadings to the same : also several cases and pleadings thereupon in the Exchequer-Chamber upon writs of error from the Kings-Bench : together with many remarkable and curious cases in the Court of Chancery : whereto are added three exact tables, one of the cases, the other of the principal matters, and the third of the pleadings : with the allowance and approbation of the Lord Keeper an all the judges.</title>
         <author>Ventris, Peyton, Sir, 1645-1691.</author>
         <author>Guilford, Francis North, Baron, 1637-1685.</author>
         <author>Hale, Matthew, Sir, 1609-1676.</author>
         <author>England and Wales. Court of King's Bench.</author>
         <author>England and Wales. Court of Common Pleas.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>2 pts. ([13], 429, [28], [21], 368, [24] p.) : ports.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by the assigns of Richard and Edward Atkyns, Esquires, for Charles Harper ..., and Jacob Tonson ...,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1696">1696.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Advertisement: p. [23]-[24] at end.</note>
         <note>Indexes: prelim. p. [8]-[13], p. [2]-[28] following p. 429, and p. [1]-[23] at end.</note>
         <note>Each part has a special t.p. with date MDCXCVI and separate paging.</note>
         <note>Some print show-through. Part 1 pages 281-90 missing in number only; 323 misnumbered; 395-96 and 401-02 missing. Part II: pages 19-22 misnumbered; 64-65, 126, and 146 marked in filmed copy. Pages 390-409 of Part I photographed from British Library copy and inserted at end.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in Cambridge University Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
