<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Popery anatomized, or, A learned, pious, and elaborat treatise wherein many of the greatest and weightiest points of controversie, between us and papists, are handled, and the truth of our doctrine clearly proved : and the falshood of their religion and doctrine anatomized, and laid open, and most evidently convicted and confuted by Scripture, fathers, and also by some of their own popes, doctors, cardinals, and of their own writers : in answer to M. Gilbert Brown, priest / by that learned, singularly pious, and eminently faithful servant of Jesus Christ M. John Welsch ...</title>
         <title>Reply against Mr. Gilbert Browne, priest</title>
         <author>Welch, John, 1568?-1622.</author>
         <author>Craford, Matthew. Brief discovery of the bloody, rebellious and treasonable principles and practises of papists.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <editionStmt>
         <edition>The second edition, revised, corrected, and divided into sections</edition>
      </editionStmt>
      <extent>[64], 519, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>By Robert Sanders ...,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>Glasgow :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1672">1672.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>"Preface" signed: Matt. Craford; "Epistle dedicatory" and "To the Christian reader" signed: M. John Welsch.</note>
         <note>"A brief discovery of the bloody, rebellious and treasonable principles and practises of papists": p. [441]-519.</note>
         <note>Originally published in Edinburgh, 1602, under title: A reply against Mr. Gilbert Browne, priest. Cf. NUC pre-1956 imprints.</note>
         <note>Errata: p. [1] at end.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the Union Theological Seminary Library, New York.</note>
         <note>Includes bibliographical references.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
