<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A reproof from the Lord declared by the movings of his Spirit to certain professors, whose habitations is in and about Hull and Beverley, who take delight in approaching to God, and to know his wayes, as a people that did righteousness, and yet seeks to limit him, and stumbles at this light, in which the knowledge of his wayes is received: with an admonition to all to beware of the leaven of the Pharisees, which is hypocrisie, who for a pretence, make long prayers, whilest iniquity is regarded in the heart, and disobedience lived in, lest you receive greater damnation. As also, an invitation to all, who are groaping in the dark, to own the light in which the pearl is found, which gives strength against sin, and rest to the soul; published for the information of such as desire to know the truth, and would enter into the kingdom, were they not deceived by the sleights of men, who shut up the way, and will neither enter themselves, nor suffer those that would go on, that you may try all things, and hold fast tha</title>
      <author>Whitehead, John, 1630-1696.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>8 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Simmons</persName>, at <placeName>the sign of the Bull</placeName> and Mouth neer <placeName>Aldersgate</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1656.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Simmons</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Aldersgate</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the sign of the Bull</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
