<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The whole duty of a woman: or a guide to the female sex From the age of sixteen to sixty, &amp;c. Being directions, how women of all qualities and conditions, ought to behave themselves in the various circumstances of this life, for their obtaining not only present, but future happiness. I. Directions how to obtain the divine and moral virtues of piety, meekness, modesty, chastity, humility, compassion, temperance and affability, with their advantages, and how to avoyd the opposite vices. II. The duty of virgins, directing them what they ought to do, and what to avoyd, for gaining all the accomplishments required in that state. With the whole art of love, &amp;c. 3. The whole duty of a wife, 4. The whole duty of a widow, &amp;c. Also choice receipts in physick and chirurgery. With the whole art of cookery, preserving, candying, beautifying, &amp;c. Written by a lady.</title>
      <author>Lady, fl. 1701.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <editionStmt>
      <edition>The second edition.</edition>
    </editionStmt>
    <extent>[6], 52, 69-104, 113-184 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">J. Gwillim, against the Great James Tavern</persName> in <placeName>Bishopsgate-street</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1696">1696.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Imperfect; stained, frayed and tightly bound, with some loss of print; B6-7 (pp. 11-14), C5-8 (pp. 33-40), D3-10 (pp. 53-68) and F5-8 (pp. 105-112) are lacking.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>J. Gwillim, against the Great James Tavern</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Bishopsgate-street</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
