<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The declaration of His Highnes William Henry, by the grace of God Prince of Orange, &amp;c. of the reasons inducing him, to appear in armes in the kingdome of England, for preserving of the Protestant religion, and for restoring the lawes and liberties of England, Scotland and Ireland Here unto are added the letters of the aforesaid his illustrious Highnesse to the sea and land forces of England, together with the prayer for the present expedition.</title>
         <title>Declaration of his Highness William Henry, by the grace of God, Prince of Orange, &amp;c. of the reasons inducing him to appear in arms for preserving of the Protestant religion and for restoring the laws and liberties of England, Scotland and Ireland.</title>
         <author>William III, King of England, 1650-1702.</author>
         <author>William III, King of England, 1650-1702. Declaration of His Highness William Henry by the grace of God Prince of Orange, &amp;c. of the reasons inducing him to appear in arms for preserving of the Protestant religion, and for restoring the laws and liberties of the ancient kingdom of Scotland. aut</author>
         <author>Burnet, Gilbert, 1643-1715.</author>
         <author>Fagel, Gaspar, 1634-1688, attributed name.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 17, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>by Arnold Leers, bookseller at the signe of Plutarch. By speciall order of his Highnesse,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>Printed at the Hague :</pubPlace>
         <date>1688.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>According to J.E.S. Clarke and H.C. Foxcroft, "Life of Gilbert Burnet" (p. 243), the declaration was actually written for William of Orange by Gaspar Fagel and was translated into English by Gilbert Burnet.</note>
         <note>At foot of title page: With priviledge of the great and mighty the states of Holland and Westfriesland.</note>
         <note>Includes "The declaration of His Highness William Henry by the grace of God Prince of Orange, &amp;c. of the reasons inducing him to appear in arms for preserving of the Protestant religion, and for restoring the laws and liberties of the ancient kingdom of Scotland", which has caption title on p. 11; register and pagination are continuous.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
