<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Virginia, more especially the south part thereof, richly and truly valued viz. the fertile Carolana, and no lesse excellent Isle of Roanoak, of latitude from 31 to 37 degr. relating the meanes of raysing infinite profits to the adventurers and planters.</title>
      <author>Williams, Edward, fl. 1650.</author>
      <author>Ferrar, John, d. 1657.</author>
      <author>Goddard, John, fl. 1645-1671.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <editionStmt>
      <edition>The second edition,</edition>
    </editionStmt>
    <extent>[12], 47, [14], 75, [3] p., [1] folded leaf of plates : ill., map.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">T.H.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">John Stephenson</persName> ...,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1650">1650.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>The first part of this "second edition" appeared in two previous editions: Virgo triumphans; or, Virginia richly and truly valued, and, Virgo triumphans; or, Virginia in generall but the south part thereof in particular. Both had imprint: London : Printed by T. Harper for J. Stephenson, 1650, and both lacked the map by John Ferrar. Cf. NUC pre-1956 imprints.</note>
      <note>The second part, or "addition," has special t.p.: Virginia's discovery of silke-vvormes, with their benefit ... London : Printed by T.H. for John Stephenson ..., 1650.</note>
      <note>A third edition appeared in 1651, with title: Virginia in America richly valued ...</note>
      <note>Quartich (General catalogue, v. 5, p. 2991-2992) says that John Farrer (or Ferrar), who is referred to in the preface, supplied Williams with the material for this work, and describes Ferrar's own copy of the 1st edition, with his marginalia and a drawing of a map dated 1650. Quartich also says that no map was issued with the 1st and 2nd editions, but that Ferrar's design was engraved in 1651 for the 3rd edition. However, this photographed copy of the 1650 2nd edition does contain the 1651 map, which was engraved by John Goddard.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Huntington Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>John Stephenson</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>T.H.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
