<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>This is written in plainnesse of heart, and bowels of everlasting love to my persecutors who have shot sore at me, and hated me without a cause. Both magistrates, priests and people in Stafford sheir, of elsewhere, that ye all may be turned from the darknesse to the light, and from anti-christ without, unto Chrust within, who is the light of the world, and hath lighted wvery man therein with his saving light. Some queres also, for such who call themselves ministers of Christ, but are altogether unlike him, or his ministers to answer. Together with a warning from the Lord God of life and power to repent, andleave persecuting, and striving against, or kicking against the Lord. Written from one who have been in the pit, death, grave, and Hell; but am come from far, and am sit down with Abraham, Isaack, and Jacob, in the heavenly places with them that are in Christ, but unknown to you, I am: but by the name I have received amongst you, Humphry Wollrich.</title>
      <author>Wollrich, Humphry, 1633?-1707.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 20 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Robert Wilson</persName>, at <placeName>the signe of the Black-spread-Eagle</placeName> and wind-Mill in <placeName>Martins-lane near Aldersgate</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1661">[1661]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Place and date of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Friends' House Library, London.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Robert Wilson</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Martins-lane near Aldersgate</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the signe of the Black-spread-Eagle</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
