<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The Protestant's crums of comfort containing I. Prayers and meditations, with ejaculations for every day in the week, and other occasions. II. Thanksgivings for deliverances from Popery, tyranny, and arbitrary power. III. The rebellion in Ireland, and massacre of Paris. IV. The learned Bishop Usher's prophecy, concerning Ireland, and the downfall of Rome. V. Advice to the late besieged in London-Derry, under that reverend divine and valiant commander, Coll. George Walker. Illustrated with pictures suitable to each particular occasion.</title>
         <author>Walker, George, of Londonderry.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[4], 153, [9] p., [4] leaves of plates : port.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by W.W. for Nicholas Bodington at the Golden Ball in Duck-lane,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1690">1690.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>With a licence to print on verso of title page dated December 16th. 1689.</note>
         <note>Dedication signed: G.W.; attributed by Wing to George Walker.</note>
         <note>Each part of the text headed by a caption title; on p. 1: "The Protestants manual of prayers and meditations"; on p. 61: "Ejaculations upon several occasions out of the Holy Scriptures"; on p. 93: "A short account of the massacre in Ireland &amp; Paris"; on p. 103: "Strange and remarkable predictions of that holy, learned, and excellent bishop, James Usher, late Lord Primate of Ireland"; on p. 121: "Thanksgivings for God's wonderful deliverances"; on p. 131: "Christian courage in affliction".</note>
         <note>Frontis. = plate; consists of medallion portraits of Queen Elizabeth, King James I, King William III and Queen Mary; the three folded plates include woodcuts of the coronation of William and Mary, the Reverend Bishop Usher, the Irish rebellion, and French massacre, the downfall of Rome, the Spanish invasion, the Gun Powder Plot, and the arrival of the Prince of Orange.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
