<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>An experimental treatise of surgerie in four parts : 1. The first part shewing the dangerous abuses committed among the modern surgeons, 2. Of cures of all sorts of wounds in mans body ..., 3. Of the symptomes of wounds ..., 4. Treating of all kinds of balmes, salves, plaisters, ointments, oyles, bloodstenchers, potions, tents, corrosives, &amp;c. which are used for wounds ... / by that most famous and renowned surgeon, Felix Wurtz, citie surgeon at Basell ... ; exactly perused after the authors own manuscrip, by Rodolph Wurtz, surgeon at Strasburg ; faithfully the second time translated into Neather Dutch, out of the twenty eighth copy printed in the German tongue, and now also Englished and much corrected, by Abraham Lenertzon Fox, surgeon at Zaerdam ; whereunto is added a very necessary and useful piece, by the same author, called the Childrens book, treating of all things which are necessary to be known by all those, to whose trust and overlooking, little children are committed.</title>
         <title>Practica der Wundartzney. English</title>
         <author>Würtz, Felix, 1518-1575?</author>
         <author>Fox, Abraham Lenertzon.</author>
         <author>Wurtz, Rodolf.</author>
         <author>Wurtz, Felix, 1517 or 18-1574 or 75. Childrens book of Felix Wurtz.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[20], 199, [1], 217-366 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by Gartrude Dawson ... and are to be sold by the book-sellers shops,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1656.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Translation of the author's Practica der Wundartzney--NUC pre-1956 imprints.</note>
         <note>Caption title (p. 339): The childrens book of Felix Wurtz ...</note>
         <note>"First published in Basel, in 1563"--NUC pre-1956 imprints.</note>
         <note>Marginal notes.</note>
         <note>Imperfect: torn and stained, with slight loss of print.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the Cambridge University Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
