<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The history &amp; vindication of the loyal formulary, or Irish remonstrance ... received by His Majesty anno 1661 ... in several treatises : with a true account and full discussion of the delusory Irish remonstrance and other papers framed and insisted on by the National Congregation at Dublin, anno 1666, and presented to ... the Duke of Ormond, but rejected by His Grace : to which are added three appendixes, whereof the last contains the Marquess of Ormond ... letter of the second of December, 1650 : in answer to both the declaration and excommunication of the bishops, &amp;c. at Jamestown / the author, Father Peter Walsh ...</title>
      <author>Walsh, Peter, 1618?-1688.</author>
      <author>Ormonde, James Butler, Duke of, 1610-1688. Articles of peace.</author>
      <author>Rothe, David, 1573-1650. Queries concerning the lawfulnesse of the present cessation.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>4 pts. ([2], lii, [18], 765, 83, [2], vi, 137 p.)   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>s.n.],</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
      <date notBefore="1673" notAfter="1674">1673-1674.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Place of publication from BM.</note>
      <note>"Queries concerning the lawfulnesse of the present cessation and of the censures against all confederates adhering unto it" has special t.p. with imprint: Imprinted at Kilkenny 1648, and reprinted 1673.</note>
      <note>"The articles of peace made and concluded by ... James Lord Marquess of Ormond ... with the General Assembly of the Roman-Catholicks" has special t.p. with imprint date: Reprinted 1673.</note>
      <note>The first and second appendix each has a special t.p. with imprint date: 1673.</note>
      <note>No more published. Cf. BM.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in Cambridge University Library.</note>
      <note>Some pages are faded, stained and have print show-through. The first part of the First treatise, p. 420 and 471 have print faded in filmed copy. Pages 410-475 photographed from Bodleian Library copy and inserted at the  end.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
