<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Englands unthankfulness striving with Gods goodness, for the victory as Abaslom [sic] strove with David, whether the father should be more kinde to the son; or the son more unkinde to the father. Or, enough (being wel weighed) to melt an heart of adamant. By R. Younge, florilegus. In reference to Leviticus 19.17 and Isaiah 58.1. In reading whereof, reflect upon your selves; hearken to conscience; and what concerns you, apply it to others, as David did Nathans parable, 2 Sam. 12.1, to 8. And Ahab the prophets, 1 King.20. 39, to 43. Want of application makes all means ineffectual; and therefore are we Christians in name only, because we think out selves Christians indeed, and already good enough.</title>
      <author>Younge, Richard.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <editionStmt>
      <edition>The fourth Impression. Imprimatur, Thomas Gataker.</edition>
    </editionStmt>
    <extent>72 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">J Bell</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">James Crumpe a booke-binder:</persName> and are to be sold at <placeName>his House, in Little Bartholomewes Wel-yard</placeName>, and probably at <placeName>most Stationers shops</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1643" cert="low">[1643?]]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Caption title.</note>
      <note>Imprint from colophon; publication date conjectured by Wing.</note>
      <note>The words "Leviticus .. 58.1" are bracketed together on first page.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: Gods goodnesse, and Englands unthankfulnesse.</note>
      <note>Includes a letter and postscript, each with caption title.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>James Crumpe a booke-binder:</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>J Bell</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his House, in Little Bartholomewes Wel-yard</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>most Stationers shops</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
