<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A new art of making wines, brandy, and other spirits, compliant to the late act of Parliament, concerning distillaton illustrated by the doctrine of fermentation, by various examples of the growths and products of this land : wherein is laid down full and effectual directions, for the making of wholsome and medicinal wines : as also a true and facile way to bring low wines into proof spirits, which being by true art made from sound grain, are not inferior to those of France, for which reason are several propositions stated for the encouraging a brandy manufacturage here in England : also the way is shewn to exalt these spirits so high as to bear that proof to fire gunpowder, and their various uses, especially for lacker Jappan, and Chany varnishes, and several other useful receipts, which were never so plainly publish'd before : lastly is subjoyn'd, a general treatise concerning the original and nature of diseases : together with their cure by spagirick medicines : recommended to all that desire to improve and advance those liquors which are made from the English growths / by W.Y., spagirick physician in both medicines, and philosopher by fire.</title>
      <author>Y-Worth, W. (William)</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[50], 153, [26] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">T. Salusbury</persName> ...,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1691.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Advertisement: p. [1]-[12] at end.</note>
      <note>Errata: p. [26] at end.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in Cambridge University Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>T. Salusbury</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
