<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Collectanea chymica a collection of ten several treatises in chymistry, concerning the liquor alkahest, the mercury of philosophers, and other curiosities worthy the perusal / written by Eir. Philaletha, Anonymous, Joh. Bapt. Van-Helmont, Dr. Fr. Antonie ... [et al.].</title>
         <title>Collectanea chymica.</title>
         <author>Philalethes, Eirenaeus. Secret of the immortal liquor called Alkahest. Latin and English.</author>
         <author>Helmont, Jean Baptiste van, 1577-1644. Praecipiolum.</author>
         <author>Anthony, Francis, 1550-1623. Aurum-potabile.</author>
         <author>Bernard, of Trevisan. De lapide philosophorum. English.</author>
         <author>Ripley, George, d. 1490? Bosome-book.</author>
         <author>Bacon, Roger, 1214?-1294. Speculum alchemiae. English.</author>
         <author>Starkey, George, 1627-1665. Admirable efficacy and almost incredible virtue of true oyl.</author>
         <author>Plat, Hugh, Sir, 1552-1611? Sundry new and artificial remedies against famine.</author>
         <author>H. V. D. Tomb of Semiramis hermetically sealed.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[6], 193, [4], 32 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for William Cooper ...,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1684">1684.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Each treatise (except the last) has special t.p. dated 1683. The last treatise has special t.p. with imprint date 1684.</note>
         <note>"The secret of the immortal liquor" has added t.p. in Latin and text in English and Latin.</note>
         <note>"The tomb of Semiramis" appears separately at reel 178:18, and has been cataloged separately.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in British Library.</note>
         <note>The secret of the immortal liquor called alkahest, or ignisaqua /  by Eirenaeus Philatethes [pseud.] -- The practice of lights, or, An excellent and ancient treatise of the philosophers stone -- Praecipiolum, or, The immature-mineral-electrum / by J.B. Van-Helmont -- Aurum-potabile, or, The receit of Dr. Fr. Antonie -- A treatise of Bernard, Earl of Trevisan, of the philosophers stone -- The bosome-book of Sir George Ripley -- Speculum alchymiae = The true glass of alchemy / by Roger Bacon -- The admirable efficacy and almost incredible virtue of true oyl, which is made of sulphur-vive, set on fire and called commonly oyl of sulphur per campanem / G. Starkey -- Sundry new and artificial remedies against famine / written by Sir H. Platt -- The tomb of Semiramis hermetically sealed.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
