<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A copy of the letters, wherin the most redouted [and] mighty pri[n]ce, our souerayne lorde kyng Henry the eight, kyng of Englande [and] of Frau[n]ce, defe[n]sor of the faith, and lorde of Irla[n]de: made answere vnto a certayne letter of Martyn Luther, sente vnto him by the same and also the copy of the foresaid Luthers letter, in such order, as here after foloweth.</title>
      <title>Literarum, quibus invictissimus princeps, Henricus octavus, rex Angliae et Franciae, dominus Hyberniae, ac fidei defensor respondit, ad quandam epistolam Martini Lutheri, ad se missam. English</title>
      <author>Henry VIII, King of England, 1491-1547.</author>
      <author>Luther, Martin, 1483-1546. Epistola ad Henricum Octavum Angliae et Franciae regem. English.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[100] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>In Flete-strete by <persName type="printer">Rycharde Pynson</persName>, printer to <persName type="patron">the kynges moost noble grace</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1527" cert="low">[1527?]]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of "Literarum, quibus invictissimus princeps, Henricus octavus, rex Angliae et Franciae, dominus Hyberniae, ac fidei defensor respondit, ad quandam epistolam Martini Lutheri, ad se missam", including the letter from Luther originally published as "Epistola ad Henricum Octavum Angliae et Franciae regem".</note>
      <note>Printer's name and address from colophon; publication date conjectured by STC.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A&#185;&#178;  B-E F&#8310;.</note>
      <note>The final leaf contains a printer's mark.</note>
      <note>In this edition, B1r line 4 ends: fayth.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the British Library (reel 52:10) and the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery (reel 519:16).</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Rycharde Pynson</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="patron">
      <persName>the kynges moost noble grace</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
