<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A declaration of Henry Marc de Gouffier Marquise of Boniuet, Lord of Creuec&#339;ur, &amp;c. Made in the consistorie of Rochell, in the presence of the pastors and elders of the said towne; as also of Monsieur de la Violette and Theuenot, pastors of the churches of Marans and Benet, on Wednesday being the third of August, 1616. The which very same protestation likewise hath beene made by the said Lord Marquise in the presence of the whole church of Rochel, on Sunday being the seuenth of the said moneth, after the morning sermon in the great church. At Rochell, printed for H. Haultin, by Cornelis Hertman. 1616.</title>
      <title>Declaration de Henri-Marc de Gouffier. English</title>
      <author>Bonnivet, Henri Marc de Gouffier, Marquis de, d. 1589.</author>
      <author>E. M., of Christ Church, Oxford.</author>
      <author>Meetkerke, Edward, 1590-1657.</author>
      <author>R. M., fl. 1616.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 14 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Edward Griffin</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Nathaniel Butter</persName>, dwelling neere <placeName>S. Austens gate, at the signe of the Pide-Bull</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1616">1616.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Announcing his conversion to the Reformed Church.</note>
      <note>Translation of: Declaration de Henri-Marc de Gouffier.</note>
      <note>Translator's preface signed: E.M., i.e. Edward Meetkerke?.</note>
      <note>With a letter, and an extract of another, both signed R.M.</note>
      <note>Usually found as part 2 of "Newes from France" (STC 7372), a reissue of: La Mothe Luyne, M. Du Tertre, sieur de.  A declaration and manifestation, of the chiefe reasons and motives of the conversion of master M. du Tertre.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Nathaniel Butter</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Edward Griffin</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>S. Austens gate, at the signe of the Pide-Bull</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
