<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The contemplation of mankinde contayning a singuler discourse after the art of phisiognomie, on all the members and partes of man, as from the heade to the foote, in a more ample maner than hytherto hath beene published of any. In the place next after the chapter of the forehead, hath the phisiognomer added a proper treatise of the signification of sundrie lines seene in most mens foreheads: which in sundrie disputations with a skilfull Iew, he at the last obtayned. ... In the ende is a little treatise added of the signification of moles ... written by a worthie Grecian named Melampus. All which, englished by Thomas Hyll.</title>
         <author>Hill, Thomas, b. ca. 1528.</author>
         <author>Cocles, Bartolommeo della Rocca, 1467-1504. Chyromantie ac physionomie anastasis.</author>
         <author>Malampus, 3rd cent. B.C. Peri elai&#333;n s&#333;matos. English.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[16], 208, 109-132, 233-236 [i.e. 244] leaves : ill. (woodcuts), port.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>By [Henry Denham for] William Seres, dwelling at the west ende of Paules Church, at the signe of the Hedgehogge],</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1571">1571.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A greatly enlarged version of Hill's 1556 translation of "Chyromantie ac physionomie anastasis" by Bartolommeo della Rocca Cocles, in which these woodcuts first appeared. The work by Malampus is "Peri elai&#333;n s&#333;matos".</note>
         <note>Ostensible printer's name and address from colophon; actual printer's name from STC.</note>
         <note>Includes a bibliography of Hill's works.</note>
         <note>The first leaf is blank except for signature-mark "[par.].j.".</note>
         <note>Quires B and C have numbered leaves interleaved with unnumbered.</note>
         <note>Running title reads: A pleasaunt discourse of phisiognomie.</note>
         <note>Identified as STC 17787 on UMI microfilm reel 287.</note>
         <note>Reproductions of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery (same copy filmed twice).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
