<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A miracle, of miracles As fearefull as euer was seene or heard of in the memorie of man. Which lately happened at Dichet in Sommersetshire, and sent by diuers credible witnesses to be published in London. Also a prophesie reuealed by a poore countrey maide, who being dead the first of October last, 1613. 24. houres, reuiued againe, and lay fiue dayes weeping, and continued prophesying of strange euents to come, and so died the 5. day following. Witnessed by M. Nicholas Faber, parson of the towne, and diuers worthy gentlemen of the same countrey. 1613, withall, Lincolnshire teares. For a great deluge, in which fiue villages were lamentably drovvned this present month.</title>
         <author>T. I., fl. 1614.</author>
         <author>Schlichtenberger, Eyriak. Prophecey eines Bawren Tochter, welch den 18. Jenner. English.</author>
         <author>Trundle, John, attributed name.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[32] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed [by G. Eld] for Iohn Trundle: and are to be sold at Christ Church gate,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1614.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Contains a revised version of STC 5681 ("A true and most dreadfull discourse of a woman possessed with the Devill") and STC 21818 (which is a translation, with dates altered in the present item, of "Prophecey eines Bawren Tochter, welche den 18. Jenner")--Cf. STC.</note>
         <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
         <note>Preface signed: T.I. [i.e. John Trundle?].</note>
         <note>"Lincolnshire Teares" has a separate dated title page that reads: Lamentable newes out of Lincolne-shire of the ouerflowing of waters, breaking from the seas, which drowned 5. villages with all their goods and cattell, with other places of the land, this present month of Nouember: 1613. to the great hurt of many people there dwelling.</note>
         <note>Signatures: A-D⁴.</note>
         <note>Formerly also STC 15652.</note>
         <note>Reproductions of the original in the British Library.</note>
         <note>Appears at reel 774 and at reel 802 (both are British Library copy).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
