<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>God be thanked A sermon of thanksgiuing for the happy successe of the English fleetes, sent forth by the honourable company of aduenturers to the East Indies. Preached to the honourable gouernors and committees, and the whole company, of their good ship, the Hope Marchant happily returened: at Deptford on Maundy Thursday last being the 29th of March. 1616. Hereunto are added sundry necessary and vseful formes of prayer and thankes-giuing for the helpe of all such as trauell by sea, fitted to their seruerall occasions. By Samuel Page Dr. in Diuinitie.</title>
      <author>Page, Samuel, 1574-1630.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 32, [4], 14, [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Nicholas Okes</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Simon Waterson</persName>, and are to bee sold at <placeName>his shop in Pauls Church-yard at the signe of the Crowne</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1616">1616.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"Diuine sea-seruice" has separate title page and pagination; register is continuous.</note>
      <note>The last leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>"Diuine sea-seruice" identified as STC 19090 on UMI microfilm reel 585.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the Folger Shakespeare Library and the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      <note>Appears at reel 585 (Folger Shakespeare Library copy) and at reel 1355 (Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery copy).</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Simon Waterson</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Nicholas Okes</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop in Pauls Church-yard at the signe of the Crowne</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
