<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The chirche of the euyll men and women wherof Lulyfer [sic] is the heed, and the membres is all the players dyssolute and synners reproued.</title>
      <title>Quadragesimale de christiana religione. Sermo 42. English. Selections</title>
      <author>Bernardino, da Siena, Saint, 1380-1444.</author>
      <author>Watson, Henry, fl. 1500-1518.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[76] p. : ill. (woodcut)  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Wynkyn de Worde?]</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[[Paris? :</pubPlace>
      <date>M.CCCCC.xj. [1511] the. xxij. daye of Auguste]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation by Henry Watson of an adapted French translation of a section of sermo 42 of "Quadragesimale de christiana religione" by Bernardino da Siena; both individuals' names appear on A1v.</note>
      <note>Publication date from colophon, which reads: This present treatye hathe made to be prynted two venerable doctours of the faculte of theologye at Parys mayster thomas Varnet curate of saynt Nycolas of the feldes, and mayster Nowell beda pryncypall of the ryght ruled college of Mou[n]tagu ..</note>
      <note>"While the types have considerable resemblance to those of de Worde, the woodcuts, orns., and inits. are not part of his usual stock and are prob. French; the colophon date may merely repeat that in a French ed."--STC.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A-F&#8308;&#183; G&#178; .</note>
      <note>Identified as STC 5213 on UMI microfilm reel 133.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in Cambridge University Library and the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      <note>Appears at reels 11 and 25 (Cambridge University Library copy, filmed twice), and at reel 133 (Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery copy).</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Wynkyn de Worde?]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
