<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The ioyfull entrie of the Dukedome of Brabant &amp; the articles agreed vpon, and graunted by their lordes, and confirmed by the Emperour Charles the Fifte, and solemnely sworne by Philippe his sonne King of Spaine. Anno 1549. Set foorth to the viewe of al louers of the trueth, who openly may see therein, how the same in no wise is perfourmed, (the Lord in his mercie emende it) but to the contrary, in place of getting and preseruing of priuiledges and liberties, they are through the inspiration of the Pope and his allyed, with all crueltie and tyrannie, broken, taken away, &amp; totally voyd. Printed at Delft in Dutch, and Englished by R.V.S. 1581.</title>
         <title>Treaties, etc. Brabant (Duchy), 1549-07-05</title>
         <author>Holy Roman Empire. Emperor (1519-1556 : Charles V)</author>
         <author>Cuba. Fuerzas Armadas Revolucionarias.</author>
         <author>Brabant (Duchy). Treaties, etc. Holy Roman Empire, 1549-07-05.</author>
         <author>Spain. Sovereign (1556-1598 : Philip II)</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[40] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>By Robert VValdegraue, dwelling without Temple-bar, neere vnto Sommerset-House,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>Printed at London :</pubPlace>
         <date>[1581]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>The title refers to the "Blijde Inkomst" of 3 Jan. 1356, but this is in fact a separate agreement.</note>
         <note>Dated at end: Giuen in our citie of Louaine, the fift day of Iuly, anno. 1549. ..</note>
         <note>Signatures: A-B C⁴.</note>
         <note>Running title reads: Articles agreed vpon by the king of Spaine.</note>
         <note>Reproductions of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
         <note>Appears on reels 177 and 275 (same copy filmed twice).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
