<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The third part of the Defence of the Reformed Catholike against Doct. Bishops Second part of the Reformation of a Catholike, as the same was first guilefully published vnder that name, conteining only a large and most malicious preface to the reader, and an answer to M. Perkins his aduertisement to Romane Catholicks, &amp;c. Whereunto is added an aduertisement for the time concerning the said Doct. Bishops reproofe, lately published against a little piece of the answer to his epistle to the King, with an answer to some few exceptions taken against the same, by M. T. Higgons latley become a proselyte of the Church of Rome. By R. Abbot Doctor of Diuinitie.</title>
         <title>Defence of the Reformed Catholicke of M. W. Perkins. Part 3</title>
         <author>Abbot, Robert, 1560-1618.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8], 184, 183-385, [1], 80, 91-108 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Impensis Georgii Bishop,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>Londini :</pubPlace>
         <date>1609.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A reply to: Bishop, William.  The second part of The reformation of a Catholike deformed.</note>
         <note>Printed at Eliot's Court Press. Cf. STC.</note>
         <note>The first leaf is blank.</note>
         <note>"An advertisement for the time concerning Doctor Bishops reproofe" has separate pagination; register is continuous.</note>
         <note>Identified as part of STC 50 on UMI microfilm reel 947.</note>
         <note>Reproductions of the originals in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery and Cambridge University Library.</note>
         <note>Appears at reel 1591 (Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery copy) and at reel 947 (Cambridge University Library copy).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
