<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Foure sermons viz. 1. The blessednesse of peace-makers. 2. The aduancement of Gods children. Preached before the King. 3. The sinne against the holy Ghost. Preached at Pauls Crosse. 4. The Christian petitioner. Preached at Oxford on the Act Sunday. By Iohn Denison Doctor of Diuinity, and one of his Maiesties Chaplaynes.</title>
         <author>Denison, John, d. 1629.</author>
         <author>Denison, John, d. 1629. Beati pacifici.</author>
         <author>Denison, John, d. 1629. Sinne against the holy ghost plainly described.</author>
         <author>Denison, John, d. 1629. Christian petitioner. Shewing how we must sue for reward and remission.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[10], 278 [i.e. 280] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by T. S[nodham] for Iohn Budge, and are to be sold at the signe of the greene-Dragon in Paules Church-yard,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1620">1620.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
         <note>The words: "The blessednesse .. Gods children" are bracketed together on the title page.</note>
         <note>Each of the four sermons has a separate dated title page; collation and pagination are continuous.</note>
         <note>STC 6593 is now part of this. Consists of general title page plus A-F (a reissue of Denison's "Beati pacifici"; STC 6583) and G-S (reprints of STC 6591 and 6585)--Cf. STC.</note>
         <note>Numerous errors in pagination; actual pagination derived from signature collation.</note>
         <note>Sermon 3 formerly STC 6593.</note>
         <note>Identified as STC 6593 on UMI microfilm reel 1445.</note>
         <note>Imperfect as filmed; Bodleian Library copy on reel 1445 contains only the third sermon.</note>
         <note>Reproductions of the originals in the Bodleian Library and the British Library.</note>
         <note>Appears at reel 1063 (British Library copy) and at reel 1445 (Bodleian Library copy).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
