<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A manifestation of the motiues, vvhereupon the most Reuerend Father, Marcus Antonius de Dominis, Archbishop of Spalato, (in the territorie of Venice) vndertooke his departure thence. Englished out of his Latine copy</title>
      <title>Marcus Antonius de Dominis, Archiepiscopus Spalatensis, suae profectionis consilium exponit. English</title>
      <author>De Dominis, Marco Antonio, 1560-1624.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 56, 5, [3], 5, [19] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed [by <persName type="printer">Robert Barker]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">John Bill</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1616">Anno 1616.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of: Marcus Antonius de Dominis, Archiepiscopus Spalatensis, suae profectionis consilium exponit.</note>
      <note>Actual printer's name from STC.</note>
      <note>The first leaf is blank except for signature-mark "A" and a woodcut.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A-G&#8308; H&#178;  I-M&#8308;.</note>
      <note>The last leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>Quires B, D, E and F are largely in two settings. B2r line 3 up has (1) "raise" or (2) "rayse". D2r line 4 has (1) "doe" or (2) "do". E1v begins (1) "auncient" or (2) "ancient". F2r line 9 has (1) "alowd" or (2) "aloud".</note>
      <note>"Decretum sacr&#230; congregationis ill.morum S.R.E. Cardinalium" (5, [3] p.) comes in three versions: (1) signed G (same version as found in some copies of STC 6996); (2) same type reimposed, signed with an italic I; (3) same type reimposed, signed by a roman I.</note>
      <note>"The decree of the sacred congregation of the most illustrious cardinals of the holy Church of Rome" (second 5, [3] p.), a translation of the above, comes in two versions: (1) signed I; (2) same type reimposed, signed K.</note>
      <note>Identified as STC 6998a on UMI microfilm reel 922.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the Folger Shakespeare Library and the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      <note>Appears at reel 922 (Folger Shakespeare Library copy) and at reel 1481 (Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery copy).</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>John Bill</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Robert Barker]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
