<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>By the Queene. A proclamation vvith certayne clauses of diuers statutes, &amp; other necessary additions, first published in the xix. yeere of the Queenes Maiesties reigne, and now reuiued by her highnes commandement to be put in execution, vpon the penalties in the same conteined</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Sovereign (1558-1603 : Elizabeth I)</author>
      <author>Elizabeth I, Queen of England, 1533-1603.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>8 leaves.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">Christopher Barker</persName>, printer to <persName type="patron">the Queenes moat excellent Maiestie.</persName> Cum priuilegio Regi&#230; Maiestatis,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1580">Anno Dom. 1579 [i.e. 1580]]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"Given at our palace of Westminster, the xii of februarie, in the xxii yeere of our raigne"--Leaf [2].</note>
      <note>Imprint from colophon on sheet 7; year given according to Lady Day dating.</note>
      <note>Against excess in apparel--STC.</note>
      <note>Sheet 3 has caption title "A briefe content of certaine clauses of the statutes of King Henrie the eyght, and Queene Marie, .." Sheet 6 has caption title "Necessarie additions." Sheet 7 has caption title "A commandement giuen by the Queenes most excellent Maiestie, .., concerning clokes and ruffes of excessiue length and depth."; sheets 1-6 reprint STC 8091, with 3-6 signed A3-A6. Sheet 7 may originally have concluded the set of sheets; perhaps because it has new text it is found in two settings: last indented line to right of initials begins: "other" (most copies) or "the". Sheet 8, which also has imprint as above, possibly represents a separate proclamation, but because of its date of issue is usually considered part of the present item--STC.</note>
      <note>Incorrectly identified as STC 8091 at reel 1874:80.</note>
      <note>Imperfect: item at reel 1874:80 lacks sheets 7-8.</note>
      <note>Appears at reel 565 (Bodleian Library copy) and at reel 1874 (Society of Antiquaries copy).</note>
      <note>One Bodleian copy is complete, plus sheets 3-5 w. STC 8091.--Cf. STC.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the Bodleian Library and the Society of Antiquaries.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Christopher Barker</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="patron">
      <persName>the Queenes moat excellent Maiestie.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
