<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A voyage to the East-Indies giving an account of the Isles of Madagascar, and Mascareigne, of Suratte, the coast of Malabar, of Goa, Gameron, Ormus : as also A treatise of the distempers peculiar to the eastern countries : to which is annexed an abstract of Monsieur de Rennefort's History of the East-Indies, with his propositions for the improvement of the East-India Company / written originally in French by Mr. Dellon ...</title>
         <title>Relation d'un voyage des Indes Orientales. English</title>
         <author>Dellon, Gabriel, b. 1649.</author>
         <author>M. C. Treatise of the distempers relating in particular to the eastern countries.</author>
         <author>Crull, J. (Jodocus), d. 1713?</author>
         <author>Rennefort, Souchu de, ca. 1630-ca. 1690. Histoire des Indes orientales. English. Selections.</author>
         <author>Dellon, Gabriel, b. 1649. Traité des maladies particulières aux pays orientaux et dans la route et de leurs remèdes. English.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[30], 248, 43 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for D. Browne ..., A. Roper ..., and T. Leigh ...,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1698.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Translation by Jodocus Crull of: Relation d'un voyage des Indes orientales.</note>
         <note>Special t.p. on p. [221]: A treatise of the distempers relating in particular to the eastern countries, and such other diseases as commonly happen in the voyages into those parts, with their proper remedies / by M.C., D.D., E.M.</note>
         <note>Special t.p. and separate pagination (43 p.): A supplement to the Sieur Dellone's relation to the East-Indies, &amp;c.</note>
         <note>Reel 622:4 has "A treatise of the distempers" only, as Wing C85 (number cancelled in Wing 2nd ed.).</note>
         <note>This item appears at reel 180:1 as Wing D943 (number changed to D943A in Wing 2nd ed.).</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in British Library and Bodleian Library, Oxford.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
