<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Index Biblicus: or An exact concordance to the Holy Bible, according to the last translation. Whereunto are added The marginal readings, with the acceptations and various significantions of the principal words contained in the Holy Scriptures of the Old &amp; New Testaments. / Composed in a new and most comprehensive method, and adorned with divers significant and pregnant scripture-phrases.  By John Jackson, minister of the Gospel at Moulsea in Surrey.</title>
         <author>Jackson, John, minister of the Gospel at Moulsea in Surrey.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[193] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by John Field, Printer to the University,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>Cambridge :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1668">1668.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>This item appears as Wing J79 on reel 1287:16, as Wing H2196 on reel 1593:66 and 2917:9b, and is also found bound with: The Holy Bible. Cambridge : Printed by John Field, 1668, (Wing B2277, on reel 1088:1).  Cf.  Wing (2nd ed.).</note>
         <note>Includes index.</note>
         <note>Imperfect: Copy at 2917:9b is stained and tightly bound with some loss of text.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of originals in: Bodleian Library (reel 1088:1), Trinity College Library (University of Cambridge) (reel 1593:66), University of Illinois (Urbana-Champaign Campus) (reel 1287:16), and British and Foreign Bible Society (reel 2917:9b).</note>
         <note>Bound and filmed with B2259A: The Holy Bible, containing the Old Testament and the New: newly translated out of the original tongues ..., London : Printed by John Bill and Christopher Barker, Printers to the Kings most Excellent Majesty, 1661.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
