<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Prophecies of Christopher Kotterus, Christiana Poniatovia, Nicholas Drabicius Three famous German prophets, foretelling forty years agoe this present invasion of the Turks into the Empire of Germany, and the events that will ensue. The miraculous conversion of the great Turk, and the translating of the Bible into the Turkish language. Predictions concerning the Pope, Emperor, and King of France, with the sudden destruction of the Popish religion in the year 1666. Presaging also the uniting of all religions into one visible church, and how that church shall be governed by Bishops, &amp;c. Many of the prophecies were very much desired by the late King of Bohemia, and were presented to him by the learned and eminent Protestant divine Comenius, and by him made publick. Translated out of the Latine by R. C. Gent. Licensed and entered according to order.</title>
      <title>Lux in tenebris. English.</title>
      <author>Kotter, Christoph, d. 1647. aut</author>
      <author>Poniatowska, Krystyna, 1610-1644. aut</author>
      <author>Drabik, Mikul&#225;&#353;, 1588-1671. aut</author>
      <author>Comenius, Johann Amos, 1592-1670.</author>
      <author>Codrington, Robert, 1601-1665.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <editionStmt>
      <edition>The second edition corrected and amended.</edition>
    </editionStmt>
    <extent>[4], 115 p., [1] leaf of plates : ill.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Robert Pawlet</persName> at <placeName>the sign of the Bible in Chancery-lane, near the Inner-Temple Gate</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1664.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of: Lux in tenebris.</note>
      <note>The words "Christopher .. Drabicius." are bracketed together on title page.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: Prophesies of the Turke, Emperour, Pope, and France.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Robert Pawlet</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the sign of the Bible in Chancery-lane, near the Inner-Temple Gate</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
