<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The royall martyr. Or, King Charles the First no man of blood but a martyr for his people Being a brief account of his actions from the beginnings of the late unhappy warrs, untill he was basely butchered to the odium of religion, and scorn of all nations, before his pallace at White-Hall, Jan. 30. 1648. To which is added, A short history of His Royall Majesty Charles the Second, King of England, Scotland, France, and Ireland, defender of the faith, &amp;c. third monarch of Great Brittain.</title>
         <title>King Charles the First, no man of blood: but a martyr for his people.</title>
         <author>Philipps, Fabian, 1601-1690.</author>
         <author>W.H.B.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8], 224 [i.e. 222] p., plate : ports. (woodcut)  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed for Henry Bell, and are to be sold by most book sellers,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1660.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>By Fabian Philipps.</note>
         <note>Dedication signed: W.H.B.</note>
         <note>The first leaf is blank.</note>
         <note>"An exact list of the names of those pretended judges" and "A short history of His Royall Majesty" each have separate dated title page; pagination and register are continuous.</note>
         <note>Originally published in 1649 as: King Charles the First, no man of blood: but a martyr for his people.</note>
         <note>Errors in paging; some pages printed and bound out of order.</note>
         <note>Imperfect: NNUT copy lacks pp. [7]-[8]; pp. [5]-[6] torn.</note>
         <note>Copy at reel 1139:29 appears as Wing B243 (number cancelled in CD ROM, 1996).</note>
         <note>Reproductions of originals at the University of Illinois (Urbana-Champaign Campus) . Library (reel 1139:29) and the Union Theoligcal Seminary Library, New York (reel 2109:7).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
