<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Margariton A rich treasure discovered of problemes and their resolves. In three parts. Amorous. Naturall Morall and politique. Faithfully translated out of French, for the profit and delight of the ingenious English of both sexes; to serve as a usefull helpe in their discourse.</title>
      <title>Delectable demaundes, and pleasaunt questions, with their severall aunswers, in matters of love, naturall causes, with morall and politique devises.</title>
      <author>Landi, Ortensio, ca. 1512-ca. 1553. Quattro libri di dubbi. English. Adaptations.</author>
      <author>Painter, William, 1540?-1594.</author>
      <author>T. S.</author>
      <author>Rawlins, Thomas, 1620?-1670, engraver.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[24], 307, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">B. Alsop.</persName> and <persName type="printer">T[homas]. F[awcet].</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Daniel Frere</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop, at the Red Bull in little Britaine</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1640">1640.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Based on the first three books of "Quattro libri di dubbi" by Ortensio Landi, probably through the French translation "Questions diverses" (Lyon, 1558). Wrongly attributed to Alain Chartier.</note>
      <note>Originally published in English in 1566 as: Delectable demaundes, and pleasaunt questions, with their severall aunswers, in matters of love, naturall causes, with morall and politique devises.</note>
      <note>Translated by William Painter. STC's attribution of translation of "T.S.", who signs the new foreword, is in error.</note>
      <note>Fawcet's name from STC.</note>
      <note>With an additional title page, engraved, with imprint "London printed for D: Frere. 1640", signed: TR fer:, i.e. Thomas Rawlins.</note>
      <note>The first leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>Copy at 2082 lacks blank leaf.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Folger Shakespeare Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Daniel Frere</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>B. Alsop.</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>T[homas]. F[awcet].</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop, at the Red Bull in little Britaine</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
