<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>M. Perkins, his Exhortation to repentance, out of Zephaniah preached in 2. sermons in Sturbridge Faire. Together with two treatises of the duties and dignitie of the ministrie: deliuered publiquely in the Vniuersitie of Cambridge. With a preface pr&#230;fixed touching the publishing of all such workes of his as are to be expected: with a catalogue of all the perticulers [sic] of them, diligently perused and published, by a preacher of the word.</title>
      <author>Perkins, William, 1558-1602.</author>
      <author>Crashaw, William, 1572-1626.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[32], 101, [19], 184 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>imprinted by <persName type="printer">T. C[reede].</persName> for <persName type="publisher">William Welby</persName>, and are to bee sold at <placeName>his shop in Pauls Church-yard, at the signe of the Grey-hound</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1605">1605.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>With a dedication signed: William Crashaw, and including: 'The second treatise of the duties and dignities of the ministerie' by William Perkins, with a divisional titlepage, separate pagination and register and a dedication signed: W. Crashawe.</note>
      <note>Collation of 'Exhortation': A * B-G H&#8308; of which sigs. A1-2, *4 and *8 are blanks.</note>
      <note>Printer from STC (2nd ed.).</note>
      <note>Marginal notes.</note>
      <note>Copy filmed at UMI microfilm Early English Books 1475-1640 reel 2014 lacks 8 preliminary pages to second part.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Cambridge University Library, England.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>William Welby</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>T. C[reede].</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop in Pauls Church-yard, at the signe of the Grey-hound</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
