<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The free customes, benefits and priviledges of the copyhold tennants, of the mannors of Stepny and Hackny in the countie of Middlesex within this composition Before which is prefixed an abstract or briefe relation of the assurance given by the Right Honorable Thomas Lord Wentworth lord of both the said mannors, vnto his lordships said tennants (within this composition) for the ratifying and perpetuall establishing of the same. Whereunto two tables alphabeticall are fitted, the one containing the names of the said copyhold tenants, now hauing compounded: the other (with the marginall notes in the booke) serueth for the ready finding of any note worthy matter herein contained.</title>
      <title>Auncient severall customes, of the severall mannors of Stebbunhuth, and Hackney, 1587.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 70, 70-88 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">William Iones</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1617">1617.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Caption title on p. 1: An abstract of the indenture of covenants.</note>
      <note>"Anno. 21. Jacobi regis." (caption title) has separate register; pagination is continuous.</note>
      <note>Another edition, revised and enlarged, of "The auncient severall customes, of the severall mannors of Stebbunhuth, and Hackney, 1587", London, ca. 1610 (STC 23252); another issue of STC 23254, with additions: Memorandum, ... An acte for confirmationof the copyhold estates and customes ... of Stepny and Hackney.'--STC.</note>
      <note>Text is continuous despite pagination.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library, London, England.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>William Iones</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
