<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The portraiture of the image of God in man In his three estates, of creation. Restauration. Glorification. Digested into two parts. The first containing, the image of God both in the body and soule of man, and immortality of both: with a description of the severall members of the body, and the two principall faculties of the soule, the understanding and the will; in which consisteth his knowledge, and liberty of his will. The second containing, the passions of man in the concupiscible and irascible part of the soule: his dominion ouer the creatures; also a description of his active and contemplative life; with his conjunct or married estate. Whereunto is annexed an explication of sundry naturall and morall observations for the clearing of divers Scriptures. All set downe by way of collation, and cleared by sundry distinctions, both out of the schoolemen, and moderne writers. The third edition, corrected and enlarged. By I. Weemse, of Lathocker in Scotland, preacher of Christs Gospel.</title>
      <author>Weemes, John, 1579?-1636.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[28], 283, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">T[homas] C[otes]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Iohn Bellamie</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>the signe of the three Golden Lyons in Cornehill, neere the Royall Exchange</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1636.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>The words "creation. Restauration. Glorification." are bracketed together on title page.</note>
      <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
      <note>Intended to be issued with STC 25216.5. Usually found as part of STC 25208 or 25209.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Iohn Bellamie</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>T[homas] C[otes]</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the signe of the three Golden Lyons in Cornehill, neere the Royall Exchange</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
