<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>An exposition of the lawes of Moses Viz. Morall. Ceremoniall. Iudiciall. The second volume. Containing an explanation of diverse questions and positions for the right understanding thereof. Wherein also are opened divers ancient rites &amp; customes of the Iewes, and also of the Gentiles, as they haue relation to the Iewish. Together with an explication of sundry difficult texts of Scripture, which depend upon, or belong unto every one of the Commandements, as also upon the ceremoniall and iudiciall lawes. Which texts are set downe in the tables before each particular booke. All which are cleered out of the originall languages, the Hebrew and Greeke, and out of the distinctions of the schoolemen and cases of the casuists. / By Iohn Weemse, of Lathocker in Scotland, preacher of Gods Word.</title>
         <title>Works. v. 3</title>
         <author>Weemes, John, 1579?-1636.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[34], 261, [29], 221, [32], 188, [3] p. : ill. (woodcuts)  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by Iohn Dawson [and Thomas Cotes] for Iohn Bellamie, and are to be sold at his shoppe at the signe of the three Golden Lyons in Cornehill, neere the Royall Exchange,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1632">1632.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Volume 3 of the "Workes".</note>
         <note>A reissue, with added general title page (printed as *4 of part 2), of "An explanation of the ceremoniall lawes of Moses, as they are annexed to the Tenne commandements" (STC 25213a, printed by Thomas Cotes) and "An explication of the judiciall lawes of Moses" (STC 25214).</note>
         <note>Includes indexes.</note>
         <note>With a final addendum leaf.</note>
         <note>Includes: Exercitations divine: London, 1632.</note>
         <note>Each part also appears cataloged separately elsewhere.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the University of Illinois (Urbana-Champaign Campus). Library.</note>
         <note>An explanation of the ceremoniall lavves of Moses, as they are annexed to the Tenne Commandements. T. Cotes for Iohn Bellamie, 1632 (STC 2nd ed. 25213a) -- An explication of the iudiciall lawes of Moses. Iohn Dawson for Iohn Bellamie, 1632 (STC 2nd ed. 25214) -- Exercitations divine containing questions and solutions for the right understanding of the Scriptures (STC 2nd ed. 25212).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
