<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A briefe declaration for vvhat manner of speciall nusance concerning private dwelling houses, a man may have his remedy by assise, or other action as the case requires Vnfolded in the arguments, and opinions of foure famous sages of the common law; together with the power, and extent of customes in cities, townes, and corporations, concerning the same: together with the determination of the law, concerning the commodity, and use of houses, and their appurtenances. Whereunto is added, the iustices of assise their opinion, concerning statute law for parishes, and the power of iustices of peace, church wardens, and constables; and to know what they are to doe concerning bastards borne in their parishes, reliefe of the poore, and providing for poore children, what remedy for the same.</title>
         <author>Monson, Robert, d. 1583.</author>
         <author>Plowden, Edmund, 1518-1585.</author>
         <author>Wray, Christopher, Sir, 1524-1592.</author>
         <author>Manwood, John, d. 1610.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 45, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed [by Bernard Alsop and Thomas Fawcet] for William Cooke, and are to be sold at his shop, neere Furnivals-Inne gate in Holbourne,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1636">1636.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>The "four famous sages" are Robert Monson, Edmund Plowden, Sir Christopher Wray, and John Manwood.</note>
         <note>Printers' names from STC.</note>
         <note>In this edition the text begins on B2r.</note>
         <note>Identified as STC 6453 on UMI microfilm reel 1269.</note>
         <note>Reproductions of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
         <note>Appears at reel 1269 and at reel 1955 (same copy filmed twice).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
