<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Die Sabbati 15. Junii. 1644. An ordinance of the Lords and Commons assembled in Parliament. For continuance of the former ordinance for four moneths longer, from the time of the expiration of the said ordinance, for the raising, maintaining, paying, and regulating of 3000. foot, 1200. horse, and 500. dragoons, to be commanded by Sir William Waller, as Serjeant Major Generall of the said forces, under his Excellency the Earl of Essex, in whose absence he is to be commander in chief over them, and all other forces raised, or to be raised in the associated counties of Southampton, Surrey, Sussex, and Kent. The Lords and Commons in Parliament assembled, do ordaine and declare, and it be ordained and declared, that the ordinance intituled, An ordinance for the raising, maintaining, paying and regulating of 3000. foot, 1200 horse, and 500. dragoones, to be commanded by Sir William Waller as Serjeant Major Generall of the said forces under his excellency the Earle of Essex Generall, and of all other forces, raised, or to be raised in the associated counties of Southampton, Surrey, Sussex, and Kent, and every clause, article, and thing therein contained, shall have continuance for and during the spoace of 4 moneths longer from the time of the expiration of the said Ordainance</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>15-18 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>s.n.,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1644">1644]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Place of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>Signatures: C&#178; .</note>
      <note>Also issued as part of Wing E1772.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "June 17. 1644".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
