<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Seasonable observations on a late book intitvled A system of the law: as it was contrived and published by the committee appointed for regulation: so far as it relates to the high Court of Chancery, and the fees and proceedings thereof: Wherein several proposals made by the said committee, are held unsafe and inconvenient; some are approved of, and illustrated; and others supplyed wherein the same are conceived defective: With further proposals, for the better regulation of said court, and more speedy and cheap hearing of causes. And an exact table. 1. Containing the fees now paid to the grand officers and patentees. 2. How much will satisfie the true labourers. 3. What wil [sic] be saved thereby to all suiters in the said court. Unto which is likewise annexed, the memorable case put by the late King James, to the then learned judges of the land, touching the power and jurisdiction of the said court, for relieving complainants after judgements given in the Courts of Common-Law; and how far the Statutes of Pr&#230;munire do extend to restrain the said court therein: With the reasons and resolutions of the said judges thereupon: Tendered to the consideration of the supreme authority: and published for the general good and information of all practitioners and suiters in the said court. / By Philostratus Philodemius.</title>
      <author>Philodemius, Philostratus.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8], 62 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">R.W.</persName> and are to sold by <persName type="bookseller">Edw. Dod</persName>, and <persName type="bookseller">Nath. Ekins</persName>, at <placeName>the Gun in Ivie-Lane.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1653">1653.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>R.W.</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Edw. Dod</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Nath. Ekins</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Gun in Ivie-Lane.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
