<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
<<<<<<< HEAD
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A Faithfull searching home vvord, intended for the view of the remaining members of the former old Parliament in the time of their late second sitting at Westminster. Shewing the reasonableness and justness of their first dissolution, as also the dangerous rock they formerly split upon, that so they might learn to beware for the future: But being a second time dissolved upon the like account, as so many fruitless trees twic dead plucked up by the roots. It is now presented to the officers of the army as another looking-glass wherein they may plainly see, how woefully they also have dissembled, dealt treacherously, deceitfully and wickedly both with God and man, in having so greatly apostatized from, rejected, trodden under foot, persecuted, Judas-like betrayed, and as it were crucified and kept down in the grave (as the soldiers formerly did Christ) that blessed cause and those good principles, they once so highly pretended to own ... Together with an other seasonable word by way of counsel and proposal to the aforesaid officers of the armies of England, Scotland, and Ireland. All which, is also to be seen, and read of all men loving righteousness, that thereby they may (with the army) better know how to chuse the good, refute the evil, and rightly steer their course, and bend their spirits in the future, for the exaltation of Christ, his cause, and interest, and against all the apostacy and treachery, though never so refined, that may further appear in this gloomy, dark, overturning day.</title>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>44 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>s.n.],</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1659">Printed in the first year of the army's endeavouring to deal treacherously with the faithful friends of the cause a second time, after their first and second dissolution of the late long Parliament, 1659.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Place of publication suggested by Wing.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
=======
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A Faithfull searching home vvord, intended for the view of the remaining members of the former old Parliament in the time of their late second sitting at Westminster. Shewing the reasonableness and justness of their first dissolution, as also the dangerous rock they formerly split upon, that so they might learn to beware for the future: But being a second time dissolved upon the like account, as so many fruitless trees twic dead plucked up by the roots. It is now presented to the officers of the army as another looking-glass wherein they may plainly see, how woefully they also have dissembled, dealt treacherously, deceitfully and wickedly both with God and man, in having so greatly apostatized from, rejected, trodden under foot, persecuted, Judas-like betrayed, and as it were crucified and kept down in the grave (as the soldiers formerly did Christ) that blessed cause and those good principles, they once so highly pretended to own ... Together with an other seasonable word by way of counsel and proposal to the aforesaid officers of the armies of England, Scotland, and Ireland. All which, is also to be seen, and read of all men loving righteousness, that thereby they may (with the army) better know how to chuse the good, refute the evil, and rightly steer their course, and bend their spirits in the future, for the exaltation of Christ, his cause, and interest, and against all the apostacy and treachery, though never so refined, that may further appear in this gloomy, dark, overturning day.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>44 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>s.n.],</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
      <date>Printed in the first year of the army's endeavouring to deal treacherously with the faithful friends of the cause a second time, after their first and second dissolution of the late long Parliament, 1659.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Place of publication suggested by Wing.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
>>>>>>> imprintparse
</sourceDesc>
