<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Happy news to England sent from Oxford. 1. The joyfull hopes of a peace, and of an accomodation that is to be made between the King and his Parliament. 2. The Kings intentions to come to his high Court of Parliament. 3. The preparations that is made for his Majesties comming to White Hall, and the store of provisions of wine and other things that is laid in there for his entertainment. 4. The names of those lords that are nominated to goe to his Majesty with the answer to his late propositions, and to know who his Majesty will nominate and appoint for the accomodation and treaty, and the place where. 5. The security and hostage which is offered by foure noblemen, and also by their estates for the Kings security there and his safe returne to his court at Oxford, if in case the Parliament and his Majesty doth not agree. 6. His Majesties returning to London is suddainely expected, will under God make all those lying astronomers and deceivers, which prophesied of a great battaile prove false and counterfeit.</title>
         <author>Alsted, Johann Heinrich, 1588-1638.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8] p. : ill.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>s.n.],</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1643">Printed 1642 [i.e. 1643]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Attributed to Johann Heinrich Alsted. cf. NUC pre-1956.</note>
         <note>Place of publication from Wing.</note>
         <note>Signatures: A&#8308;.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Lond: feb: 17:".</note>
         <note>Woodcut illustration of horse and rider (representing Charles I?) verso of last leaf, filmed with with E.89[30] following.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
