<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Anglia liberata, or, The rights of the people of England, maintained against the pretences of the Scotish King, as they are set forth in an Answer to the Lords Ambassadors propositions of England. Which ansvver was delivered into the Great Assembly of the United Provinces at the Hague, by one Mac-Donnel, who entitles himself Resident for his Majesty, &amp;c. June 28/18 1651: and is here published according to the Dutch copy. Whereto is added a translation of certain animadversions upon the answer of Mac-Donnel. Written by an ingenious Dutch-man. As also an additional reply to all the pretended arguments, insinuations and slanders, set forth in the said Scotish answer written a while since by a private pen, and now presented to the publick.</title>
         <author>MacDonnell, William, Sir.</author>
         <author>Ingenious Dutch-man.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[4], 68 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by T. Newcomb [and Samuel Brown] for Richard Lowns, at the White Lion in Pauls Church-yard near the west end,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1651">1651.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>"An answer to the propositions made by the English Ambassadors .. Hagh, printed by Samuel Brown, English book-seller, 1651" and "Animadversions upon a certain Scottish answer" each have separate dated title page; pagination and register are continuous.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "October. 7.".</note>
         <note>Identified as Wing M119 on UMI microfilm set "Early English Books, 1641-1700".</note>
         <note>Reproductions of the originals in Cambridge University Library (Early English books) and the British Library (Thomason Tracts).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
