<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Ishmael, and his mother, cast out into the wilderness, amongst the wild beasts of the same nature: or, a reply to a book entitulled, The scriptures proved to be the word of God, put forth by one of Ishmaels children, who calls himself a minister of the Gospel, and a pastor of S. Austins and Savours parish in Norwich; but is clearly made manifest by the light of God in his servants, to be a scoffer, and an enemy to the Gospel, which the saints of God are ministers of, and sufferers for, by such as hee is, who Ishmael-like, hath laid his folly open, and is discovered to the faithful, who are of Abraham, and of the seed of promise. Also, a cleer distinction between the minsters of Christ, who are of the seed of Abraham, and the priests of this generation, who are of Ishmaels root; who with the truth are plainly made manifest, by the light of Christ in us, who for the testimony of God do suffer by the sons of Hagar, and this generation of priests in Notwich [sic]: ... / Given forth from the spirit of the Lord in us that do suffer in the goal of Norwich for the truths sake, ... Christopher Atkinson, George Whitehead, Iames Lancaster, Thomas Simonds.</title>
      <author>Atkinson, Christopher.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 13, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Giles Calvert</persName>, at <placeName>the black Spread-Eagle, at the west end of Pauls</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Londou [sic] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1655">1655.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A reply to: Townsend, Sampson.  The Scriptures proved to be the word of God.</note>
      <note>Annotation in Thomason copy: "March. 12.", "1654"; 5 in imprint date crossed out.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Giles Calvert</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the black Spread-Eagle, at the west end of Pauls</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
