<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Prosperous proceedings in Ireland: being a remonstrance, or exact relation of the most distressed estate of the inhabitants of Galloway, Arrowmoore, and Baltimoore, when that worthy captaine Captaine Thomas Ashley, Captaine of the imployment of London first arrived there; shewing the most inhumane, unparaleld crueltie of the rebells to the protestants, nurthering them in the open streets. As also, shewing the happie successe God hath given him, in defeating the Rebells, by taking of castles from them, with many hundred head of cattell, for the reliefe of the poore distressed Protestants. As was certified to the Honorable Houses of Parliament (the 15. of October 1642.) by three certificates, under the hands of divers of the gentry and clergie, inhabiting within the said places (whose names are within mentioned) presented as a meanes of his continuance for the further defence of the aforesaid places, with all his successefull proceedings since his first arrivall to the present. All which good services were thankfully accepted of both Houses of Parliament, and desired to be printed.</title>
      <author>Ashley, Thomas, 17th cent, attributed name.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>8 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">John Hancocke</persName>, in <placeName>Burchen-lane at the signe of the Bible</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>October 19. 1642.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Attributed to Thomas Ashley by Wing.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>John Hancocke</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Burchen-lane at the signe of the Bible</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
