<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Basilius Valentinus, monk, of the Order of St. Bennet: his last will and testament Which being alone, he hid under a table of marble, behinde the high-altar of the Cathedral Church, in the Imperial City of Erford: leaving it there to be found by him, whom Gods providence should make worthy of it. Wherein, he sufficiently, declares the wayes he wrought to obtain the philosophers stone: which he taught unto his fellow collegians, so that they all attained the said philosophers stone, whereby not onely the leprous bodies of the impure, and inferior metals are reduced unto the pure and perfect body of gold and silver, but also all manner of diseases whatsoever are cured in the bodies of unhealthfull men, and kept thereby in perfect health unto the prolonging of their lives. A work long expected.</title>
      <author>Basilius Valentinus.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[24], 175, [7], 39, [3], 25, [3], 21, [3], 9, [3], 23, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">W.B.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">T. Davis</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop in St. Pauls Church-yard at the signe of the Bible over against the little North door</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1658">1658.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"The second part of the last testament", "The fourth part of Basilius Valentinus", "Basilius Valentinus his XII. keyes", "A short way and repition of former writings", "The fifth and last part of the last testament" and "Basilius Valentinus his treatise concerning microcosme" each have separate title pages dated 1656 and most have separate pagination; register is continuous.</note>
      <note>Wing reports title as "Basilius Valentinus Friar of the Order ...".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Glasgow University Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>T. Davis</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>W.B.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop in St. Pauls Church-yard at the signe of the Bible over against the little North door</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
