<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The arrovv of the Almighty shot out of the creatures bowe, against the uncalled ministers in England. Or, A messages sent to them to forewarn them of their determined destruction, before it fall upon them. Likewise here is shewed, from whence they had their calling into the ministery; and how all people have been decieved by them. Here is also a glass wherein all formalists may see their own deformity, and so seek after that which is the substance, wherein all their deformity shall be done away. Likewise here is opened the mystery of the Lords Supper, and the mystery in Baptism; and how there is a threefold Baptism, having relation to the three fold name of Father, Son, and Holy Ghost; with other truths very needful to be known. All of them being laid down in as brief a manner as possiblemay be, for the use and instruction of the Presbyterians, Independants, and Anabaptists, so called; or for the good of all others who have a minde to seek God in a right way; and in the conclusion, a word to the free-gracians. By Geo. Baitman.</title>
      <author>Baiteman, George.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[16], 122 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">R.I.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">William Hutcheson</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop in the City of Durham.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1653">1653.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Sept: 9th".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>William Hutcheson</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>R.I.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop in the City of Durham.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
