<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The storming of Antichrist, in his two last and strongest garrisons; of compulsion of conscience, and infants babptisme [sic]. Wherein is set down a way and manner for cburch [sic] constitution; together with markes to know right constituted churches, from all other societies in the world. Also the cruelty inequality and injustice of compulsion for conscience, by 29. arguments is opened; with an answer to 26. objections brought for the same. Also 12. arguments against the baptizing of infants; with an answer to 26. objections brought for the same. Wherein is displayed to the view of all, from the testimonies of Scriptures, Fathers, councels; the mischiefs, uncertainties, novelties, and absudities [sic] that do attend the same. Wherein is answered the most valid arguments brought by St. Martiall, in his sermon preached in the Abbey Church at Westminister, for the defence hereof. With an answer to Mr. Blake his arguments, in his book cald Birth-priviledge; and to the arguments of divers others. As also a catechisme, wherein is cleerely opened the doctrine of baptisme, together with a resolution of divers questions and cases of conscience, about baptisme. Written by Ch. Blackwood, out of his earnest desire he hath to a thorow reformation, having formerly seen the mischiefs of half reformations.</title>
         <author>Blackwood, Christopher.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[4], 35 [i.e. 39], [1], 68 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>s.n.],</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
         <date>Printed Anno 1644. Being one of those years, wherein Antichrist threatned the storming of the churches.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>In part a reply to "A sermon of the baptizing of infants" by Stephen Marshall and "Infants baptisme, freed from Antichristianisme" by Thomas Blake.</note>
         <note>Place of publication from Wing.</note>
         <note>P. 39 is misnumbered 35; quire e is irregularly paginated.</note>
         <note>Signatures: *²  a-e⁴ A⁴(-A1) B-H⁴ I² .</note>
         <note>"The storming of Antichrist .. The second part." begins new pagination on A2r.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "London. Decemb: 28th 1644".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
