<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The covenant sealed. Or, A treatise of the sacraments of both covenants, polemicall and practicall. Especially of the sacraments of the covenant of grace. In which, the nature of them is laid open, the adæquate subject is largely inquired into, respective to right and proper interest. to fitnesse for admission to actual participation. Their necessity is made known. Their whole use and efficacy is set forth. Their number in Old and New Testament-times is determined. With several necessary and useful corollaries. Together with a brief answer to Reverend Mr. Baxter's apology, in defence of the treatise of the covenant. / By Thomas Blake, M.A. pastor of Tamworth, in the counties of Stafford and Warwick.</title>
         <author>Blake, Thomas, 1597?-1657.</author>
         <author>Cartwright, Christopher, 1602-1658.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[20], 668, [16] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed for Abel Roper, at the Sun against Dunstans Church in Fleet-street,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
         <date>1655.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Preface signed: Christopher Cartwright.</note>
         <note>In part a reply to: Baxter, Richard.  Rich. Baxters apology against the modest exceptions of Mr. T. Blake and the digression of Mr. G. Kendall.</note>
         <note>Title page in red and black.</note>
         <note>The words 'to right .. actual participation.' are linked to 'respective' using a left bracket.</note>
         <note>"A postscript to reverend and learned Master Baxter, .. printed by S.G. for Abel Roper" has separate dated title page; register and pagination are continuous.</note>
         <note>Includes index.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "July 7".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
