<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The arraignment of errour: or, A discourse serving as a curb to restrain the wantonnesse of mens spirits in the entertainment of opinions; and as a compasse, whereby we may sail in the search and finding of truth; distributed into six main questions. Quest. 1. How it may stand with Gods, with Satans, with a mans own ends, that there should be erroneous opinions? Quest. 2. What are the grounds of abounding errours? Quest. 3. Why so many are carried away with errour? Quest. 4. Who those are that are in danger? Quest. 5. What are the examens, or the trials of opinions, and characters of truth? Quest. 6. What waies God hath left in his Word for the suppressing of errour, and reducing of erroneous persons? Under which generall questions, many other necessary and profitable queries are comprized, discussed, and resolved. And in conclusion of all; some motives, and means, conducing to an happy accommodation of our present differences, are subjoyned. / By Samuel Bolton minister of the Word of God at Saviours-Southwark.</title>
      <author>Bolton, Samuel, 1606-1654.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[20], 360 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">G. Miller</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Andrew Kembe</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop at the Talbot gate in Southwark</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1646">M.DC.XLVI. [1646]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Jan: 24 1645"; the I in imprint date crossed out.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Andrew Kembe</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>G. Miller</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop at the Talbot gate in Southwark</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
