<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Of Christs testaments, viz: baptisme and the Supper. Written in two bookes. The 1. of holy Baptisme, how it is to be understood in the ground thereof, and why a Christian should be baptised. The 2. of the holy supper of the Lord Christ, what it is, with the benefit and effects of it, and how the same may be worthily participated of. And how these are to be understood, both according to the Old and New Testament. Set forth from the true theosophicall ground, through the three principles of the divine revelation, and presented to the children of God for the information of their understandings. / Written in the yeare of Christ 1624. by Jacob Behm of Old Seidenberg alias Teutonicus Philosophus. And Englished by John Sparrovv, barrister of the Inner Temple London.</title>
         <title>Von Christi Testamenten. English</title>
         <author>B&#246;hme, Jakob, 1575-1624.</author>
         <author>Sparrow, John, 1615-1665?</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[25], 23, 23, 24-75, [11] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by M. Simmons, and are to be sold neare the signe of the Golden Lyon in Aldersgate-streete, or by H. Blunden at the Castle in Cornhill neere the Exchange,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1652">1652.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A translation of: Von Christi Testamenten.</note>
         <note>"The second booke. Concerning the holy supper of our Lord Jesus Christ" has separate dated title page; register and pagination are continuous.</note>
         <note>Pages 1-23: opposite pages bear duplicate numbering.</note>
         <note>Includes index.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "may. 22".</note>
         <note>Reproductions of the originals in the Yale University Library and the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
