<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Several treatises of vvorship &amp; ceremonies, by the Reverend Mr. William Bradshaw, one of the first Fellows of Sydney Colledge in Cambridge; afterward minister of Chattam in Kent, 1601. Known by his learned treatise De justificatione. 1. A consideration of certain positions archiepiscopal. 2. A treatise of divine worship, tending to prove the ceremonies, imposed on the ministers of the Gospel in England, in present controversie, are in their use unlawful. Printed 1604. 3. A treatise of the nature and use of things indifferent. 1605. 4. English Puritanism, containing the main opinions of the ridgedest sort of those called Puritans in the realm of England. 1604. 5. Twelve general arguments, proving the ceremonies unlawful. 1605. 6. A proposition concerning kneeling in the very act of receiving, 1605. 7. A protestation of the Kings supremacy, made in the name of the afflicted ministers, and oposed to the shameful calumniations of the prelates. 1605. 8. A short treatise of the cross in baptism.</title>
      <author>Bradshaw, William, 1571-1618.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8], 95, [[1], 103-104, 102-122 p., [1] folded leaf   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Cambridge</persName> and <persName type="publisher">Oxford, and to be</persName> sold in <placeName>Westminster Hall</placeName>, and <persName type="publisher">Pauls Church-Yard</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1660">1660.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Place of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>"A consideration of certain positions archiepiscopal" and "A treatise of divine vvorship" each have caption title; "A treatise of the nature &amp; use of things indifferent", "English puritanism", "Twelve general arguments", "A protestation of the Kings supremacy", "A proposition concerning kneeling in the very act of receiving", and "A short treatise of the Crosse in baptisme" each have separate dated title page; register and pagination are continuous throughout.</note>
      <note>The folded leaf bears advertisements.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Sept. 11.".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Cambridge</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Oxford, and to be</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Pauls Church-Yard</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Westminster Hall</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
