<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>With the light is fifteen priests, (of the Isle of Wight reproved, who have joyned and subscribed their names together, (and printed) in publike view, declaring themselves to be ministers of Christ; yet confessing and largely demonstrating that they are dark sinful sinners of the Gentiles, living in obscurity, chained up in a cave of darkness, their light eclipsed, their eyes dim, their sloath great, their hearts begin to gather blackness, and are seised on with fear, and that their authority in preaching is marred by unholy living, and that the greatest misteries of their religion have been squeesed out of the writings of heathens. ... Ro. Tuchin. Robert Dingley. Vincent Spark. Thomas Clark. William Bignel. John Barnes, James Craswick. Joshua Tomkins. William Harby. Ric. Beminster. Edward Bucklar. John Martin. Simon Pole. Martin Wells. Mathew Hearn. / Given forth as a true testimony from the hand of one of the meanest servants of the eternal living truth, against a rebellious seed of evil and deceitful workers, that cannot cease from sin, whose mouthes are to be stopt, under whom this body in vvhich I am, suffers bonds, tryals, and tribulations, for the testimony of Jesus, and of a pure conscience, though in a filthy noysome prison, the common jaile, and stinking dungeon and house of correction, (vvith other of the friends of Christ at Winchester: I ha[v]e suffered a close and cruel imprisonment well nigh seven months, but Father forgive them that hate me without cause, and know me by no other name then Daniel Baker.</title>
         <author>D. B. (Daniel Baker), fl. 1650-1660.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 30 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>In the 12th. month for Mary Westwood.,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London printed, :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1658">1658.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>The letter "v" of "have" on t.p. was printed upside-down.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the Friends' Library, London.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
