<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A certaine warning from a naked heart before the Lord, to the earthly, wise, great, and honourable men, and inhabitants of the earth, and to all among them, without respect of persons, that know not the rocke of ages, the light, the higher power, the sure foundation, the truth, the way, the life, which is the grace that brings salvation that appeares to all men, as saith the Scripture, Titus 2.11. : With a quick loud thundring alarum, sounded in the holy mountaine, of the Lords house of holinesse that the inhabitants and great men of the earth might be awakened, and tremble, and cease from idolitry, and prepare to meet the mighty God, the everlasting light and life of men, who sheweth to man what is his secret thoughts, Amos 4.12,13. : Given forth from the hand of a freind [sic] to the whole creation, and of precious soules (of the sons and daughters of men without respect of persons) that lyeth under the bondage of corruption, a freind [sic] and servant to him that's arising to smite the earth with the rod of his mouth. / Daniel Baker.</title>
      <author>D. B. (Daniel Baker), fl. 1650-1660.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>8 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>For <persName type="publisher">M.W.</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1659">1659]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Caption title.</note>
      <note>Imprint suggested by Wing.</note>
      <note>"London, from the hole in the Poultrey Counter this 30th of the 8th month and first day of the week. 59"--P. 8.</note>
      <note>Imperfect: repair overlay possibly obscures text on lower portion of p. 8.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Friends' Library, London.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>M.W.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
