<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Four books on the eleventh of Matthew: viz: I. Christ inviting sinners to come to him for rest. II. Christ the great teacher of souls that come to him. To which is added a treatise of meekness and of anger. III. Christ the humble teacher of those that come to him. IIII. The only easie way to heaven. By Jeremiah Burroughs, preacher of the Gospel at Stepny and Cripple-Gate, London.</title>
      <author>Burroughs, Jeremiah, 1599-1646.</author>
      <author>Goodwin, Thomas, 1600-1680.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[28], 394; [24], 477, [12], 478-775, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">Peter Cole, printer and</persName> book-seller, and are to be sold at <placeName>the sign of the Printing-Press in Cornhill, near the Royall Exchange</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1659">1659.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"A testimony to the reader" signed: Thomas Goodwin [and 6 others].</note>
      <note>Vertical half-title preceding general title page reads "Mr Burroughs four books on Matthew". Vertical half-title preceding title page for part 3 reads "Mr Burroughs easie way to heaven".</note>
      <note>Part 1, "Christ inviting sinners to come to him for rest" has separate dated title page, pagination and register. Part 2, "The second book on Matth. 11.29", and part 3, "The third and fourth book, on Matthew 11", each have separate dated title page; pagination and register are continuous. The parts may also have been issued separately.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy E.963[2]: " Jan: 6th"; the 9 in the date has been crossed out and replaced with an 8; on Thomason copy E.964[1]: the 9 in imprint date has been crossed out; on Thomason copy E.965[1]: "1658 January"; the 9 in the imprint date has been crossed out and replaced with an "8".</note>
      <note>Part 1 = E.963[2]; part 2 = Thomason E.964[1]; part 3 = Thomason E.965[1].</note>
      <note>Part 1 = Wing B6060; parts 2 and 3 = B6116.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the British Library (Thomason Tracts), Harvard University Library (Early English books, reel 1378, part 1 only), and the William Andrews Clark Memorial Library (Early English books, reel 2204, parts 2-4 only).</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Peter Cole, printer and</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the sign of the Printing-Press in Cornhill, near the Royall Exchange</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
