<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A declaration of the sad and great persecution and martyrdom of the people of God, called Quakers, in New--England for the worshipping of God. Wherof 22 have been banished upon pain of death. 03 have been martyred. 03 have had their right-ears cut. 01 hath been burned in the hand with the letter H. 31 persons have received 650 stripes. 01 was beat while his body was like a jelly. Several were beat with pitched ropes. Five appeals made by them to England, were denied by the rulers of Boston. One thousand forty four pounds worth of goods hath been taken from them (being poor men) for meeting together in the fear of the Lord, and for keeping the commands of Christ. One now lyeth in iron-fetters, condemned to dye. Also, some considerations, presented to the King, which is in answer to a petition and address, which was presented unto him by the general court at Boston : subscribed by J. Endicot, the chief persecutor there; thinking thereby to cover themselves from the blood of the innocent.</title>
      <author>Burrough, Edward, 1634-1662.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>32 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Robert Wilson</persName>, in <placeName>Martins Le Grand</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1661">[1661]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Signed at end: E.B., i.e. Edward Burrough.</note>
      <note>Title page in red and black; the words "22 have been banished .. condemned to dye." are bracketed together.</note>
      <note>Publication date from Wing.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "March 30. 1661".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Robert Wilson</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Martins Le Grand</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
