<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>[Ba&#699;al-samz] or, Soveraigne balsome, gently applied in a few weighty considerations (by way of qu&#230;rie) for healing the distempers of such professors of religion as Satan hath wounded and drawn aside (under the notion of living in God) to the utter renouncing and casting off the use of divine ordinances, and Gospel-institutions of worship. With an apendix by way of postscript to such professors, wherein the most principall grounds upon which they build their practise, are fully answered and removed. And a catalogue of the errors that many of them hold since they left the ordinances, discovered. As also a true relation of Gods extraordinary working upon one of this way very lately in Plimouth, to the sight of his error, for the good of others published. / By Will. Bartlet, an unworthy minister of the Gospel, and lecturer at Bytheford in Devonshire.</title>
      <author>Bartlet, William, 1609 or 10-1682.</author>
      <author>M. P.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[12], 62, [6] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>by <persName type="printer">G. Dawson</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">Elizabeth Overton</persName> in <placeName>Popes-head Alley, neere the Royall Exchange</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1649.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>First word of title in xylographic Hebrew characters.</note>
      <note>The last three leaves contain "A catalogue of those (never enough to be abhorred opinions)", and "A true copy of a letter from Plimouth, February the 12" signed: M.P.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Aprill 5th".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Elizabeth Overton</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>G. Dawson</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Popes-head Alley, neere the Royall Exchange</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
