<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Ichnographia. Or A model of the primitive congregational way: wherein satisfaction is offered, by unfolding (according to the Scriptures) what the right order of the Gospel, and way of the saints in the visible worshipping of God is, in the dayes of the New Testament. And how the saints in these dayes may walk up to it, notwithstanding their present hindrances. Together with the maine points in controversie, touching the right visible church-state Christ hath instituted under the Gospel, with the extent of church-officers, and power of particular visible churches, and continuance of divine ordinances and institutions under the defection and apostasie of Antichrist. By W. Bartlet, Minister of the Gospel, at Wapping.</title>
      <author>Bartlet, William, 1609 or 10-1682.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[20], 144 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">W.E.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">H. Overton</persName>, at <placeName>the entrance into Popes-head Alley, out of Lumbard-street.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1647">1647.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>The first word of the title is printed in Greek characters.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "March 25".</note>
      <note>Imperfect: trimmed at fore-edge, affecting some page numbers and marginal notes.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>H. Overton</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>W.E.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the entrance into Popes-head Alley, out of Lumbard-street.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
