<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Sabbatum redivivum: or The Christian sabbath vindicated; in a full discourse concerning the sabbath, and the Lords day. Wherein, whatsoever hath been written of late for, or against the Christian sabbath, is exactly, but modestly examined: and the perpetuity of a sabbath deduced, from grounds of nature, and religious reason. / By Daniel Cawdrey, and Herbert Palmer: members of the Assembly of Divines. Divided into foure parts. 1. Of the decalogue in generall, and other laws of God, together with the relation of time to religion. 2. Of the fourth commandement of the decalogue in speciall. 3. Of the old sabbath, 4. Of the Lords day, in particular. The first part.</title>
      <title>Sabbatum redivivum. Part 1</title>
      <author>Cawdrey, Daniel, 1588-1664.</author>
      <author>Palmer, Herbert, 1601-1647.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[14], 368 [i.e. 384] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Robert White</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Vnderhill</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>the signe of the Bible in Woodstreete.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1645">1645.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Title page in red and black.</note>
      <note>The words "1. Of the decalogue ... Of the Lords day," and the words "Of the old sabbath, 4. Of the Lords day," are each bracketed together on title page, with "in particular" following the latter bracket.</note>
      <note>Parts 2-4, mentioned on the title page, were published in 1651, according to Thomason notation (Wing C1635).</note>
      <note>Page 384 misnumbered 368.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "May 1st.".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Vnderhill</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Robert White</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the signe of the Bible in Woodstreete.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
