<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The compleat midwifes practice, in the most weighty and high concernments of the birth of man. Containing perfect rules for midwifes and nurses, as also for women in their conception, bearing, and nursing of children: from the experience not onely of our English, but also the most accomplisht and absolute practicers among the French, Spanish, Italian, and other nations. A work so plain, that the weakest capacity may easily attain the knowledge of the whole art. With instructions of the midwife to the Queen of France (given to her daughter a little before her death) touching the practice of the said art. / Published with the approbation and good liking of sundry the most knowing professors of midwifery now living in the city of London, and other places. Illustrated with severall cuts in brass. By T.C. I.D. M.S. T.B. practitioners.</title>
         <author>Chamberlayne, Thomas.</author>
         <author>Boursier, Louise Bourgeois, ca. 1563-1636.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[16], 2, [2], 3-841, 94, [2], 95-108, [2] 109-126 p., [6] leaves of plates : port.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for Nathaniel Brooke at the Angell in Cornhill.,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1656">1656.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Attributed to Thomas Chamberlayne, who initials appear on title page.</note>
         <note>With engraved frontispiece depicting Louise Bourgeois Boursier, midwife to the Queen of France.</note>
         <note>Frontis. = plate.</note>
         <note>Text appears continuous despite pagination.</note>
         <note>P. 148 misnumbered 841.</note>
         <note>Leaf R8 is blank.</note>
         <note>There are 2 bifoliums in this item. The first, inserted following p.2, consists of an engraving of female anatomy on verso of first leaf and letterpress "Explanation of the first figure" on recto of second leaf; the second, inserted following p.108 (2nd sequence), consists of engraving of female and infant anatomy on verso of first leaf and letterpress "Explanation of the third figure" on recto of second leaf.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "May 12".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
