<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>His Majesties declaration to all his loving subjects, occasioned by a false and scandalous imputation laid upon His Majesty of an intention of raising or leavying war against his Parliament, and of having raised force to that end. Also, His Majesties declaration and profession, together with that of the Lords and others of his councell there present, disavowing any preparations or intentions of leavying war against his two Houses of Parliament.</title>
         <author>England and Wales. Sovereign (1625-1649 : Charles I)</author>
         <author>Charles I, King of England, 1600-1649.</author>
         <author>England and Wales Sovereign (1625-1649 : Charles I).</author>
         <author>England and Wales. Privy Council.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 13, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by Robert Barker, Printer to the Kings most Excellent Majestie: And by the Assignes of John Bill,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1642">1642.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>In response to: Certain propositions of both Houses of Parliament, concerning the raising of horse, horsemen, and arms, for the defence of the King, and both Houses of Parliament (Wing E1273).</note>
         <note>Includes "The Kings Majesties declaration and profession, disavowing any preparations or intentions in him, to levy warre against his two Houses of Parliament" (Wing C2181).</note>
         <note>Also published as items 2-4 of "His Maiesties proclamation and declaration to all his loving subjects, occasioned by a false and scandalous imputation laid upon His Maiesty, of an intention of raising or leavying war against his Parliament and of having raised force to that end" (Wing C2548).</note>
         <note>In this edition, lines 8-12 on page 7 are in roman type rather than black letter.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
