<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Cheshires successe since their pious and truly valiant collonell Sr. VVilliam Brereton barronet, came to their rescue. Set forth in 4. chapters; I. The battell at Namptwich, Jan. 28. II The battell at Torperley, Feb. 21. III. An account how the time was spent since Sir William's first advancing into the county, till the battell at Middlewich. IIII. The memorable battell at Middlewich, March 13. Confirmed by a letter sent from that industrious and faithfull collonell unto his deare friend in London: and a copy of the same unto an honourable member of the House of Commons and by the House ordered to be printed. Together with a catalogue of the names of the chiefe commanders that were taken prisoners at the said battell: which are 1. baronet, 1. collonell, 1. lievtenant collonell, 2. sergeant majors, 9. captaines, 6. lievtenants, 4. ensignes, 2. corporalls, 1. quartermaster, 2. canomers, 4. cornets colours 400. and odde prisoners; 2. brasse pieces 8. barrells of gunpowder, &amp;c. Whereunto is added a strange warrant, &amp;c. And certain newes of the great battell neare Stafford, much like Kyneton Battell.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[12] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>March 25. Printed for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Vnderhill</persName>, and are to be sold in <placeName>Wood-street</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>[1643]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Date of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>With accounts of military battles in Cheshire, a number of letters, and "A copie of a warrant sent abroad in Cheshire, from the chiefe agents for the king in that country, and which should have been put in strict execution, had not the good successe of valiant Sir William Breerton hindered it".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Vnderhill</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Wood-street</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
