<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Anti-Socinianism, or, A brief explication of some places of holy Scripture, for the confutation of certain gross errours, and Socinian heresies, lately published by William Pynchion, Gent. in a dialogue of his, called, The meritorious price of our redemption, concerning 1. Christ's suffering the wrath of God due to the elect. 2. God's imputation of sin to Christ. 3. The nature of the true mediatorial obedience of Christ. 4. The justification of a sinner. Also a brief description of the lives, and a true relation of the death, of the authors, promoters, propagators, and chief disseminators of this Socinian heresie, how it sprung up, by what means it spread, and when and by whom it was first brought into England, that so we be not deceived by it. / By N. Chewney, M.A. and minister of God's Word.</title>
      <author>Chewney, Nicholas, 1609 or 10-1685.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[6], 123, [9], 124-240 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">J.M.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">H. Twiford</persName>, and <persName type="publisher">T. Dring</persName>, and are to be sold in <placeName>Vine-Court</placeName>, <placeName>Middle Temple;</placeName> and at <placeName>the George in Fleetstreet, neer Cliffords Inn.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1656">1656.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>There is a separate dated title page after p. 123 which reads: Airesiarchai, or a cage of unclean birds; pagination is continuous.</note>
      <note>The first word of the title on the separate dated title page is printed in Greek characters.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Septemb: 16.".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>H. Twiford</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>T. Dring</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>J.M.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Middle Temple;</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Vine-Court</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the George in Fleetstreet, neer Cliffords Inn.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
