<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The wise taken in their craftiness, and their wisdom made manifest to be foolishness with God; and their actions discovered to be contrary to the pure law of righteousness given forth by the pure law-giver, Christ Jesus the light; by which light some one judge, or judges of this nation are made manifest, how he, or they have acted contrary to the law of God, and the law of this nation; and contrary to all the kings, rulers, and judges, spoken of in Scripture; by setting fines upon men, and sending them to prison till payment of the same, for not putting off their hats, and stand bare-headed before them in their court of assises, and goal-delivery. Also, here is shewed, that it is no sin for a man to stand with his hat on his head, before any emperor, king, ruler, judge, justice, or other magistrate, either alone, or in open court; neither is the putting the hat off, and standing, bare-headed before them, the honour that is due unto magistrates, which the Scripture speaks of. / VVritten by, me who am known by the name of Henry Clark.</title>
      <author>Clark, Henry, 17th cent.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 12 [i.e. 18]] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Giles Calvert</persName>, at <placeName>the Black spread-Eagle, neer the west end of Pauls</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1656">1656.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Pages 16-18 and misnumbered 9, 8, 12.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "June. 15".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Giles Calvert</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Black spread-Eagle, neer the west end of Pauls</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
