<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The civil magistrates povver in matters of religion modestly debated, impartially stated according to the bounds and grounds of scripture, and answer returned to those objections against the same which seem to have any weight in them. Together with A brief answer to a certain slanderous pamphlet called Ill news from New-England; or, a narrative of New-Englands persecution. By John Clark of Road-Island, physician. By Thomas Cobbet teacher of the church at Lynne in New-England. This treatise concerning the christian magistrates power, and the exerting thereof, in, and about matters of religion, written with much zeal and judgement by Mr. Cobbet of New-England, I doe allow to be printed; as being very profitable for these times. Feb. 7th. 1652. Obadiah Sedgwick.</title>
      <author>Cobbet, Thomas, 1608-1685.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[16], 108, 52 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">W. Wilson</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Philemon Stephens</persName> at <placeName>the Gilded Lion in Paul's Churchyard.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1653">1653.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A reply to: Clarke, John. Ill newes from New-England; or, a narrative of New-Englands persecution.</note>
      <note>"A brief answer to a scandalous pamphlet .." has separate pagination and register.</note>
      <note>"A brief answer to a scandalous pamphlet .." identified as Wing B4541 and Thomason E.687[3]; possibly also issued separately.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy E.687[2]: "ffebr. 15 1652."; the 3 in the date has been crossed out; annotation on Thomason copy E.687[3]: "Febr. 15.".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Philemon Stephens</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>W. Wilson</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Gilded Lion in Paul's Churchyard.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
