<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Clavis ad aperiendum carceris ostia. Or, The high point of the writ of habeas corpus discussed. And not onely the several branches of the said writ, but also the authorities of both common and statute-law (with divers ancient and obscure records) produced and cleared. Shewing the remedies against illegal and unjust imprisonment. (Fit for the perusal of every English-man.) It being the case of Mr. John Streater, in Michaelmas &amp; Hilary-Terms last past, at the Upper-bench-bar: he being committed by vertue of an Order of the late Councel of State, and an Order of Parliament of Nov. 21. 1653. Wherein are recited the arguments of the prisoner and his learned counsel, on the one part; and those of Mr. Attorney-General, on the other. With the opinion of the reverend judges upon the whole matter. Also, a narrative of Mr. John Lilburn's proceedings in Michaelmas Term, in order to the obtaining of an habeas corpus.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[16], 45, [3] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">James Cottrel;</persName> and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">him</persName> at <placeName>his house of Addle-hlll [sic]</placeName>, and by <persName type="bookseller">Richard Moone</persName>, at <placeName>the seven stars in Paul's Church-yard, neer the great north-door.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date>1654.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "March [the] 14.".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Richard Moone</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>him</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>James Cottrel;</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his house of Addle-hlll [sic]</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the seven stars in Paul's Church-yard, neer the great north-door.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
