<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Helpes for discovery of the truth in point of toleration: being the judgment of that eminent scholler Tho. Cartwright, sometimes Divinity-Professor in the University of Cambridge in the reigne of Queen Elizabeth of happy memory, and then a famous non-conformist, for which through the tyranny of the Bishops he suffered exile. Wherein the power and duty of the magistrate in relation to matters of religion is discussed; as also whether the judiciall lawes given by Moses to the Jewes are abrogate by the coming of Christ. More particularly in relation to some sinnes, viz. blasphemy, adultery, &amp;c. Occasionally handled in a controversie betweene the said publike professor T.C. and Doctor Whitgift. Here also by the way is laid downe his judgment in the case of divorce, and that the party innocent may marrie again.</title>
      <author>Cartwright, Thomas, 1535-1603.</author>
      <author>Cartwright, Thomas, 1634-1689, attributed name.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 14 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Banks</persName>, at <placeName>the signe of the Seale in Westminster Hall</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1648.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Sometimes erroneously attributed to Thomas Cartwright 1634-1689.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Jan.24"; the 8 in imprint date has been crossed out and date altered to 1647.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Banks</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the signe of the Seale in Westminster Hall</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
