<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A letter from the Lord Lieutenant of Ireland, to the Honorable William Lenthal Esq; Speaker of the Parliament of England giving an account of the proceedings of the army there under his Lordships command; and several transactions between his Lordship and the Governor of Wexford. Together with a relation of the taking in of Wexford, with the fort, haven and shipping there; and of several other garisons of the enemy. As also the propositions tendred for the rendition of Wexford: and a copy of a censure, under the hand of Nicholas Bishop of Fernes, against Talbot who dyed a Protestant. Ordered by the Parliament, that these letters and transactions be forthwith printed and published. Hen: Scobell, Cleric. Parliamenti.</title>
      <author>Ireland. Lord Lieutenant (1649-1650 : Cromwell)</author>
      <author>Cromwell, Oliver, 1599-1658.</author>
      <author>Sinnot, David.</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament. Proceedings. 1649-10-30.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>16 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">John Field</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Edward Husband</persName>, printer to <persName type="patron">the Parliament of England</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1649.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>In addition to the letter from Cromwell to Lenthall, dated 4 Oct. 1649, contains a series of letters exchanged between Cromwell and David Sinnot, "governor of the town and castle of Wexford".</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Octo: 30".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Folger Shakespeare Library, Washington, D.C.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="patron">
      <persName>the Parliament of England</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Edward Husband</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>John Field</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
