<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A letter sent from Lieutenant Generall Cromwel to the Marquis of Argyle and Generall Lesley, and his protestation concerning the Scottish forces, under the command of Gen. Monro; and the marching of the English army into that kingdom under the conduct of the said Lieuten. Generall Cromwel, and Colonell Generall Lambert. Also, the resolution of the said Gen. Monro, touching Lieut. Gen. Cromwels entring into Scotland, and a great victory obtained by him; with the number killed and taken prisoners. Likewise, the declaration of the said Lieut. Generall Cromwell, to his army, and his directions to every colonell, concerning their proceedings against Monro. Commanded to be published throughout the army, by every captain of each respective troop or company. Signed, O. Crumwell.</title>
      <author>Cromwell, Oliver, 1599-1658.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 6 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">C.VV.</persName> and are to be sold at <placeName>the Royall Exchange in Cornhill</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1648">1648.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"Comprises the text of Cromwell's order to his army against plundering, of 20 Sept. 1648 (Abbott 299b), followed by a news pamphlet which incidentally summarizes Cromwell's letter to Argyle."--NUC pre-1956 imprints.</note>
      <note>Place of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the British Library (Thomason Tracts) and in the University of Illinois Library (Early English books).</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>C.VV.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Royall Exchange in Cornhill</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
