<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Culpeper's last legacy left and bequeathed to his dearest wife, for the publicke good, being the choicest and most profitable of those secrets which while he lived were lockt up in his breast, and resolved never to be publisht till after his death. Containing sundry admirable experiences in severall sciences, more especially, in chyrurgery and physick, viz. compounding of medicines, making of waters, syrrups, oyles, electuaries, conserves, salts, pils, purges, and trochischs. With two particular treatises; the one of feavers; the other of pestilence; as also other rare and choice aphorisms, fitted to the understanding of the meanest capacities. Never publisht before in any of his other works. By Nicholas Culpeper, late student in astrology and physick.</title>
         <author>Culpeper, Nicholas, 1616-1654.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[7], 48 p., [4], 73 p., [8], 144 [i.e. 140] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for N. Brooke at the Angell in Cornhill,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
         <date>1655.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Place of publication from Wing.</note>
         <note>Many pages misnumbered in second part.</note>
         <note>"Febrilia, or, A treatise of feavers in generall", "A treatise of the pestilence", "Composita, or, A synopsis of the chiefest compositions in use now with Galenists", "Aphorismes", "Select medicinall aphorismes" have separate dated title pages.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "May. 11".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
         <note>Febrilia, or, A treatise of feavers in generall -- A treatise of the pestilence -- Composita, or, A synopsis of the chiefest compositions in use now with Galenists -- Aphorismes -- Select medicinall aphorismes.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
