<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A discovery of the great fantasie, or, Phantasticall conceitednesse. That is to say, of the antichristian blindnes of those, that out of a meer false imagination and phantasticall conceitednesse, do hold themselves to be Christians, sprituall divines, deputies and messengers or spokes-men of Christ, and take upon them, as mediatours, to save others, whom they call the secular lay-men; therewithall, reviling, traducing, condemning, excommunicating, persecuting, exiling, and putting to death the true children of God, for not yeelding unto this phantasie of theirs, conceiving, that therein they do God great service, when they busie themselves in weeding the ground thus, according to their phantasies, and endeavouring to save the angels a labour against the time of the harvest. Together with a discovery of the great arch-whore, and her paramours or lovers, whereof the spirit of God beareth witnesse.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 22 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">T. P.</persName> and <persName type="printer">M. S.</persName> in <placeName>Goldsmiths Alley</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1642">1642.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Text of the "Discovery of the great arch-whore .." p. 19-22.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Octob. 19".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>M. S.</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>T. P.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Goldsmiths Alley</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
