<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Anno Regni Caroli II. Regis Angli&#230;, Scoti&#230;, Franci&#230;, &amp; Hiberni&#230;, duodecimo. At the Parliament begun at Westminster, the five and twentieth day of April, an. Dom. 1660 In the twelfth year of the reign of our most gracious soveraign lord Charles, by the grace of God, of England, Scotland, France, and Ireland, King, Defender of the Faith, &amp;c.</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Sovereign (1660-1685 : Charles II)</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>150 [i.e. 148], [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">John Bill</persName>, Printer to <persName type="patron">the Kings most Excellent Majesty</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1661">1660] [i.e. 1661]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Contains the acts drafted by the Convention Parliament.</note>
      <note>List of additional acts not included: pp. 148-150.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A-Z&#178;  2A-2G&#178;  2H&#185; 2I-2P&#178; .</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Jan 7".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      <note>An act for the better ordering the selling of wines by retail -- An act for the levying of the arrears of the twelve moneths assessment commencing the 24th of June 1659, and the six moneths assessment commencing the 25 of December 1659 -- An act for granting unto the Kings Majesty, four hundred and twenty thousand pounds, by an assessment of threescore and ten thousand pounds by the moneth, for six moneths, for disbanding the remainder of the army and paying off the navy -- An act for further supplying and explaining certain defects in an act intituled An act for the speedy provision of money for disbanding and paying off the forces of this kingdom -- An act for the raising of seventy thousand pounds for the further supply of his Majesty -- An act for the attainder of several persons guilty of the horrid murther of his late Sacred Majestie King Charles the First -- An act for confirmation of leases and grants from colledges and hospitals -- An act for confirmation of marriages -- An act for prohibiting the planting, setting, or sowing of tobacco in England and Ireland -- An act for erecting and establishing a post-office -- An act impowering the master of the rolls for the time being, to make leases for years, in order to new build the old houses belonging to the rolls.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>John Bill</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="patron">
      <persName>the Kings most Excellent Majesty</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
