<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A declaration and ordinance of the Lords and Commons assembled in Parliament, for the better securing and setling of the peace of the county of Kent, and for enabling them to associate with the City of London, or any other counties adjacent. And to raise forces within the said county, as well horse as foot, and therewith to give, or cause battell to be given to all such forces as are or shal be raised without the consent of both houses of Parliament; and all such persons with their abbettors and adherents to invade, resist, put to flight, pursue, suppresse, kill, slay, put to execution of death, and by all means to destroy, as enemies to the kingdom. Likewise, instructions for the lord-lieutenant, deputy-lieutenants, and other offiers [sic], and commanders in the county of Kent. And, that every person which shall be imployed as souldiers in this service, of the age of 16. yeers and upwards, shall solemnly take an oath, to be approved of by the Parliament, and they that wilfully neglect the same shall be proceeded against as delinquents, and enemies of the peace of the kingdom. Die Martis, 30 Maii. 1643. Ordered by the Lords and Commons assembled in Parliament, that this declaration and ordinance with the instructions shall be forthwith printed and published. J. Brown Cler. Parliamentorum.</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[12] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">I. Wright</persName> in <placeName>the Old-baily</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1643">Iune 1. 1643.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Signatures: A&#8308; B&#178; .</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>I. Wright</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Old-baily</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
