<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Two declarations of the Lords and Commons of the Parliament of England: the first, to the Convention of the Estates of Scotland; the second, to the Generall Assembly of the Kirke of Scotland. Together with the severall answers of the Convention of the Estates of Scotland, and of the Generall Assembly of the Kirke of Scotland, to the Parliament of England. Die Mercurii, 13. Septemb. 1643. It is this day ordered by the Commons assembled in Parliament, that the declaration of both Houses of Parliament, to the Convention of the Estates in Scotland, with their answer; the declaration of both houses to the Assembly of the Kirke of Scotland, with their answer; And the letter of the Assembly of Divines, met at Westminster, to the Generall Assembly of the Kirke of Scotland, with the Assemblies answer, shall be forthwith printed and published. Hen. Elsyn. Cler. P. D. Com.</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
      <author>Scotland. Convention of Estates.</author>
      <author>Church of Scotland. General Assembly. Commission.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 13, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>for <persName type="publisher">John Bellamie</persName> and <persName type="publisher">Ralph Smith</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Printed at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1643">1643.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"The General assemblies answer and declaration to the Parliament of England": p. 10.</note>
      <note>"A Declaration of the Lords and Commons in the Parliament of England, to the Genarall Assembly of the Church of Scotland" has separate caption title; register and pagination are continuous.</note>
      <note>"A Declaration of the Lords and Commons in the Parliament of England, to the Genarall Assembly of the Church of Scotland" identified as Thomason E.67[19].</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Sept: 16.".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>John Bellamie</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Ralph Smith</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
