<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A declaration of the Commons assembled in Parliament, upon two letters sent by Sir John Brooks, (sometimes a Member of the Commons House this parliament, ... being a projector, a monopolist, and a fomentor of the present bloudy and unnaturall war; for bearing of arms actually against the Parliament) to William Killegrew at Oxford (intercepted neer Coventrey) giving his advice how the King should proceed in the Treaty upon the propositions for peace, presented unto him by the Parliament. With the names of the lords, baronets, knights, esquires, gentlemen, ministers and freeholders, indicted the last sessions at Grantham, of high-treason, by Sir Peregrine Bartue and the said Sir John Brooks, before themselves, and other their fellow-cavaliers, rebels and traitors, commissioners, appointed, (as they say), for that purpose. ... Also, the ordinance of both Houses, made the 17 of Decemb. 1642. that the pretended commissioners, and all others, sheriffs, officers, jurors, and any whom it may concern, may know what to expect, that shall presume to molest the persons or estates of any for their service to the Parliament and Kingdom. With some abstracts of credible letters from Exceter, ... Ordered by the Commons in Parl. that this declaration and letters be forthwith printed and published: H: Elsynge, Cler. Parl. D. Com.</title>
         <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>14 [i.e. 16] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>May 10. London, Printed for Edw. Husbands in the Middle-Temple,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
         <date>1643.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
         <note>Numerous internal mispaginations. Text is continuous despite pagination.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
