<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A declaration of the House of Commons touching the breach of their priviledges, and for the vindication thereof, and of divers members of the said house &amp;c. Wherein is likewise contayned, first, a remonstrance of the present state of divers things in, and about, the City of London, Westminster and Parliament-house, ... : 2. The examination of His Majesties Attourny Generall by the House of Commons, ... 3. Seaven articles of high treason against Coronell Lunsford: together with an order of both Houses for the speedy apprehension of the Lord Digby, and the aforesaid Lunsford, ... 4. The wonderfull deliverance of foure honorable Peeres of this land, ... 5. The votes of both Houses of Parliament against those eleven Bishops which were accused of high treason, &amp;c. 6. The advice sent from His Majewties Commissioners in Scotland, to both the honorable houses of Parliament in England, Ianuary the 15. 1641. ... 7. The sea-mens protestation. Lastly, how two boats laden with great saddles to bee carried down into Kingston, were staid, ... Published this 19. of Ianuary. 1641.</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament. House of Commons.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>8 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Fr. Coules</persName>, and <persName type="publisher">T. Bankes</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1642">1641. [i.e. 1642]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Newsbook -- Wing.</note>
      <note>Also published with title : A declaration of the House of Commons touching the late breach ..</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Fr. Coules</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>T. Bankes</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
