<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>England's new vvonders or Four strange and amazing relations that have lately come to pass in England I. A strange and wonderfull account of one Mary Blackstone, near Hull in York-shire, who after ten years barrenness, was with child of a [mo]nstrous birth, and delivered after wo [sic] years going of it in having 3 heads, each an eye in the forehead, serpents twisting about each neck, 4 arms, and 4 legs, each 10 fingers and toes on the hands and feet; the privities of male and female. With the examination of the mother by the miller, what answer she [ga]ve, her prayer and advice to all women. Not to wish for things God sees not convenient to give lest fearfull punishments overtake them, with the [...] for her funeral sermon, before she dyed, and the substance of the sermon. By D. Boase. [I]I. An account of a mighty serpent, and the appearing of a terrible fiery serpent, at [...] Bedfordshire. ... [I]V. An account of two enemies fighting in the [...] in Bri[t]any in France. All very terrible and wonderful. Licensed according to print.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>15, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">J. Blare</persName> at <placeName>the Looking Glass off London-Bridge:</placeName> and reprinted at <placeName>Aberdeen</placeName> by <persName type="printer">Iohn Forbes</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Aberdeen] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1697">anno Dom. 1697.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Lwe copy, reel 2443, is tightly bound, title page is stained and has missing print.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Wellcome Institute for the History of Medicine, London, England.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>J. Blare</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Iohn Forbes</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Aberdeen</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Looking Glass off London-Bridge:</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
