<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Pseudochristus: or, A true and faithful relation of the grand impostures, horrid blasphemies, abominable practises gross deceits; lately spread abroad and acted in the county of Southampton, by William Frankelin and Mary Gadbury, and their companions. The one most blasphemously professing and asserting himself to be the Christ, the Messiah, the Son of God who dyed and was crucified at Jerusalem for the sins of the people of God. The other as wickedly professing and asserting her self to be the Spouse of Christ, called, the Lady Mary, the Queen, and Bride, and Lambs Wife. Together with the visions and revelations, to which they did pretend their ways of deceiving, with the names and actions of sundry persons deceived by them. As also their examinations and confessions before the justices of the peace, their imprisonment, and their tryal before the judg of assize, at the last assize holden at Winchester, March 7. 1649. Published for a publique benefit and warning to every one to take heed to himself, that he be not deceived by the errors and deceits of these present times. / By Humphry Ellis, minister of the word in the city of Winton.</title>
         <author>Ellis, Humphrey, d. 1676.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>62, [2] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by John Macock, for Luke Fawn, and are to be sold at his shop at the sign of the Parrot in Pauls Church-yard,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1650.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>An edition of: Ellis, Humphry.  Pseudo christus.</note>
         <note>"Grand .. Blasphemies," enclosed in right curly brackets on title page; "Abominable .. Deceits;" by left curly brackets.</note>
         <note>Final leaf = imprimatur leaf.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "May. 27".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
