<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>By the Council of State. A proclamation. Whereas the Parliament assembled at Westminster the third of November, one thousand six hundred and forty, is now dissolved, and the enemies of this Commonwealth, in this interval, are likely to take advantage, to carry on their designs, for disturbance of the publick peace: and taking notice of the great confluence of papists, and other disaffected persons, at this time to the Cities of London, and Westminster, and places adjacent, with intention, probably, to put in execution their said designs, whereof, their great boldness and confidence expressed doth here, and in several parts of the nation, giveth just occasion of suspition, and more then ordinary apprehension of danger, to those who are well affected to the peace of the nation: ...</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Council of State.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>1 sheet ([1] p.)   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Abel Roper</persName>, and <persName type="printer">Thomas Collins</persName>, Printers to <persName type="patron">the Council of State</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1660">[1660]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Title from caption and opening lines of text.</note>
      <note>Order to print dated: Saturday the 17 of March 1659. At the Council of State at Whitehal. Signed: W. Jessop, Clerk of the Council.</note>
      <note>Place of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "March 19".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Abel Roper</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Thomas Collins</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="patron">
      <persName>the Council of State</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
