<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>By the Council of State. A proclamation. Whereas the Council of State hath received information, that there is an endeavour by Colonel John Lambert, and other officers (lately reduced) to raise a new war and to imbroil the nation in blood and distractions, and to hinder the members from meeting in the next Parliament, on whose free councel (under God) the hope of setling the nations both principally depend. ...</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Council of State.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>1 sheet ([1] p.)   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Abel Roper</persName> and <persName type="printer">Tho. Collins</persName>, Printers to <persName type="patron">the Council of State</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1660">[1660]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Title from caption and opening lines of text.</note>
      <note>Dated at end: Given at the Council of State at Whitehall, this one and twentieth day of April, 1660.</note>
      <note>"As Col. Lambert and other officers are trying to raise a new war, Cols. John Hewson, Edward Salmon, Ashfield, Major Creed, Maj. General Tho. Harrison, Col. John Okey, Major Wagstaff, Lievtenant Col. Miller, Capts. John Blackwell, Richard Dean, and Major Gladman with Col. Robert Lilburne are suspected of wishing to join Lambert. They are to surrender at Whitehall within three days after the proclamation of this in their country, on pain of sequestration." -- Cf. Steele.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Abel Roper</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Tho. Collins</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="patron">
      <persName>the Council of State</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
