<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The Levellers vindication or, a tragicall story, presented unto this common-vvealth, city, and army: together with a letter directed to his Excellency, and the Councell of Warre sitting at White-Hall, concerning the great cruelty and oppression still continued in this land, notwithstanding the many undertakings of the army, their vowes, promises, and protestations to the contrary. Shewing withall, the most fearfull judgements of almighty God on many thousands of perfidious and deceitfull persons: / By James Freize, Merchant. This was delivered by Nathaniel Neale, to Colonell Pride, and by him presented to the Councell of War then sitting at White-Hall, the 8 of September 1649.</title>
      <author>Freize, James.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>8 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">George Lindsey</persName>, and are to be sold, at <placeName>his shop at London Stone</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1649">[1649]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Freize is in opposition to the large number of lawyers in Parliament; he states that 57 of 80 members of the House are lawyers. He illustrates his point in the tale of Boris Godunov, Emperor of Russia, in "The fruits of perfidiousness" beginning on p.5.</note>
      <note>Date of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Sept: 11 1649".</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the British Library and the Kres Library, Harvard University.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>George Lindsey</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop at London Stone</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
