<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Two letters from his Excellency Sir Thomas Fairfax, to the Right Honourable the House of Peeres. With a letter from the House of Peeres to his Excellency, giving him thanks for his constant care of the safety of the kingdome, also a remonstrance of his Excellency and the Army under his command. Together with an ordinance of both Houses of Parliament, declaring all votes, orders, and ordinances passed in one, or both Houses, from the 26 of July untill the 6 of this present August 1647. to be null and voyd. Die Veneris, 20 Aug. 1647. Ordered by the Lords in Parliament assembled, that this House approves of this remonstrance, and that the same with the letters be forthwith printed and published. J. Brown. Cler. Parl.</title>
      <author>Fairfax, Thomas Fairfax, Baron, 1612-1671.</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament. House of Lords.</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Army. Council.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 26 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">J. Wright</persName> at <placeName>the Kings head in the Old Baily</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1647">1647.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Pages 25-26, "An ordinance for declaring all votes, orders, and ordinances, passed in one or both Houses, since the force on both Houses Iuly 26, untill the sixth of this present August, 1647 to be null and voyd" [dated at head: Die Veneris 20 Aug. 1647], is identified as Thomason Tract E.402[29].</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>J. Wright</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Kings head in the Old Baily</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
