<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The false and scandalous remonstrance of the inhumane and bloody rebells of Ireland, delivered to the Earl of St. Albans and Clanrickard, the Earl of Roscomon, Sir Maurice Eustace Knight, and other His Majesties Commissioners at Trim, the 17. of March, 1642. to be presented to His Majesty, by the name of The remonstrance of grievances presented to His Majestie in the behalf of the Catholicks of Ireland. ... Together with an answer thereunto, on behalf of the Protestants of Ireland. Also a true narration of all the passages concerning the petition of the Protestants of Ireland. ... August 27. 1644. It is this day ordered by the Committee of the House of Commons in Parliament concerning Printing, that the books, intituled, An answer presented to His Majestie at Oxford, unto the false and scandalous remonstrance of the inhumane and bloody rebells of Ireland; together with A narration of the proceedings at Oxon, be forthwith printed and published: John White.</title>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>80, 77-132, [2] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for Edw. Husbands, in the Middle-Temple.,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1644">1644.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>At foot of title, above imprint: August 27. 1644. It is this day ordered by the Committee of the House of Commons in Parliament concerning Printing, that the books, intituled, An answer presented to His Majestie at Oxford, unto the false and scandalous remonstrance of the inhumane and bloody rebells of Ireland; together with A narration of the proceedings at Oxon, be forthwith printed and published: John White.</note>
         <note>With a final errata leaf.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "11 Sept".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
