<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A character whereby the false christs, or antichrists, seducers, false prophets, and house creepers may be known. Now in the latter dayes, wherein there are perilous tims [sic], as it is written &amp; hath been foretold of in 2 Tim. 3.3. And saith Jesus, false prophets shall come, but by their fruits shall ye know them, Mat. 7. 15, 16. and 20. And now they are come, and by their fruits they are known, as it is written. As may be seen in two letters sent to severall priests in Liestershire, after two severall meetings, betwixt them and those called Quakers, one letter was to be sent to one Tho. Cockeram of swannington [sic], servant to the Lord Protector, at whose house one meeting was, as the letter will further make mention, and shew the difference betwixt the true prophets and the false, which letter was directed to him to to [sic] be read to the priests being present at the meeting, and the other was to the priest of Twycrosse, after the meeting appointed betwixt two priests, and those whom the world scornfully calleth Quakers: wherein is discovered the true prophet and the false, and who those are that creep into houses, leading silly people men and women captive, laden with sin, and led away with diverse lusts, ever learning, and never able to come to the knowledge of the truth; and who those false prophets and house-creepers are, that are spoken of, as is proved, both by their fruits, and also by Scripture, as may be seen, &amp;c. / By one known to the world, by R[ichard Fu]rnvvorth.</title>
         <author>R. F. (Richard Farnworth), d. 1666.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 14 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed, and are to be sold by Giles Calvert at the sign of the Black spread-Eagle at the west-end of Pauls.,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
         <date>1654.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Nou: 17".</note>
         <note>Imperfect: ms. on t.p. obscures a portion of author's name.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
