<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The spirituall man iudgeth all things: or the spirituall mans true iudgment: and how by him the hearts of others were, and may be judged by the spirit of truth; and also how things by the spiritual man were judged of, concerning both salvation and damnation, proved by several Scripture examples, according to the spirit of truth, which were, and is the guide of the Lords people out of error and deceit into all truth, according to sweet Gospel-promise, Joh. 16. 13. Rom. 8. 14. Also, something in short, concerning Melchizedeks order of taking the tythes of spoils only of Abraham, after the return from the slaughter of the kings, a free-will offering at one time, and no more, Gen, 14. answering Heb. 7. And in short, of the order of tythes, by command under the law, in the Aaronical and Levitical priesthood, the change of the law, and priesthood also, Heb. 7. 12. so an end of tythes: with a godly exhortation and instruction, full of sweet Gospell truths, to such as have the witness of the new Testament, through the blood of Jesus, and some mementoes: with something also to stop lies and slanders, that trute [sic] may be cleared.</title>
         <author>R. F. (Richard Farnworth), d. 1666.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 36 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for Giles Calvert, and are to be sold at his shop, at the Black Spread-Eagle, at the westend of Pauls,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1655">1655.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>To the reader signed (misprinted): Robert Farnworth.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "March. 6. 1654"; the final 5 in imprint date crossed out.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
