<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The sacrifice of the faithfull. Or, A treatise shevving the nature, property, and efficacy of zealous prayer; together with some motives to prayer, and helps against discouragements in prayer. To which is added seven profitable sermons. 1. The misery of the Creature by the sinne of man, on Rom. 8. 22. 2. The Christians imitation of Christ, on Ioh. 2. 6. 3. The enmity of the wicked to the light of the Gospel, on John 3. 20. 4. Gods impartiality, on Esay 42. 24. 5. The great dignity of the saints, on Heb. 11. 28. 6. The time of Gods grace is limited, on Gen. 6. 3. 7. A sermon for spirituall mortification, on Col. 3. 5. / By William Fenner, minister of the Gospel Fellow of Pembrok Hall in Cambridge, and lecturer of Rochford in Essex.</title>
         <author>Fenner, William, 1600-1640.</author>
         <author>Stafford, John, fl. 1658, engraver.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[20], 214, [9], 85, [1] p. : ill. (port.)  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for John Stafford, and are to be sold at his House over against Brides Church in Fleet-street,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1649">1649.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>With engraved portrait of Fenner on first leaf, signed: John Stafford excudit.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "march. 9."</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
         <note>The misery of the Creature by the sinne of man -- The Christians imitation of Christ -- The enmity of the wicked to the light of the Gospel -- Gods impartiality -- The great dignity of the saints -- The time of Gods grace is limited -- A sermon for spirituall mortification.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
