<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Vnheard-of curiosities concerning the talismanical sculpture of the Persians; the horoscope of the patriarkes; and the reading of the stars. Written in French, by James Gaffarel. And Englished by Edmund Chilmead, Mr. of Arts, and chaplaine of Christ-Church Oxon.</title>
      <title>Curiositez inouyes, sur la sculpture talismanique des persans. Horoscope des patriarches. Et lecture des estoilles. English.</title>
      <author>Gaffarel, Jacques, 1601-1681.</author>
      <author>Chilmead, Edmund, 1610-1654, translator.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[40], 433, [9] p., folded plate   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">G.D.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Humphrey Moseley</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop, at the Princes Armes in St. Pauls Church-Yard</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1650">1650.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of: Curiositez inouyes, sur la sculpture talismanique des persans. Horoscope des patriarches. Et lecture des estoilles.</note>
      <note>The first leaf contains "The testimony that Leo Allatius gives, in his Apes urban&#230;, concerning this book".</note>
      <note>The final quire A&#8308; contains advertisements, with caption title: Courteous reader, these books following are printed for Humphrey Moseley, and are to be sold at his shop at the Princes Armes in St Pauls Church-yard." (first line: 1. The history of the banished virgin, a ro-).</note>
      <note>The "plates" are woodcuts.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "May 14".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Humphrey Moseley</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>G.D.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop, at the Princes Armes in St. Pauls Church-Yard</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
