<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Neophytopresbyteros, or, The yongling elder, or, novice-presbyter. Compiled more especially for the Christian instruction and reducement of William Jenkin, a young presbyter, lately gone astray like a lost sheep from the wayes of modesty, conscience and truth. And may indifferently serve for the better regulation of the ill governed Society of Sion Colledge. Occasioned by a late importune pamphlet, published in the name of the said William Jenkin, intituled Allotrioepiskopos; the said pamphlet containing very little in it, but what is chiefly reducible to one, or both, of those two unhappy predicaments of youth, ignorance, &amp; arrogance. Clearly demonstrated by I.G. a servant of God and men in the glorious Gospel of Jesus Christ. Wherein also the two great questions, the one, concerning the foundation of Christian religion: the other, concerning the power of the naturall man to good supernaturall, are succinctly, yet satisfactorily discussed. With a brief answer in the close, to the frivolous exceptions made by C B. against Sion Colledge visited, in a late trifling pamphlet, called, Sion Colledge what it is, &amp;c.</title>
      <author>Goodwin, John, 1594?-1665.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8], 139, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Henry Overton</persName> in <placeName>Popes-head-Alley</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1648">1648.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"To the unpartiall reader" signed: John Goodwin.</note>
      <note>A reply to "Allotrioepiskopos" by William Jenkyn and "Sion College what it is, and doeth" by Cornelius Burges.</note>
      <note>The words "Neophytopresbyteros" and "Allotrioepiskopos" are in Greek characters on title page; the words "ignorance, &amp; arrogance" are enclosed in brackets.</note>
      <note>Place of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "June 15".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Henry Overton</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Popes-head-Alley</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
