<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A modest vindication of the doctrine of conditions in the Covenant of Grace, and the defenders thereof, from the aspersions of arminianism &amp; popery, which Mr. W. E. cast on them. By the late faithful and godly minister Mr. John Graile, minister of the gospel at Tidworth in the county of Wilts. Published with a preface concerning the nature of the Covenant of Grace, wherein is a discovery of the judgment of Dr. Twisse in the point of justification, clearing him from antinomianism therein. By Constant Jessop, minister of the Gospel at Wimborn minister in the county of Dorset. Whereunto is added, a sermon, preached at the funeral of the said Mr. John Grail. By Humphrey Chambers, D.D. and pastor of the church at Pewsie.</title>
         <author>Graile, John.</author>
         <author>Chambers, Humphrey, 1598 or 9-1662.</author>
         <author>Jessop, Constantine, 1601 or 2-1658. Pauls sad farewel to his Ephesians.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 49, [1], 125, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for Mat. Keinton at the Fountain in Pauls Church-yard,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
         <date>1655. [i.e. 1654]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>"The Covenant of Grace, not absolute, but conditional, modestly asserted", with caption title, begins new pagination and register. Within this series, "Pauls sad farevvel to his Ephesians" has separate dated title page.</note>
         <note>"The Covenant of Grace, not absolute, but conditional, modestly asserted" is identified as Thomason E.817[2].</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Nou: 13"; the 5 in imprint date has been crossed out and date altered to 1654.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
