<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The Covenanters plea against absolvers. Or, A modest discourse, shewing why those who in England &amp; Scotland took the Solemn League and Covenant, cannot judge their consciences discharged from the obligation of it, by any thing heretofore said by the Oxford men; or lately by Dr Featly, Dr. Gauden, or any others. In which also several cases relating to promisory oathes, and to the said Covenant in special, are spoken to, and determined by Scripture, reason, and the joynt suffrages of casuists. Contrary to the indigested notions of some late writers; yet much to the sense of the Reverend Dr. Sanderson. Written by Theophilus Timorcus a well-wisher to students in casuistical divinity.</title>
      <author>Timorcus, Theophilus.</author>
      <author>Gataker, Thomas, 1574-1654, attributed name.</author>
      <author>Vines, Richard, 1600?-1656, attributed name.</author>
      <author>Baxter, Richard, 1615-1691, attributed name.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[24], 87, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">T.B.</persName> and are to be sold in <placeName>Westminster Hall</placeName> and <persName type="publisher">Pauls Church-yard</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1660">1661. [i.e. 1660]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Attributed to Richard Baxter, Thomas Gataker, and Richard Vines by John Brown in his "An apologeticall relation of the particular sufferings of the faithfull ministers &amp; professours of the Church of Scotland, since August, 1660" (p. 379), though the second two died in 1654 and 1656 respectively.</note>
      <note>The first leaf contains "The portraiture of his sacred Majesty in his Solitudes, .. [quotation]".</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Decemb. 17".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Pauls Church-yard</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>T.B.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Westminster Hall</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
