<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The fort-royal of Christianity defended. Or, a demonstration of the divinity of scripture, by way of excellency called the Bible. With a discussion of some of the great controversies in religion, about universal redemption, free-will, original sin, &amp;c. For the establishing of Christians in truth in these atheistical trying times. / By Thomas Gery, B.D. and Rector of Barwell in Leicestershire.</title>
      <author>Gery, Thomas, d. 1670?</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[12], 139, [5], 100, [8] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">T.C.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Nathanael Web</persName>, and <persName type="publisher">William Grantham</persName> at <placeName>the sign of the black Bear in Paul's Church-yard, neer the little North-door of Paul's</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date>1657.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>With a separate dated title page: A discussion and decission of some great controversies in religion: .. London, printed for N. Webb and W. Grantham. 1657. Signatures are continuous.</note>
      <note>The final 4 leaves contain an advertisement: Books printed, and are now to be sold by Nathanael Web, and William Gratham, at the black Bear in St. Paul's Church-yard, neer the little North-door, 1657. Signatures are continuous.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "June 30".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Nathanael Web</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>William Grantham</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>T.C.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the sign of the black Bear in Paul's Church-yard, neer the little North-door of Paul's</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
