<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Britains royal star: Or, An astrological demonstration of Englands future felicity; deduced from the position of the heavens as they beheld the earth in the meridian of London, at the first proclaiming of his Sacred Majesty King Charles the second, on May 8. 10h. 56m. A.M. 1660. And an enquiry made into the use and abuse of astrologie, resolving whether it be convenient to be continued or contemned. Also, an admirable observation of a conjunction of Jupiter and Mars made in the year 1170. by a learned monck of Canterbury, communicated to the learned in astronomy. Together with an exaination and refutation of that nest of sedition, published by Mr. H. Jessey, concerning frogs, dogs, &amp;c. in his pamplet falsly intituled, The Lods Loud call to England, &amp;c. By John Gadbury, philomathematicus.</title>
      <author>Gadbury, John, 1627-1704.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 34, [2], 24 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">Sam. Speed</persName>, at <placeName>the signe of the Printing-Press in St. Paul's Church-yard</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1660">1661. [i.e. 1660]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"A brief examination of that nest of sedition, and phanatick forgeries, published by Mr. H. Jessey" has separate dated title page and pagination; register is continuous.</note>
      <note>"A brief examination of that nest of sedition, and phanatick forgeries, published by Mr. H. Jessey" is identified as Thomason E.1050[1*].</note>
      <note>Thomason copy bound with items from 1660.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Novem 22".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Sam. Speed</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the signe of the Printing-Press in St. Paul's Church-yard</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
