<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Knaves and fooles in folio. Discovered, and then advised, that once at the last they will grow both wise and honest. Or, a meanes to undeceive, and so to beget a right understanding and judgement throughout the three kingdomes, hitherto deluded by the aforesaids. Dedicated with all respectivenesse both for discovery and caution against the aforesaids, to all the wise and honest of the three nations, whom wee highly prize and honour, especially the Honourable Citie of London, whose goodnesse, piety, easie betrust, and credulity of such unworthies, hath been too much wrought upon and abused by depraved polititians of all sorts. In which tract is shewed the wickednesse of the one side in their severall pretences, and the weaknesse on the other side, in being through too much credulity surprized and circumvented by such pretenders, who intend not what they pretend; but bave [sic] their own self-ends to compasse under such pretexts. -Conceived very usefull to be taken knowledge of, by all sorts whatsoever. For that wee hope the reader will finde himselfe fully satisfied thereby, which may probably much check, if not totally break the neck of this uncivill Civill Warre. The contents of the booke are in the next page.</title>
      <author>S. H.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[6], 36 [i.e. 37], [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">M. Simmons</persName> for <persName type="publisher">R[alph] H[arford]</persName> in <placeName>Queens-head-Alley</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1648">1648.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"To the reader" signed: S.H.</note>
      <note>Printer's name from the Huntington Library catalogue.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: The kingdome how deluded by knaves and fooles in folio.</note>
      <note>P. 37 misnumbered 36.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Sept. ye 11".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>R[alph] H[arford]</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>M. Simmons</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Queens-head-Alley</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
