<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The skirts of the whore discovered, and the mingled people in the midst of her. In a letter sent by Denys Hollister to the independent baptiz'd people, who call themselves a Church of Christ in Bristol, but are found to be a synagogue of Satan, in answer to a charge brought to him from them by some of their members, and by him ... published. Together with another letter written by him to Thomas Ewens, a teacher among them, ... referring to his speaking among his people of having Sarah Latchet a servant of Jesus, once a member among the Baptists, sent to Bridewell, and whipt for testifying to them in the name of the Lord in their meeting the second day of the ninth moneth. 1655. And likewise an answer to 16 antiqueries directed to the people called Quakers, which answer was sent to Thomas Ewens, from whom the antiqueries were received, though Iohn Pendarviss a long time after published the antiqueries by the name of Queries, without the answer to them, or taking the least notice of it in a book entituled Arrows against Babylon which hath occasiond the presenting of the one, and the other, now to the view of those who read, and understand, to judge of the whole, and of their unfaire and deceitfull dealing.</title>
      <author>Hollister, Dennis, d. 1676?</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 4, 9-31, [4], 32-34 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Giles Calvert</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop at the sign of the Black-Spread-Eagle at the west-end of Pauls.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1656">1656.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Partly a reply to: Pendarves, John.  Arrowes against Babylon.</note>
      <note>The words "in a book .. Babylon" are enclosed in square brackets on title page.</note>
      <note>The pages following p. 31 are numbered 18, 29, 28, 25.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Decemb: 3d".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Giles Calvert</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop at the sign of the Black-Spread-Eagle at the west-end of Pauls.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
