<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A survey of the summe of church-discipline. Wherein the vvay of the churches of New-England is warranted out of the vvord, and all exceptions of weight, which are made against it, answered : whereby also it will appear to the judicious reader, that something more must be said, then yet hath been, before their principles can be shaken, or they should be unsetled in their practice. / By Tho. Hooker, late pastor of the church at Hartford upon Connecticott in N.E.</title>
         <author>Hooker, Thomas, 1586-1647.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[36], 139, 185-296, 90, 46, 59, [1] p. : charts.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by A.M. for John Bellamy at the three Golden Lions in Cornhill, near the Royall Exchange,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1648">M.DC.XLVIII. [1648]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>In four parts.</note>
         <note>The author's preface is followed by an Epistle to the reader, subscribed by Edward Hopkins and William Goodwin, Hartford, 28 Oct., 1647; a poem "In obitum viri doctissimi Thom&#230; Hookeri," by Samuel Stone; two shorter poems by John Cotton and E. Rogers; and a further commendation to the reader by Thomas Goodwin, April 17, 1648.</note>
         <note>To some copies of the work John Cotton's "The way of Congregational churches cleared" was appended. Mr. Cotton's treatise continues the answers to Rutherford, begun by Mr. Hooker in pt. 1, chap. 10, which ends on p. 139; the next page is blank, and chapter 11 follows, numbered 185 with a new signature. It is thought that it may have been the intention of the editors to incorporate Mr. Cotton's work in this division of the Survey, between p. 139 and 185.</note>
         <note>Master microform held by: UnM.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
