<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Sad nevves from Ireland: how the Lord hath been pleased to chastize the Parliaments forces by a losse from the rebels, where the souldiers transported in five boats, were afterwards repulsed by the enemy, and all but eight kild and drowned. Where wee lost Major Walker, Cap. Graves, Cap. Whiting, the Lord Deputies ensigne, and divers other precious stout men. With a list of the particulars, and the manner of the fight. Also the taking of the castle in the Weare, and Col. Tuthill and others cashiered for killing some of the Irish after quarter was given them. And the taking of the fort at Limbrick bridge by storm, with other considerable news. Certifyed by a letter from the Lord Deputy Ireton. July 4. 1651. It is thought fit that this letter from the Lord Deputy of Ireland, be forthwith printed and published, to prevent the mis-information of others. Imprimatur Hen. Scobel. Parliamenti.</title>
      <author>Ireland. Lord Lieutenant (1650 : Ireton)</author>
      <author>Ireton, Henry, 1611-1651.</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 6 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Robert Ibbitson</persName> dwelling in <placeName>Smithfield neere Hosier Lane end</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1651">1651.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Aug:".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Robert Ibbitson</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Smithfield neere Hosier Lane end</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
