<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The touchstone, or, Trial of tobacco whether it be good for all constitutions : with a word of advice against immoderate drinking and smoaking : likewise examples of some that have drunk their lives away, and died suddenly : with King Jame's [sic] opinion of tobacco, and how it came first into England : also the first original of coffee : to which is added, witty poems about tobacco and coffe [sic] : something about tobacco, written by George Withers, the late famous poet ...</title>
         <title>Two broad-sides against tobacco.</title>
         <author>Hancock, John, fl. 1638-1675.</author>
         <author>Hancock, John, fl. 1669-1705.</author>
         <author>James I, King of England, 1566-1625. Counterblaste to tobacco. 1676.</author>
         <author>Maynwaringe, Everard, 1628-1699?</author>
         <author>Thomson, George, fl. 1648-1679. Aimatiasis. Selections. 1676.</author>
         <author>Ward, Samuel, 1577-1640. Woe to drunkards. 1676.</author>
         <author>Sylvester, Josuah, 1563-1618. Tobacco battered, and the pipes shattered. 1676.</author>
         <author>Everard, Giles. De herba panacea. English. Selections. 1676.</author>
         <author>Wither, George, 1588-1667.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[6], 72 p. : ill.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed and are to be sold by the several booksellers,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1676">1676.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Dedication signed: J.H. (i.e. John Hancock).</note>
         <note>Previously published under title: Two broad-sides against tobacco (London : Printed for John Hancock, 1672).</note>
         <note>Signatures: [A]&#8308; B-K&#8308;.</note>
         <note>Illustrations: 1 print : woodcut ; full-page. Subject: "The picture represents the tobacchonists [sic] armes, and Turks coffee-house."</note>
         <note>Woodcut and type flower headpieces; ornamental and cribl&#233; initials.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the William Andrews Clark Memorial Library, University of California, Los Angeles.</note>
         <note>A counterblast to tobacco (p. 1-12) -- Dr. Maynwaring's serious cautions against tobacco, collected out of his Treatise of the scurvy, (p. 70) -- Preservation of health in the choice of drinks, and regular drinking  / transcribed verbatim out of Doctor Maynwaring's Treatise of long life --  Another collection against tobacco-smoking / written by ... George Thompson, in his book Of preservation of the bloud -- Woe to drunkards : a sermon / preached many years since by Mr. Samuel Ward --Tobacco battered and the pipes shattered ... / collected out of the famous poems of Joshua Sylvester, Gent. -- A broad-side against coffee, or, The marriage of the Turk --  Collection ... taken out of that book of Dr. Everard's, entituled,  The vertue of tobacco -- A postscript, by way of apology.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
