<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The Christian faith of the people of God, called in scorn, Quakers in Rhode-Island (who are in unity with all faithfull brethren of the same profession in all parts of the world) vindicated from the calumnies of Christian Lodowick, that formerly was of that profession, but is lately fallen there-from. As also from the base forgeries, and wicked slanders of Cotton Mather, called a minister, at Boston, who hath greatly commended the said Christian Lodowick, and approved his false charges against us, and hath added thereunto many gross, impudent and vile calumnies against us and our brethren, in his late address, so called, to some in New-England, the which in due time may receive a more full answer, to discover his ignorance, prejudice and perversion against our friends in general, and G.K. in particular, whom he hath most unworthily abused. : To which is added, some testimonies of our antient friends to the true Christ of God; collected out of their printed books, for the further convincing of our opposers, that it is (and hath been) our constant and firm belief to expect salvation by the man Christ Jesus that was outwardly crucified without the gates of Jerusalem.</title>
      <author>Keith, George, 1639?-1716.</author>
      <author>Bradford, William, 1663-1752.</author>
      <author>Thurstan, Edward.</author>
      <author>Bull, Henry.</author>
      <author>Bull, Anne.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>16 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed and sold by <persName type="bookseller"><persName type="printer">William Bradford</persName></persName> at <placeName>Philadelphia in Pennsylvania</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Philadephia] :</pubPlace>
      <date>in the year 1692.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Attributed to George Keith by Wing.</note>
      <note>Page 8 signed: Edward Thurstan, Henry Bull, Anne Bull ... [et al.].</note>
      <note>Page 16 signed: Will. Bradford.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the John Carter Brown Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>William Bradford</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>William Bradford</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Philadelphia in Pennsylvania</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
