<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Jurors judges of law and fact or, certain observations of certain differences in points of law between a certain reverend judg, called Andr. Horn, and an uncertain author of a certain paper, printed by one Francis Neale this year 1650. styled, A letter of due censure and redargution to Lievt. Col. John Lilburn, touching his tryall at Guild-Hall, London in Octob. 1649. subscribed H.P. Written by John Jones, gent. Not for any vindication of Mr. Lilburn against any injury which the said author doth him, who can best vindicate himself by due cours of law; if not rather leav it to God whose right is to revenge the wrongs of his servants. Nor of my self, but of what I have written much contrary to the tenents of this letter; and for the confirmation of the free people of England, that regard their libertie, propertie, and birthright, to beleev and stand to the truth that I have written, so far as they shall finde it ratified by the lawes of God and this land; and to beware of flatterers that endevor to seduce them under colour of good counsel, to betray their freedoms to perpetual slavery.</title>
      <author>Jones, John, of Neyath, Brecon.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[22], 94 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">W.D.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">T.B.</persName> &amp; <persName type="publisher">G.M.</persName> at <placeName>the three Bibles in Pauls church-yard, near the west end</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1650">[1650]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "2d August".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>G.M.</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>T.B.</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>W.D.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the three Bibles in Pauls church-yard, near the west end</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
