<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The reformation, in which is reconciliation with God and his people or, I. Subjection to the state remonstrated: viz. That all that receive protection ought to yield subjection to this present power; (the old Protestants doctrine) opposite to that of the fift [sic] monarchy, &amp;c. II. Church-government reformed: shewing, that the church should be governed by Scripture, bishops, presbyters, pastors, all unitedly subordained under the supreme-magistrate. III. Faith, in which all should be baptized is cleared: or, a catchism [sic] unveiling the Apostles Creed, with annotations; in which faith, ordinances and government are professed as in the primitive times, in opposition to all errors and heresies.</title>
      <author>Kaye, William.</author>
      <author>Kaye, William.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[6], 36 (i.e. 38); [12], 61, [13], 54 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">M.I.</persName> and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Toh. [sic] Parkhurst, and</persName> at <placeName>the three Crowns, at the lower end of Cheapside, over-against the great Conduit</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1658">1658.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Anonymous: by William Kaye.</note>
      <note>Signatures: A-C; A-E; A-D.</note>
      <note>In three parts: title page to part 2 is on C8v (first signature sequence) and reads: II. The church-government by scripture bishops, presbyters, pastors all dependently united under the supreme magistrate jure divino; title page to part 3 ([Wing K40], A1r, third signature sequence) reads: The reformed protestant's catechism, with annotations: .. London: printed for M.I. and are to be sold by Tho. Parkhurst, at the three Crowns, at the lower end of Cheapside, over-against the great Conduit, 1658. Blank leaves: C7 (first signature sequence) and E8 (second sequence).</note>
      <note>Numerous errors in pagination.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "July".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>M.I.</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Toh. [sic] Parkhurst, and</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the three Crowns, at the lower end of Cheapside, over-against the great Conduit</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
