<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A way to sion sought out, and found, for believers to walke in. Or, A treatise consisting of three parts. In the first part is proved, 1. That God hath had a people on earth, ever since the comming of Christ in the flesh, throughout the darkest times of popery, which he hath owned as saints, and as his Church. 2. That these saints have power to reassume and take up as their right, any ordinance of Christ, which they have beene deprived of by the violence and tyranny of the man of sin. Wherein it is cleared up by scriptures, and arguments grounded upon scripture, who of right may administer ordinances, and amongst the rest the ordinance of baptisme with water. The 2. part containeth a full and large answer to 13. exceptions against the practice of baptizing believers, wherein the former particulars are more fully cleared up. The 3. part proveth that outward ordinances, and amongst the rest the ordinance of baptisme is to continue in the church, and this truth cleared up from intricate turnings &amp; windings, clouds &amp; mists that make the way doubtful &amp; dark. / By Daniel King, preacher of the Word neere Coventry.</title>
      <author>King, Daniel, preacher near Coventry.</author>
      <author>King, Daniel, preacher near Coventry. Stumbling blockes removed out of the way.</author>
      <author>King, Daniel, preacher near Coventry. Some beams of light, for the further clearing up of the way.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[20], 136, [4], 133-238, [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Charles Sumptner</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">Hanna Allen</persName>, at <placeName>the Crown in Popes-head-alley</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1650">1650.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"Stumbling blockes removed out of the way" and "Some beams of light, for the further clearing up of the way" each have separate dated title pages; pagination and register are continuous.</note>
      <note>The final leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>"Some beams of light, for the further clearing up of the way" is identified as Thomason E.596[8].</note>
      <note>"Some beams of light, for the further clearing up of the way" possibly also issued separately.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Mar. 23"; the imprint date has been altered to 1649.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Hanna Allen</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Charles Sumptner</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Crown in Popes-head-alley</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
