<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Innocency and truth justified. First against the unjust aspersions of W. Prinn, affirmed in the 17th. page of his pamphlet, called A fresh discovery of prodigious new wandring blazing stars and fire brands, ineight lines of which there is above a dozen of uutruths [sic], cleerly laid open. Next, by a just moderate reply, to his other pamphlet, called The lyar confounded, in which the case of Leiu. [sic] Coll. Lilburns imprisonment is truly stated, legally discussed, and vindicated, from the miserable misstatedness thereof by William Prinn. As also by a cleere manifestation of the strong and malitious indeavour of W. Prinn, unjustly to take away L.C. Lilburns life, by groundlesse accusing him of high treason, in designing and plotting to suppresse and cut of [sic] this present Parliament by force of armes; ... Unto which ... is annexed a coppy of a letter written by L.C. L. to one of his special friends when he was in his cruell close imprisonment, ... published now for the incouragement of the saints, cheerfully to suffer afflictions and sorrowes for the sake and cause of their lord and master.</title>
         <author>Lilburne, John, 1614?-1657.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>76, 21, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>s.n.],</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
         <date>Printed in the yeare, 1645 [i.e. 1646]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Attributed to John Lilburne by Wing.</note>
         <note>In two parts, each with separate pagination and register. Part 2 caption title reads "Innocency and truth justified. Let the quintescence of sweetnesse which is in the Lord Jesus Christ, be alwayes your delight. London, printed according to order by Thomas Paine, 1646." This is the "coppy of a letter written by L.C. L." referred to on the title page.</note>
         <note>L.C. L. = John Lilburne, who has signed part 2 at end.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Jan. 6th London Mr. Oulton [?]"; on page 1 of part 2: "Jan: 6th 1645" the second 6 in imprint date crossed out.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
