<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>An impeachment of high treason against Oliver Cromwel, and his son in law Henry Ireton Esquires, late Members of the late forcibly dissolved House of Commons, presented to publique view; by Lieutenant Colonel Iohn Lilburn close prisoner in the Tower of London, for his real, true and zealous affections to the liberties of his native country. In which following discourse or impeachment, he engageth upon his life, either upon the principles of law ... or upon the principles of Parliaments ancient proceedings, or upon the principles of reason ... before a legal magistracy, when there shal be one again in England ... to prove the said Oliver Cromwel guilty of the highest treason that ever was acted in England, and more deserving punishment and death then the 44 judges hanged for injustice by King Alfred before the Conquest; ... In which are also some hints of cautions to the Lord Fairfax, for absolutely breaking his solemn engagement with his souldiers, &amp;c. to take head and to regain his lost credit in acting honestly in time to come; ... In which is also the authors late proposition sent to Mr Holland, June 26. 1649. to justifie and make good at his utmost hazard ... his late actions or writings in any or all his books.</title>
      <author>Lilburne, John, 1614?-1657.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 8, 16, 15-56 [i.e. 64], [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>[s.n.],</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date>Anno Dom. 1649.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>P. 64 misnumbered 56.</note>
      <note>The last leaf bears "The charge of the Commons of England, against Charles Stuart King of England, of high treas n [sic], ..".</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Aug: 10".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
