<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>An vnhappy game at Scotch and English. Or A full answer from England to the papers of Scotland. Wherein their Scotch mists and their fogs; their sayings and gaine-sayings; their juglings, their windings and turnings; hither and thither, backwards and forwards, and forwards &amp; backwards again; their breach of Covenant, Articles, &amp; treaty, their King-craft present design, against the two houses of Parliament, &amp; people of England, their plots and intents for usurpation and government over us and our children detected, discovered, and presented to the view of the world, as a dreadfull omen, all-arme, and warning to the kingdome of England.</title>
         <author>Lilburne, John, 1614?-1657,</author>
         <author>Overton, Richard, fl. 1646,</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 26 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed (as truly, as the Scotch papers were at London) by Evan Tyler, printer to the Kings most Excellent Majestie, and are to be sold at the most solemn signe of the Blew-Bonnet, right opposite to the two Houses of Parliament.,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>Edinburgh [i.e. London?] :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1646">1646.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Attributed to Richard Overton and to John Lilburne.</note>
         <note>"The imprint is false"--Thomason Catalogue; probably printed at London.</note>
         <note>"The book was ordered by the House of Commons, on the day of its publication, to be suppressed and publicly burnt on the 2nd December; the Committee for Complaints were ordered to endeavour to find the printer"--Thomason Catalogue.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Nou: 30th".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
