<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>An outcry of the youngmen and apprentices of London: or, An inquisition after the lost fundamentall lawes and liberties of England. Directed (August 29. 1649.) in an epistle to the private souldiery of the Army, especially all those that signed the solemne ingagement at Newmarket-Heath, the fifth of Iune, 1647. But more especially to the private souldiers of the Generalls Regiment of Horse, that helped to plunder and destroy the honest and true-hearted English-men, trayterously defeated at Burford the 15. of May, 1649. Signed by Charles Collins, Anthony Bristlebolt, William Trabret, Stephen Smith, Edward Waldgrave, Thomas Frisby, Edward Stanley, VVilliam VVhite, Nicholas Blowd, John Floyd in the nameand [sic] behalf of themselves, and the young-men and apprentices of the City of London. Who are cordiall approvers of the paper, called, The agreement of the free people, dated May 1. 1649. and the defeated Burford-mens late vindication, dated the 20. of August, 1649.</title>
         <title>Young-mens and the apprentices outcry.</title>
         <author>Collins, Charles, apprentice.</author>
         <author>Lilburne, John, 1614?-1657, attributed name.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>12 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>s.n.,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1649]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Sometimes attributed to John Lilburne.</note>
         <note>Caption title.</note>
         <note>Imprint from Wing.</note>
         <note>The text of the petition, signed by Charles Collins and 9 others, begins on p. 10.</note>
         <note>Another impression, probably later, of "The young-mens and the apprentices outcry" (Wing Y131), with the title partly reset.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Sept: 7th 1649".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
