<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A plea, or protest, made by VVilliam Prynne, Esquire, and by him sent unto J.M. Knight, one of the eleven impeached Members. Wherein he declares the injustice and illegality of the Lords, Commons, and grandees of the Armies proceedings against him. Whereunto is annexed the case of A.B. (a citizen of London, and a free commoner of England) truly stated, in reference to a pretended impeachment of treason depending in the House of Peers against him : with an answer to certain queres framed thereupon : unto which is annexed the answer of the said A.B. unto the Lords assembled in Parliament in point of law, ... in which it is fully proved, that the House of Lords ... hath not the least jurisdiction in the world over any commoner ... with a full answer to all their presidents in such cases; and that it is not safe for the said A.B. to kneel at the Lords barre, because it is stooping and submitting to their jurisdiction. / Published for the common good of all honest Englishmen, by Lionel Hurbin Gentleman, March 17. 1647.</title>
      <author>Lilburne, John, 1614?-1657.</author>
      <author>J. M.</author>
      <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 17 [i.e. 18] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Iah. Hornish</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1648">1648.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Lionel Hurbin is an anagram of John Lilburne.</note>
      <note>Includes a previously unpublished work by William Prynne.</note>
      <note>Place of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>P. 18 misnumbered 17.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "John Lilburne"; the 8 in imprint date is crossed out and replaced with a 7.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Iah. Hornish</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
