<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Panzooryktologia. Sive Panzoologicomineralogia. Or A compleat history of animals and minerals, containing the summe of all authors, both ancient and modern, Galenicall and chymicall, touching animals, viz. beasts, birds, fishes, serpents, insects, and man, as to their place, meat, name, temperature, vertues, use in meat and medicine, description, kinds, generation, sympathie, antipathie, diseases, cures, hurts, and remedies &amp;c. With the anatomy of man, his diseases, with their definitions, causes, signes, cures, remedies: and use of the London dispensatory, with the doses and formes of all kinds of remedies: as also a history of minerals, viz. earths, mettals, semimettals, their naturall and artificiall excrements, salts, sulphurs, and stones, with their place, matter, names, kinds, temperature, vertues, use, choice, dose, danger, and antidotes. Also an [brace] introduction to zoography and mineralogy. Index of Latine names, with their English names. Universall index of the use and vertues. / By Robert Lovell. St. C.C. Oxon. philotheologiatronomos.</title>
         <author>Lovell, Robert, 1630?-1690.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[96], 519, [1]; [4], 152 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by Hen: Hall, for Jos: Godwin.,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>Oxford, :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1661">1661.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>First word of title in Greek characters; the words "Introduction to zoography .. vertues." are bracketed together.</note>
         <note>"Panoryktologia. Sive Pammineralogicon" (Wing L3245, first word of title in Greek characters) has separate pagination, register, and title page with "printed by W. Hall" in the imprint.</note>
         <note>Includes indexes.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Feb:".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
