<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The attributes of God unfolded, and applied. Wherein are handled the 1 Life 2 Perfection 3 Holiness 4 Benignitie 5 Mercy 6 Truth 7 Wisdome 8 Power 9 Justice of God. 10 Love 11 Hatred 12 Anger 13 Independencie 14 Simplicitie 15 Eternitie 16 Infiniteness 17 Immutability 18 Immensity of God. / Delivered in sundry sermons, at Tavistocke in Devon: By Thomas Larkham, preacher  of the word of God, and pastour of the congregation there. Divided into three parts.</title>
      <author>Larkham, Thomas, 1602-1669.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[24], 156; [16], 246 [i.e. 254]; [14], 63 [i.e. 66], [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Francis Eglesfield</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>the Marygold in Pauls Church-yard.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1656">1656.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>On title page items 1-9 and 10-18 are printed in columns and connectected to 'of God.' - which appears to the right of each column - by three brackets.</note>
      <note>In three parts each with a separate dated title page that begins: The attributes of God unfolded, and applied. Each part is separately paginated and the signatures begin with A for part 1, AA for part 2, and AAA for part 3. Part three has a slightly different imprint: London, printed for Francis Eglesfield, and are to be sold at the Marigold in St. Pauls Church-yard. 1656.</note>
      <note>Part 2 many pages misnumbered beginning at page 237. Part 3 page 66 misnumbered 63.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Feb: 10 1655"; also the last number of the imprint date has been marked through and replaced by a 5.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Francis Eglesfield</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Marygold in Pauls Church-yard.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
