<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A commentary upon the whole Old Testament, added to that of the same author upon the whole New Testament published many years before, to make a compleat work upon the whole Bible.   Vols. 2-4.  Wherein the divers translations and expositions, literall and mysticall, of all the most famous commentators both ancient and modern are propounded, examined, and judged of, for the more full satisfaction of the studious reader in all things, and many most genuine notions inserted for edification in the grace of our Lord Jesus Christ. A work, the like unto which hath never yet been published by any man, yet very necessary, nor only for students in divinity; but also for every Christian that loveth the knowledge of divine things, or humane, whereof this comment is also full. Consisting of IV parts. I Upon the Pentateuch, or five books of Moses. II Upon the historical part, from Joshua to Esther. III Upon Job, Psalms, Proverbs, Ecclesiastes, and Solomons Song. IV Upon all the prophets both great and small. By John Mayer, doctor of divinity.</title>
         <author>Mayer, John, 1583-1664.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[12], 865, [1], 24, 27-341, [21], 472, 330, 206, [14], 900, [26], 488, 365-850, [12] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by Robert and William Leybourn, and are to be sold at most Book-sellers shops,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1653">M DC LIII. [1653]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>"Many commentaries in one" has separate dated title page with imprint: : London, printed by John Legatt, and Richard Cotes; and are to be sold by William Leak, ... MDCXLVII. With separate pagination and register.</note>
         <note>"A commentary upon the holy vvritings of Job, David, and Salomon" has separate dated title page with imprint: London, printed for Robert Ibbitson and Thomas Roycroft. MDCLIII. With separate pagination and register.</note>
         <note>"A commentary upon all the prophets" has separate dated title page with imprint: London, printed by Abraham Miller and Ellen Cotes. 1652. With separate pagination and register.</note>
         <note>Text is continuous despite pagination.</note>
         <note>Copy filmed at UMI microfilm Early English Books 1641-1700 reel 2314 consists of part 1 and reel 2315 consists of parts 2-4.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the St. John's College Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
