<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Mercurius anglicus: or, England's Merlin. Prophetically fore-telling, the admirable events, and wonderful effects, that shall befall the King of Scots, the states of Holland, and the Parliament of England in all their consultations, warlike actions, and naval designes, both by sea and land, for the year of our Lord, 1653. With the most exact predictions, and monthly observations, touching the great rising of the European nations against England; and the success that will attend them in all their motions, enterprises, and attempts; as also, the causes of these strange re[v]olutions, mutations, inclinations, and eversions of empires, kingdoms, and common-wealths. Likewise, the astromical calculations of the eclipses, lunations, and conjunctions; portending a great change of government, religion, and law, in England, Scotland, and Ireland; together with the taking off all taxes, assesments, burdens, and oppressions; and calling to a severe account all committees and treasurers; with the executing of many great ones. Collected out of the most elaborate works of Captain George Wharton, Esquire, Mr. William Eill[ ]e, Mr. John Booker, Mr. Vincent Wing, and Mr. Nicholas Culpeper, students in as</title>
      <author>Booker, John, 1603-1667.</author>
      <author>Wing, Vincent, 1619-1668.</author>
      <author>Culpeper, Nicholas, 1616-1654.</author>
      <author>Wharton, George, fl. 1653.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>8 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">R[obert]. Wood</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1653">1653.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Printer's name from Wing (CD-ROM edition).</note>
      <note>Copy filmed at UMI microfilm Early English Books 1641-1700 reel 2503 has faded print with some loss of text.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Wellcome Institute for the History of Medicine, London.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>R[obert]. Wood</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
