<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A messenger sent to remove some mistakes; or A desirous instrument for the promoting of truth, unity, peace and love in the church of Christ. By way of answer to a book, untruly and improperly intitled, A vindication of that righteous principle of the doctrine of Christ called laying on of hands upon baptized believers. / By Thomas Morris, a servant of Jesus Christ. Also Robert Everards Three questions propounded to Benjamin Morley about his practice of laying on of hands, with his answer, and R. E. reply.</title>
      <author>Morris, Thomas, Baptist.</author>
      <author>Everard, Robert, fl. 1664. Robert Everards Three questions propounded to Benjamin Morley.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[6], 42; 18 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">R.E.</persName> and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Richard Moon</persName>, at <placeName>the seven Stars neer the North Door of Pauls Church.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1655">1655.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Robert Everards Three questions (Wing E3541).. has a caption title, separate pagination and register.</note>
      <note>A reply to: Morley, Benjamin. A vindication of that righteous principle of the doctrine of Christ called laying on of hands upon baptized believers.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "May. 19".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>R.E.</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Richard Moon</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the seven Stars neer the North Door of Pauls Church.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
