<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A most exact and true relation, extracted out of the registers of the acts, ordinances, and publick instruments. Wheerby [sic] those passages are laid open, which hapned since the pacification made at Roschilt, on the 26. of Febr. 1657/8. between the most serene princes, the kings of Denmark and Norway, and the King of Sweden; as also, since the immediately ensuing treaties, at Coppenhaghen, and elsewhere, between the Danish commissioners, and the Sweedish ambassadors ... the Swedes infringing the said peace and treaties ... without any cause ... did on the 9th of August of the same year, lay siege unto the the [sic] kingly residency of Coppenhaghen, and to the Castle of Cronenberg, both by sea and land. Translated out of the Danish, and High Dutch copies, printed at Coppenhaghen. Together with a letter written from Hamborough, by an impartial hand. Demonstrating the several mistakes, and sinister allegations, in the Swedish relation ...</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 18, 48 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">J.C.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">John Crooke</persName>, at <placeName>the signe of the ship, in St. Pauls Church-yard</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1659">1659.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"An exact relation of the transactions &amp; proceedings between the kings of Denmark and Sweden", with caption title, begins new pagination sequence.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Aprill 24".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>John Crooke</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>J.C.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the signe of the ship, in St. Pauls Church-yard</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
