<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Horlogiographia optica. Dialling universall and particular: speculative and practicall. In a threefold pr&#230;cognita, viz. geometricall, philosophicall, and astronomicall: and a threefold practise, viz. arithmeticall, geometricall, and instrumentall. With diverse propositions of the use and benefit of shadows, serving to prick down the signes, declination, and azimuths, on sun-dials, and diverse other benefits. Illustrated by diverse opticall conceits, taken out of Augilonius, Kercherius, Clavius, and others. Lastly, topothesia, or, a feigned description of the court of art. Full of benefit for the making of dials, use of the globes, difference of meridians, and most propositions of astronomie. Together with many usefull instruments and dials in brasse, made by Walter Hayes, at the Crosse Daggers in More Fields. / Written by Silvanus Morgan.</title>
      <author>Morgan, Sylvanus, 1620-1693.</author>
      <author>Goddard, John, fl. 1645-1671, engraver.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[16], 144 p. : ill. (woodcuts, metal cuts)  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">R.</persName> &amp; <persName type="printer">W. Leybourn</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">Andrew Kemb</persName>, and <persName type="publisher">Robert Boydell</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>St. Margarets Hill in Southwark</placeName>, and at <placeName>the Bulwark neer the Tower</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1652.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>With an additional title page, engraved and initialed by John Goddard.</note>
      <note>The first leaf contains verses "On the frontispiece".</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: The "2" in the imprint date is crossed out and date altered to 1652; "Febr. 4th".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Andrew Kemb</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Robert Boydell</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>R.</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>W. Leybourn</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>St. Margarets Hill in Southwark</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Bulwark neer the Tower</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
