<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The manner of the deposition of Charles Stewart, King of England, by the Parliament, and Generall Councell of the Armie: the intended triall of the King for his life, as guilty of high treason; and in case of his refusall to plead to his charge: the resolves of the Parliament, and Councell of Warre. Also the words of a woman who pretends to have seen a vision, to the Generall Councell of the Army. With a list of the names of the Commissioners for the triall of the King, viz. the Earle of Denbigh, E. of Pembroke, E. of Kent, E. of Mulgrave, E. of Nottingham, L. Grey of Wark. The L. Munson, L. Lisle, L. Grey of Groby, Lieut. G. Cromwell, Maj. G. Skippon, Com. G. Ireton, Sir Hen. Mildmay, Sir John Danvers, Sir Greg. Norton, Col. Walton, Col. Moore, Mr. Edwards, Col. Boswel, Mr. Cawley, Mr. Prideaux, Mr. Allen, Col. Ven, Col. Thorne, Col. Rossiter, Ser. Thorpe, Mr. Henry Wingham, Mr. Pury, Mr. Scot, Mr. Trenchard, Mr. Corbets, senior and junior, Mr. Holland, Mr. Hallowell, Mr. Challoner Sen. and junior, Mr. Willington, Mr. Leslo, Col. Lassels, the Lord Gen. Fairfax, Col. Whalley, Col. Rich, Sir Hardresse Waller, Col. Tomlinson, Col. Scroop, Col. Sanders, Col. Twistleton, Col. Pride, ...</title>
         <author>Charles I, King of England, 1600-1649.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 6 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>s.n.],</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
         <date>Printed in the yeere. 1649.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Place of publication from Wing.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Jan: 4th 1649".</note>
         <note>Imperfect; foxed, affecting legibility.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
