<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A bloody fight in Scotland within two miles of Edenburgh, since Lieut. Gen. Cromwel returned in to England. The malignants rize and fell upon Col. Gen. Lamberts men, but were repulsed and routed. Also instructions for the Lord Libberton, and Col. Innis, to treat with Col. Lambert. With a commission for divers lords to give satisfaction to the English and a proclamation published throught the kingdome of Scotland, for such, their goods to bee confiscate, and themselves punished with death. Octob. 15. 1648. Wee doe command and ordain these presents to bee published at the Market Crosse of Edenburgh, Haddington, Dunbarre, Lenilithgow, and Peebles, that none pretend ignorance. Tho. Henderson.</title>
      <author>Margetts, Thomas.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 6 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>... re-printed ... by <persName type="printer">Robert Ibbitson</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1648">1648.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Reprint. Originally published: Edenburgh, first printed by Evan Tylar, printer to the Kings most Excellent Majesty.</note>
      <note>Consists of four parts. The first, the description of the fight in Scotland, dated and signed: Seatoun 18. Octob. 1648. Tho. Margetts. The second and third parts, dated October 10 and 13 respectively, "Instructions for the Laird of Libberton, and Collonel Innis." are both signed A. Henderson. The fourth, the Committee of Estates proclamation of cooperation with Major Gen. Lambert's forces in Scotland.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "8ber [i.e. October] ye 24th".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Robert Ibbitson</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
