<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Satans design discovered: vvho under a pretence of worshipping Christs person in heaven, would exclude God and Christ, the spirit and light, out of the world: and that he should no more dwell in his people as he hath done, till Doomsday, that so he might rule in the hearts of men and women, unrevealed, while the world endures, onely under the name of God and Christ, talked of at a distance, that he may rule in the creation, exalted above God. Clearly laid open in an answer to Thomas Moor, who calls his book an Antidote against the spreading infections, &amp;c. Wherein is discovered the crooked ways the winding Serpent takes to save his head, and reproach the truth with lies, that by any means he might make people believe that a lying spirit is among the Quakers, but is found within him. With 48. lies, taken out from three times as many, and sent back to be proved by the founder of them, T.M. Also some particulars, what the Quakers holds ... / By a servant to truth, called James Nayler.</title>
      <author>Naylor, James, 1617?-1660.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>32, 43-58 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Giles Calvert</persName>, at <placeName>the Black Spread-Eagle near the west end of Pauls</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1655">1655.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A reply to: Moore, Thomas.  An antidote against the spreading infections of the spirit of Antichrist, abounding in these last days under many vizors.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Nou: 2d".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Giles Calvert</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Black Spread-Eagle near the west end of Pauls</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
