<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A second answer to Thomas Moore, to that which he calls, his Defence against the poyson, &amp;c. Wherein is shewed the crooked wayes, the Serpent is forced to take to keep God and his creatures at a distance, and yet would do it under the name of a teacher. But is seen to be the same, that perswaded man out from his guide in spirit, and now would keep him so, lest his unclean wayes in the heart of man should be discovered with the spiritual light of Christ; and so man should turn to the Lord, who is that spirit, and the vail be done away, ... Here is also 54. lies gathered out from amongst a multitude more, with T.M. hath heaped up for his defence, against the truth, which he calles the poyson of Satan, which are sent him back to the 48. that I sent him before, that he may either prove them, or they root with the founder, for the truth they touch not. / Set forth to clear the truth from this froth, cast upon it by the enemy thereof, By a friend to the seed of truth, called James Naylor.</title>
      <author>Naylor, James, 1617?-1660.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 30, 29-35, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Giles Calvert</persName>, at <placeName>the Black-spread-Eagle at the west end of Pauls</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1656">1655 [i.e. 1656]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A reply to: Moore, Thomas.  A defence against the poyson of Satan's designe.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Feb: 17".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Giles Calvert</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Black-spread-Eagle at the west end of Pauls</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
