<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Foot yet in the snare: though the beast hath healed his wound, and now pretends liberty, but is fallen into the trap of the priests, receiving their testimony to beare it up, who are in the pit themselves, thereby giving them occasion to insult against the truth, as the beast and the false prophet hath alwaies joyned against the lamb. Discovered in an answer to Iohn Toldervy, Matthew Pool, VVilliam Jenkin, John Tombs, John Goodwin, VVilliam Adderley, George Cockain, Thomas Jacomb, and Thomas Brooks, who under a pretence of love to the truth, have gone about to devour it, and cover it with reproach. Wherein their crooked wayes, their confusions and contradictions is traced and laid open, and their spirit tryed to bee the same which joyned Judas and the chief priests, and their false witnesses against the heir at his appearance; so those have joyned testimony to the truth, of a lying book, which by their own confession they never read over. With something of their false testimony is short laid open, lest simple minds should bee led with a lye through the fame of the forgers. / By one who loves the soul, but hates the sin, called, James Naylor.</title>
      <author>Naylor, James, 1617?-1660.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 33, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Giles Calvert</persName>, at <placeName>the Black-Spread-Eagle neer the west end of Pauls</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1656">1656.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A reply to: Toldervy, John.  The foot out of the snare.</note>
      <note>"Iohn Toldervy .. Goowin," and "VVilliam Adderley .. Brooks," enclosed in curly brackets on title page.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "January. 2d"; the second 6 in the imprint date has been crossed out and replaced with a "5".</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the Union Theological Seminary, New York, and the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Giles Calvert</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Black-Spread-Eagle neer the west end of Pauls</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
