<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Antichrist in man, Christ's enemy: who hath been pretending for Christ in notion, but now at his appearance stands up with all his power to deny his Light, and preach him unsufficient. Clearly discovered in an answer to a book titled, Antichrist in man the Quakers idol: set forth by Joshua Miller, wherein he confesseth Antichrist to be in man, but denies the light of Christ within to be sufficient to reveal him, and to witness Christ to be the onely means to salvation, he cals an error, if not damnable. With much more such confused stuffe, discovered for the sake of the simple who are led blind, with such blind guides, to their destruction: that such as will may beware and turn to the Lord, that with his Spirit of truth they may be guided into all truth, and out of this great deceit and enmity, wherein they are led and knows not. By a lover of the seed of God, and one that seeks the peace of lost souls, called James Naylor.</title>
      <author>Naylor, James, 1617?-1660.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 17, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Giles Calvert</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>the Black-spread-Eagle at the west end of Pauls.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1656">1656.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "march. 5 1655".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Giles Calvert</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Black-spread-Eagle at the west end of Pauls.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
