<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Irenicum; or, An essay towards a brotherly peace &amp; union, between those of the congregational and presbyterian way; shewing out of the most learned and renowned divines of the congregational way, that their positions concerning 1. Church matters and members. 2. Church constitution and form. 3. Church state. 4. Church officers and ordination. 5. Church government and censures. 6. Church combinations and synods. 7. Communion with and separation from churches. are sufficient for the establishing a firme and lasting peace between them and the Presbyterians ... In pursuance of the good design begun at the Savoy, where it was agreed, and declared, that such reforming churches as consist of persons sound in the faith, and of conversation becoming the Gospel, ought not to refuse the communion of each other ... Drawn up and published by Discipulus de Tempore Junior.</title>
         <author>Newcomen, Matthew, 1610?-1669.</author>
         <author>D. T.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[14], 75, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed for Nathanael Webb and William Grantham, at the black Bear in Pauls Church-yard, near the little north-door,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1659.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Discipulus de Tempore Junior = Matthew Newcomen.</note>
         <note>Preface signed: D.T.</note>
         <note>The words "congregational and presbyterian" and "7. Communion with and separation from" are enclosed in brackets on title page; the words "1. Church matters .. separation from churches." are bracketed together.</note>
         <note>With a preliminary errata leaf.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Aprill 29".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
