<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Divine observations upon the London-ministers letter against toleration: by his synodicall, priest-byter-all, nationall, provinciall, classicall, congregationall, superlative, un-erring, clericall, accademicall holynesse. reverend yongue Martin Mar-Priest, sonne, and heire to old Martin Metrapolitane. Wherin the toleration of his sacred person with the whole Independent fraternity, (by what name or title soever dignify'd or distinguished, whether Anabaptists, Brownists, or the like,) is justifyed by the reasons of the London-ministers, which they urge against toleration; and themselves, by their own reasoning, condemned. The reverend authour desires such as have received offence at the 6, 7, and 8 pages in his Ordinance for tythes dismounted, to repaire for satisfaction to the last clause hereof.</title>
      <author>Overton, Richard, fl. 1646.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>16 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Martin Claw-Clergy</persName>, printer to <persName type="patron">the reverend Assembly of Divines</persName>, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Bartholomew Bang-Priest</persName>, at <placeName>his shop in Toleration-street, at the signe of the Subjects Liberty, right opposite to Persecution-Court</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Europe [i.e. London?] :</pubPlace>
      <date>1646.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Martin Mar-Priest = Richard Overton.</note>
      <note>The imprint is false.</note>
      <note>A reply to: A letter of the ministers of the city of London (Wing L1578).</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Jan: 24th 1645"; the second 6 in imprint date crossed out.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="patron">
      <persName>the reverend Assembly of Divines</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Bartholomew Bang-Priest</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Martin Claw-Clergy</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop in Toleration-street, at the signe of the Subjects Liberty, right opposite to Persecution-Court</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
