<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The araignement of Mr. Persecution: presented to the consideration of the House of Commons, and to all the common people of England wherein he is indicted, araigned, convicted, and condemned of enmity against God, and all goodnesse, of treasons, rebellion, bloodshed, &amp;c. and sent to the place of execution. In the prosecution whereof, the Jesuiticall designes, and secret encroachments of his defendants, Sir Symon Synod, and the John of all Sir Johns, Sir Jonh Presbiter, upon the liberty of the subject id detected, and laid open, / by yongue Martin Mar-Preist, son to old Martin the Metrapolitane. This is licensed, and printed according to holy order, but not entered into the Stationers monopole.</title>
      <author>Overton, Richard, fl. 1646.</author>
      <author>Robinson, Henry, 1605?-1664?,</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 45 [i.e. 46], [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Martin Claw Clergie [i.e. Richard Overton]</persName>, printer to <persName type="patron">the reverend Assembly of Divines</persName>, and are to be sould at <placeName>his shop in Toleration Street, at the signe of the Subjects Liberty, right opposite to Persecuting Court.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Europe [i.e. London?] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1645">1645.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Martin Mar-Priest = Richard Overton.</note>
      <note>Sometimes attributed to Henry Robinson.</note>
      <note>The imprint is false; "published by Overton's own press" (Brailsford, H.N. "The levellers and the English revolution", p.54).</note>
      <note>The first leaf contains an order to print.</note>
      <note>Page numbers 30-46 misnumbered 29-45.</note>
      <note>The final leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Aprill 8th".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Martin Claw Clergie [i.e. Richard Overton]</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="patron">
      <persName>the reverend Assembly of Divines</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop in Toleration Street, at the signe of the Subjects Liberty, right opposite to Persecuting Court.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
