<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>An arrow against all tyrants and tyrany, shot from the prison of New-gate into the prerogative bowels of the arbitrary House of Lords, and all other usurpers and tyrants whatsoever. wherein the originall rise, extent, and end of magisteriall power, the naturall and nationall rights, freedomes and properties of mankind are discovered, and undeniably maintained; ... the late Presbyterian ordinance (invented and contrived by the diviners, and by the motion of Mr. Bacon and Mr. Taet read in the House of Commons) examined, refuted, and exploaded, as most inhumaine, tyranicall and barbarous. / By Richard Overton prerogative archer to the arbitrary House of Lords, their prisoner in New-gate, ... sent by way of a letter from him, to Mr Henry Martin, a Member of the House of Commons. Imprimatur rectat justitia.</title>
      <author>Overton, Richard, fl. 1646.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>20 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed at <placeName>the backside of the Cyclopian Mountains</placeName>, by <persName type="printer">Martin Claw-Clergy</persName>, printer to <persName type="patron">the reverend Assembly of Divines</persName>, and are to be sould at <placeName>the signe of the Subjects Liberty, right opposite to persecuting Court.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1646">1646.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>The imprint is fictitious; actual place of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "8ber [i.e. October] 10th".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Martin Claw-Clergy</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="patron">
      <persName>the reverend Assembly of Divines</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the backside of the Cyclopian Mountains</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the signe of the Subjects Liberty, right opposite to persecuting Court.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
