<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Parnassi puerperium: or, some well-wishes to ingenuity, in the translation of six hundred, of Owen's epigrams; Martial de spectaculis, or of rarities to be seen in Rome; and the most select, in Sir. Tho. More. To which is annext a century of heroick epigrams, (sixty whereof concern the twelve C&#230;sars; and the forty remaining, several deserving persons). / By the author of that celebrated elegie upon Cleeveland: Tho. Pecke of the Inner Temple, Gent.</title>
      <author>Pecke, Thomas, b. 1637.</author>
      <author>Martial.</author>
      <author>More, Thomas, Sir, Saint, 1478-1535.</author>
      <author>Cottrel, James, fl. 1649-1670.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8], 184, [10] p., [1] leaf of plates : port.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>by <persName type="printer">James Cottrel</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">Tho. Bassett</persName> in <placeName>St. Dunstans CHurch yard in Fleet-street</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Printed at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1659">1659.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Martial's, More's, and Pecke's epigrams each have separate divisional title pages; pagination and register are continuous.</note>
      <note>F.l. = Latin address the Bishop of Exeter, signed by Pecke; "The printer to the reader", (verse) signed: J.C. [i.e. James Cottrell]; an advertisement for Basset; a perpendicular half-title which reads: Peck's Epigrams; "Upon Cottrell, the printer" (verse, by Pecke), errata and "To the reader" (verse).</note>
      <note>"When Pecke read Cottrell's verses, .. which ask the charity of the peruser for the errors in printing and claim the authorship of some of the contents, he was apparently sufficiently concerned to insist that Basset allow him to add a reply which in a few copies is found inserted in an unsigned leaf at the end"--Pforzheimer catalogue.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "July".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Tho. Bassett</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>James Cottrel</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>St. Dunstans CHurch yard in Fleet-street</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
