<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A defence of church-government, exercised in presbyteriall, classicall, &amp; synodall assemblies; according to the practise of the reformed churches: touching I. The power of a particular eldership, against those that plead for a meere popular government, specially Mr Ainsvvorth in his Animadversion to Mr Clyft. &amp;c. II. The authority of classes and synods, against the patrons of independencie: answering in this poynt Mr Davenport his Apologeticall reply, &amp;c. and Mr Canne his Churches plea, &amp;c, sent forth first by W. Best, and afterwards for this part of it, under the title of Syons prerogative royall. By Iohn Paget, late able and faithfull pastour of the Reformed English Church in Amsterdam. Hereunto is prefixed an advertisement to the Parliament, wherein are inserted some animadversions on the Cheshire Remonstrance against Presbytery: by T.P.</title>
      <author>Paget, John, d. 1640.</author>
      <author>Paget, Thomas, d. 1660.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[32], 255, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>M DC XLI. Printed by <persName type="printer">H.A.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Vnderhill</persName>, dwelling at <placeName>the signe of the Bible, in Woodstreet</placeName>, <placeName>London</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Dordrecht] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1641">[1641]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"An humble advertisement to the high court of Parliament" signed: Thomas Paget.</note>
      <note>Place of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Vnderhill</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>H.A.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>London</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the signe of the Bible, in Woodstreet</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
