<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A prospective-glasse for gamesters: or, A short treatise against gameing: in which is contained a plaine and perfect manifestation of the inconveniencies, miseries and calamities which the user or practiser of unlawfull games doth bring upon himselfe, not onely in regard of his mortall body, but also upon his eternall soule. Wherein also these six evill consequences of gaming are exactly and pertinently handled, viz. [brace] Drunkennesse. Lying. Swearing. [double brace] Adultery. Poverty. Theevery. [brace] Written at the request of a gamester, upon his detestation of his former idle life and practice in this kind. / By John Philpot Master in Arts. Dedicated to the honest and judicious youngmen and apprentices of the honourable city of London. Published according to order.</title>
      <author>Philpot, John, Master in Arts.</author>
      <author>Philipot, John, 1589?-1645,</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 12 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Bates</persName>, at <placeName>the Maidenhead on Snow-hill, neere Holborne Conduit.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date>1646.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Wing identifies the author as John Philipot, 1589?-1645, but this attribution is unlikely. Philipot was 1) Somerset Herald 1624 and 2) D.C.L. Oxford 1643.  He would not have referred to himself (or have been referred to posthumously) as Master in Arts. Further, as a royalist active on the side of the King, Philipot is unlikely to have had the gaming habits of the "youngmen and apprentices" of London uppermost in his mind. Foster and Venn list no John Philpot or Philipot (or variant) whose highest degree was Master of Arts and who was living in 1646 or shortly before.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "July 23".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Bates</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Maidenhead on Snow-hill, neere Holborne Conduit.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
