<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A vindication of The preacher sent, or A vvarrant for publick preaching without ordination. Wherein is further discovered. 1. That some gifted men unordained, are Gospel preachers. 2. That officers sustain not a relation (as officers) to the universal Church; and other weighty questions concerning election and ordination, are opened and cleared. In answer to two books. 1. Vindiciæ ministrij evangelici revindicatæ or the Preacher (pretendly) sent, sent back again. By Dr. Colling of Norwich. 2. Quo warranto, or a moderate enquiry into the warrantableness of the preaching of gifted and unordained persons. By Mr. Pool, at the desire and appointment of the Provincial Assembly of London. With a reply to the exceptions of Mr. Hudson and Dr. Collings against the epistle to the preacher sent. / Published by Frederick Woodal, minister of the Gospel at Woodbridge in Suffolk. Samuel Petto minister of the GospeI [sic] at Sandcraft in Suffolk.</title>
         <author>Woodall, Frederick, b. 1614.</author>
         <author>Petto, Samuel, 1624?-1711.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[32], 213, [11] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by J.T. Livewell Chapman at the Crown in Popes head Alley,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London. :</pubPlace>
         <date>1659.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A defense of "The preacher sent" by John Martin, in reply to "Vindiciae ministerii evangelici" by John Collinges and "Quo Warranto" by Matthew Poole.</note>
         <note>With four final leaves bearing Scripture tables and errata; the last leaf is blank.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "June".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
