<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A discovery of the priests, that say they are sent off by the Lord, but upon trial are found out of the commands of Christ, the prophets, and Apostles, and to be those that are not sent of the Lord, but to be such that the sent ones of the Lord did cry wo against, and to be such that are false apostles, deceitful, wicked, transforming themselves into the apostles of Christ: and no marvail, for Satan himself is transformed into an angel of light; therefore it is no great thing, if his ministers be transformed as the ministers of righteousness, ... With a few words to such professors and prophane, that together joyn to persecute the righteous: and to the ranters that do commit all manner of sins with greediness. Darkness denied by the children of Light, and the babe of Christ growing up to a perfect man. / Written from one who is known to the world by the name of John Pain, who accounts it great riches to suffer reproaches, and afflictions with the people of the Lord, who scornfully by the world are called Quakers, ... Written from Starford in Hartford-shire the 7. day of the 4. month. 1655.</title>
      <author>Pain, John, shoemaker.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 22, 31-38, 31-37, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Jo. Streater</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Giles Calvert</persName> at <placeName>the Black-spread-Eagle at the end of Paul's</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1655">1655.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "July. 20.".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Giles Calvert</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Jo. Streater</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Black-spread-Eagle at the end of Paul's</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
