<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The opening of the great seale of England. Containing certain brief historicall and legall observations, touching the originall, antiquity, progresse, vse, necessity of the great seal of the kings and kingdoms, of England, in respect of charters, patents, writs, commissions, and other processe. Together with the kings, kingdoms, Parliaments severall interests in, and power over the same, and over the Lord Chancellour, and the lords and keepers of it, both in regard of its new-making, custody, admi nistration [sic] for the better execution of publike justice, the republique necessary safety, and vtility. Occasioned by the over-rash censures of such who inveigh against the Parliament, for ordering a new great seale to be engraven, to supply the wilfull absence, defects, abuses of the old, unduely withdrawne and detained from them. / By William Prynne, Utter-Barrester of Lincolns Inne. ...</title>
      <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 32, [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Michael Sparke Senior.</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Lodon [sic]. :</pubPlace>
      <date>1643.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>At foot of title, above imprint: It is this fifteenth day of September, anno Dom. 1643. ordered by the Committee of the House of Commons, concerning printing, that this treatise, intituled, The opening of the great seale of England, be forthwith printed by Michael Sparke Senior. John White.</note>
      <note>With a final errata leaf.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Octob: 9th".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Michael Sparke Senior.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
