<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The signal loyalty and devotion of God's true saints and pious Christians, especially in this our island towards their kings: (as also of some idolatrous pagans) Both before, and under the law and gospel; expressed by their private and publick prayers, supplications, intercessions, thanksgivings, well-wishes for the health, safety, long life, prosperity, temporal, spiritual, eternal felicity of the kings and emperours under whom they lived, whether pagan or Christian, bad or good, heterodox or orthodox, Papists or Protestants, persecutors or protectors of them: and likewise for their royal issue, posterity realms; and by their dutiful conscientious obedience and subjection to them; with the true reasons thereof from scripture and policy. Evidenced by presidents and testimonies in all ages, worthy the knowledg, imitation, and serious consideration of our present degenerated disloyal, antimonarchical generation. In two parts. By William Prynne Esq; late bencher, and reader of Lincolns-In</title>
      <title>Signal loyalty and devotion of Gods true saints and pious Christians, towards their kings. Parts 1 and 2.</title>
      <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[20], 96, [2], 321, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">Edward Thomas</persName>, at <placeName>the Adam</placeName> and Eve in <placeName>Little-Britain</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1680">1680.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"The second part of the signal loyalty" has drop-head title with separate pagination and register which begins with signature B.</note>
      <note>With a final page of errata.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Folger Shakespeare Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Edward Thomas</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Little-Britain</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Adam</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
