<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>King Richard the Third revived. Containing a memorable petition and declaration contrived by himself and his instruments, whiles Protector, in the name of the three estates of England, to importune and perswade him to accept of the kingship, and crown of England, by their joynt election, (as if he were unwilling to undertake, or accept, though he most ambitiously aspired after them, by the bloudy murthers of K. Henry 6. Edward 5. and sundry others) before his coronation; presented afterwards to, and confirmed by the three estates and himself, in his first Parliament, to give him a colourable title both by inheritance, and their election to the crown. Transcribed out of the Parliament roll of 1.R.3. (printed in Speeds History of Great Britain: where his other additionall policies to engage the City of London, lawyers, divines and people, to elect, and make him their king, are at large recorded.)</title>
      <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 9, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">William Leak</persName>, at <placeName>the Crown in Fleetstreet, betwixt the two Temple-gates.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1657">1657.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Attributed to William Prynne.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy E.903[9]: "March 1st"; the 7 in imprint date has been crossed out and date altered to 1656.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>William Leak</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Crown in Fleetstreet, betwixt the two Temple-gates.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
