<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The third part of The soveraigne povver of parliaments and kingdomes. Wherein the Parliaments present necessary defensive warre against the Kings offensive malignant, popish forces; and subjects taking up defensive armes against their soveraignes, and their armies in some cases, is copiously manifested, to be just, lawfull, both in point of law and conscience; and neither treason nor rebellion in either; by inpregnable reasons and authorities of all kindes. Together with a satisfactory answer to all objections, from law, Scripture, fathers, reason, hitherto alledged by Dr. Ferne, or any other late opposite pamphleters, whose grosse mistakes in true stating of the present controversie, in sundry points of divinity, antiquity, history, with their absurd irrationall logicke and theologie, are here more fully discovered, refuted, than hitherto they have been by any: besides other particulars of great concernment. / By William Prynne, utter-barrester, of Lincolnes Inne. It is this eighth day of May, 1643. ordered ... that this booke, ... be printed by Michael Sparke, senior. John White.</title>
      <title>Soveraigne power of parliaments and kingdomes. Part 3</title>
      <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669.</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament. House of Commons.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8], 144, 143-150 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>for <persName type="publisher">Michael Sparke</persName>, <persName type="publisher">Senior.</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Printed at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1643">1643.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Part three of: The soveraigne power of parliaments and kingdomes.</note>
      <note>With errata at foot of p. 150.</note>
      <note>Also issued as part 3 of Wing P4087A.</note>
      <note>A2r has a headpiece of type ornaments. Variant: with woodcut headpiece.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "June 23".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Michael Sparke</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Senior.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
