<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A seasonable, legall, and historicall vindication and chronologicall collection of the good, old, fundamentall, liberties, franchises, rights, laws of all English freemen (their best inheritance, birthright, security, against arbitrary, tyrannicall, and Egyptian burdens) and of their strenuous defence in all former ages; of late years most dangerously undermined, and almost totally subverted, under the specious disguise of their defence and future establishment, upon a sure basis, their pretended, greatest propugners. Wherein is irrefragably evinced by Parliamentary records, proofs, presidents, that we have such fundamentall liberties, ... that to attempt or effect the subversion of all or any of them, ... is high treason: ... / By William Prynne of Swainswick, Esquire.</title>
      <title>Seasonable, legall, and historicall vindication and chronologicall collection of the good, old, fundamentall, liberties, franchises, rights, laws of all English freemen. Part 1</title>
      <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 60 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">the authour</persName>, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Edward Thomas</persName> in <placeName>Green Arbour</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1654">1654.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Second and third parts were published in 1655 and 1657.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "7ber [i.e., September] 25".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>the authour</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Edward Thomas</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Green Arbour</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
