<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Mount-Orgueil: or Divine and profitable meditations raised from the contemplation of these three leaves of natures volume, 1. Rockes, 2. Seas, 3. Gardens, digested into three distinct poems. To which is prefixed, a poeticall description, of Mount-Orgueil Castle in the Isle of Jersy. By VVilliam Prynne, late exile, and close prisoner in the sayd Castle. A poem of The soules complaint against the body; and Comfortable cordialls against the discomforts of imprisonment, &amp;c. are hereto annexed.</title>
         <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669.</author>
         <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669. Rockes improved.</author>
         <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669. Christian sea-card.</author>
         <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669. Christian paradise.</author>
         <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669. Comfortable cordials.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[14], 56, 59-184, [2]; [4], 16, [2] p., [1] leaf of plates : port.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed by Tho. Cotes, for Michael Sparke Senior, and are to be sold by Peter Inch of Chester,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1641">1641.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>In verse.</note>
         <note>One of four possible imprint variants of this text.</note>
         <note>With marginal notes.</note>
         <note>Order and number of preliminary leaves vary. Ideal copies include a 4-line verse (printed in 7 lines) which faces a portrait of the author. These two leaves may either precede or follow title page. There are two verse dedications, "To the Christian reader", which fill both sides of a leaf, and "To the Right Worshipfull his ever honoured worthy friend ..." on a leaf signed [par.]3, the verso of which is blank.  These two dedication leaves are frequently interchanged.</note>
         <note>With a final errata leaf.</note>
         <note>"Rockes improved", "Christian sea-card", "Christian paradise", and "Soules complaint" each have separate dated title page with "printed by T. Cotes for Michael Sparke, dwelling at the blue Bible in Greene Arbor, 1641; pagination and register are continuous.</note>
         <note>"Comfortable cordials" has separate title page with imprint "Printed anno. 1641"; pagination and register are separate. It may also have been issued separately (Wing P3927).</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in the Folger Shakespeare Library, Washington, D.C..</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
