<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The treachery and disloyalty of papists to their soveraignes, in doctrine and practise. Together with an exact parallel of the jurisdiction, power, and priviledges claimed and exercised by our popish Parliaments, prelates, Lords and Commons in former times, with those now claimed and practised by the present Parliament, Lords and Commons, which are here manifested to be farre more loyall, dutifull, moderate; more consistent with, lesse invasive on, and destructive to the Kings pretended soveraigne power and prerogative, then those of popish parliaments, and subjects. Wherein likewise the traiterous, antimonarchicall doctrines, practises and attempts of papists upon their soveraignes prerogatives, crownes, persons, with the dangerous consequences, effects, and designes, of their present illegall arming, and accesse to the Kings Army, and person by meanes of evill counsellours, are briefely discovered; ... It is ordered by the Committee for Printing that this treatise be forthwith printed and published, by Michael Sparke, senior. Januar. 13. 1642. John White.</title>
      <title>Soveraigne power of parliaments and kingdomes. Part 1</title>
      <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669.</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 42 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>for <persName type="publisher">Michael Sparke</persName>, <persName type="publisher">Senior.</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Printed at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1643">1643.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Attributed to William Prynne by Wing.</note>
      <note>Part 1 of: The soveraigne power of parliaments and kingdomes.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "March. 16".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Michael Sparke</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Senior.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
