<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Good tydings for sinners, great ioy for saints; or, A word to the world, and two to those that are chosen out of the world. Wherein is held forth, first, the sweet tenders of grace from the father through the son to all dejected sinners; he invites them, he woes them, he intreats them, nay, he beseecheth them to accept of mercy. In the second part of this book, called, Two words to those chosen out of the world, is spoken to the saints under their severall forms, taking notice first of the things commendable in them: and in the second place reproving them for things amisse among them. With a short prophesie of the downfall of presbyterie, independencie, anabaptismie, vaine notions, free-will. With a brief description of a true church-state, against which the gates of Hell shall not prevaile; it being founded upon a rock, it will stand against all waves and storms, that either men or devils can raise against it. I will give you all one heart, and one way. Then the Lord shall be one, and his name one. / Robert Purnell.</title>
      <author>Purnell, Robert, d. 1666.</author>
      <author>Parnell, Robert, attributed name.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 48, 57-75 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>for <persName type="publisher">Giles Calvert</persName>, and are to bee sold at <placeName>the Black-spread Eagle at the West end of Pauls</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Printed at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1649">1649.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Erroneously attributed to Robert Parnell in Wing P542.</note>
      <note>Text continuous despite pagination.</note>
      <note>Identified as both Wing P542 and as Wing P4234.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "June 1st".</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the British Library (Thomason Tracts) and the Trinity College Library, Cambridge University (Early English books).</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Giles Calvert</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Black-spread Eagle at the West end of Pauls</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
