<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A letter sent from one Mr. Parker a gentleman, dwelling at upper Wallop in Hampshire, to his friend a gentleman in London, wherein is related some remarkable passages there, as of a battell fought betweene the inhabitauts [sic] of the county, and of the cavaliers, about the settle ment of the militia, and commission of array. August 14. Also a speech as it was delivered word for word by the major of Southhamton to the high sheriffe and gentlemen of the said county concerning the militia; declaring his resolution, and his encouragement to the inhabitants to stand for the defence of true religion, the Kings prerogative, and priviledges of Parliament. Also a relation of a robbery committed by the cavalieres, and how they robbed two gentlemen of good quality within three miles of VVinchester, and tooke from them about fourescore pounds in gold and tenne pounds in silver, and how at last they were taken at a place cald Runsey, and sent to Winchester Iayle where they lye in expectation of the rigor of the law for their notorious robbery. Together with a letter to Mr. Speaker, from the county of Essex concerning the militia. Ordered that this be forthwith printed and published. Hen. Elsing Cler. Par. De. Com.</title>
      <author>Parker, John, Gentleman.</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 7, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>for <persName type="publisher">Tho. Banks</persName>,and <persName type="publisher">William Ley</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Printed at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1642">1642.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "August 17th".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Tho. Banks</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>William Ley</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
