<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The meritorious price of our redemption, iustification, &amp;c. Cleering it from some common errors; and proving, Part I. 1. That Christ did not suffer for us those unutterable torments of Gods wrath, that commonly are called hell-torments, to redeem our soules from them. 2. That Christ did not bear our sins by Gods imputation, and therefore he did not bear the curse of the law for them. Part II. 3. That Christ hath redeemed us from the curse of the law (not by suffering the said curse for us, but) by a satisfactory price of attonement; viz. by paying or performing unto his father that invaluable precious thing of his mediatoriall obedience, wherof his mediatoriall sacrifice of attonement was the master-piece. 4. A sinners righteousnesse or justification is explained, and cleered from some common errors. / By William Pinchin, Gentleman, in New-England.</title>
      <author>Pynchon, William, 1590-1662.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[12], 158 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">J.M.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">George Whittington</persName>, and <persName type="publisher">James Moxon</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>the blue Anchor in Corn-hill neer the Royall Exchange</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1650">1650.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Errata on p. 12.</note>
      <note>Part I (items 1 and 2) and Part II (items 3 and 4) are bracketed on the titlepage.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "June 2d".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>George Whittington</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>James Moxon</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>J.M.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the blue Anchor in Corn-hill neer the Royall Exchange</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
