<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A remonstrance presented to the high and mighty lords the States of Zealand by the deputies of the foure classes of Zealand. Concerning the vvelfare of the Church of England. Sent over by Walter Strickland Esquire, now in Holland, imployed for the affaires of the Parliament. Wherein the Christian affection of the ministers of Zealand, to the prosperity of their Protestan [sic] brethren in England, and their zeale to the maintenance of the true Protestant reformed religion. And the good hand of God in moving the hearts of the professors of the same religion in forraigne parts is manifested. / Published, even according to the intent of this order. Die Mercurii 24. Maii 1643. It is this day ordered by the Commons now assembled in Parliament, that the declaration of the states of Zealand, concerning the affaires of England, this day be presented to the House, be referred to the perusall and consideration of Mr. Rous Mr Reynolds and Mr. Pym, who have power to give order for the printing of it, if they shall hold it fitting. H. Elsynge. Cler. Parl. D. Com.</title>
      <author>Apollonius, Willem, 1602 or 3-1657.</author>
      <author>Lansbergen, Philips van, 1561-1632.</author>
      <author>Rogiers, Johan.</author>
      <author>Strickland, Walter, d. 1670.</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament. aut</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>8 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>May 29. London, printed by <persName type="printer">R. Oulton</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1643">Anno Dom. 1643.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Signed: Gulielmus Appolonij, Johannes Rogiers, Phillippus Iansborgius.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      <note>P.4 misnumbered p.3.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>R. Oulton</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
