<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>John the Baptist, forerunner of Christ Iesvs: or, A necessity for liberty of conscience, as the only meanes under heaven to strengthen children weake in faith; to convince hereticks mis-led in faith; to discover the gospel to all such as yet never heard thereof; and establish peace betweene all states and people throughout the world; according unto which, were both our Saviours commission, and the apostles practice for the propagation of it peaceably: as appeares most evidently by sundry Scriptures digested into chapters, with some observations at the end of every one; most humbly devoted to the use and benefit of all such as are zealously inquisitive after truth; piously disposed to imbrace it, and constantly resolved to practice it in their lives and conversations; to the honour of God, the edifying of their brethren, and their owne salvation unto eternity. The contents of the chapters follow in the next leaf. This is licenced, but not permitted to be entred according to order.</title>
         <author>Robinson, Henry, 1605?-1664?</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8], 12, 16, 13-107, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>s.n.,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[London? :</pubPlace>
         <date>1644]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Attributed to Henry Robinson by Wing.</note>
         <note>Between pages 12 and 13 are inserted 8 leaves, with pagination 1-16, containing: "Christs order, and the Disciples practice concerning the ministers maintenance, and releeving of the poore." This is intended to form chap. 2 of the whole work.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Septemb. 23."; "London. 1644.".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
