<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Christos kai kerdos. = Christ the life, and death the gain, of every true beleever: or, The life of a saint resolved into Christ, and His death into gain. Held forth clearly in a sermon preached at the late sad and solemn funeral of the right worshipful Rowland Wilson, Esq; a Member of the Parliament of England, and of the honorable Councel of State; and one of the aldermen and sheriffs of the city of London. By Obadiah Sedgvvick, B.D. and minister of the Gospel at Covent-Garden. Together with an epistle dedicatory: wherein is an exact account given upon some years more then ordinary experience of the superlative worth of this eminent servant of Christ, and of the Common-wealth. By George Cokayn, an unworthy teacher of the Gospel at Pancras Soper lane, London.</title>
      <author>Sedgwick, Obadiah, 1600?-1658.</author>
      <author>Cokayn, George, 1619-1691.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[10], 34 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">J. Macock</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Brewster</persName> and <persName type="publisher">Gregory Moul</persName>, at <placeName>the three Bibles in Pauls church-yard, neer the West end</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1650">1650.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>First three words of title are in Greek characters.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Aprill 30".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Gregory Moul</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Brewster</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>J. Macock</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the three Bibles in Pauls church-yard, neer the West end</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
