<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Secrets discovered. In Englands complaint or outcry against the high and mighty Lords, the States Generall of the United Provinces, for their perfidious, deceitfull, and unthankfull proceedings against the welfare of this kingdom. Clearly laid open in a letter transmitted to a Friend who is a subject to the said states of Holland. Wherein is declared several acts of state, not onely between them and the Queene of England, but also betweene the said states and this present Parliament, by way of answer to our Parliaments severall declarations. Likewise, a discovery that notwithstanding their firme resolutions and promises to the representative body of this kingdome, concerning their neutrality, have made use of the first opportunity to strengthen the enemy against us, and suffered our Queen (not only in the time she was there) to transport... Translated out of a Dutch printed copy into English, to undeceive this Kingdom.</title>
      <title>Engelandts klachte, ende gheschrey, over Nederlandts gheveynsde, ondanckbare, ende onbarmhertighe procedueren teghen haer. English</title>
      <author>United Provinces of the Netherlands. Staten Generaal.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 30 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Benjamin Allen</persName> in <placeName>Popes-head-Alley</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1643">Anno Dom.1643.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation of Engelandts klachte .. 1643.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "June 19th".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Benjamin Allen</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Popes-head-Alley</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
