<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The famers fam'd or An answer, to two seditious pamphlets, the one intituled The just man in bonds, the other A pearle in a dunghill, written in the behalfe of that notorious lyar, and libeller John Lilburne. Also a full reply, with a confutation of certaine objections devised by the trayterous author of a seditious and unparraled [sic] libell, intituled A remonstrance of many thousand citizens, and other free borne people of England, to their owne House of Commons, &amp;c. Wherein the wickednesse of the authors, and their abettors, the destructive courses of the sectaries, and their adherors is amply discovered. So that all (not wilfully blind) may cleerely see, that they are men stirred up by mans enemie, the Devill, as to ruine themselves, so this poore nation, that yet lies bedrid of her wounds lately received. And ought to be avoided as serpents, to be contemned as abjects, and to be delivered over to Satan, as blasphemers and reprobates. / Written by S. Shepheard.</title>
         <author>Sheppard, S. (Samuel)</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[4], 28 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for Iohn Hardesty, at the signe of the Black-spread Eagle in Duck-Lane,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1646">1646.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A reply to "The just man in bonds" (Wing L2124) by John Lilburne, and "A pearle in a dounghill" (Wing O632A) and "A remonstrance of many thousand citizens, and other free-born people of England, to their own House of Commons" (Wing O632B) by Richard Overton.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Aug: 4th".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
