<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The midwives book, or, The whole art of midwifry discovered. Directing childbearing women how to behave themselves in their conception, breeding, bearing, and nursing of children in six books, viz. ... / By Mrs. Jane Sharp practitioner in the art of midwifry above thirty years.</title>
      <title>Midwives book</title>
      <author>Sharp, Jane, Mrs.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[12], 418, [4] p., [2] leaves of plates (folded) : ill.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Simon Miller</persName>, at <placeName>the Star at the West End of St. Pauls</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1671">1671.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Publisher's catalog on [4] p. at end.</note>
      <note>Some errors in pagination.</note>
      <note>Imperfect: print show-through.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in: Henry E. Huntington Library, San Marino, California.</note>
      <note>I. An anatomical description of the parts of men and women. -- II. What is requisite for procreation : signs of a womans being with child, and whether it be male or female, and how the child is formed in the womb. -- III. The causes and hindrances of conception and barrenness and of the paines and difficulties of childbearing with their causes, signes and cures. -- IV. Rules to know when a woman is near her labour, and when she is near conception, and how to order the child when born. -- V. How to order women in childbirth, and of several diseases and cures for women in that condition. -- VI. Of diseases incident to women after conception. Rules for the choice of a nurse; her office; with proper cures for all diseases incident in young children.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Simon Miller</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Star at the West End of St. Pauls</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
