<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A warning to the world, being sundry strange prophecies revealed to Nicholas Smith, living at Tillington neer Petworth in Sussex, shoe-maker. As he was about thirty years since in the hous of one Vickers, living in the Stert at Abbington in Berkeshire, spoken to him by a man whom he affirmeth was his lord and saviour Jesus Christ; in the presence of the said Vickers (master of the inne) one Katherine Smith, one carpenter's wife, and a maid-servant of the house, who all both saw the vision, and heard all the words of this prophesie. 1. Concerning the restauration of the creatures. 2. Concerning the Bible, and all the bookes in the world. 3. Concerning my own life and conversation, 4. Concerning this particular nation, and the whole world besides. 5. Concerning things past, things present, and things to come. / Manifested by the spirit of God to me Nicholas Smith on Matthias day last, in obedience to whose blessed will and pleasure I am now come up to London to perform the work I am commanded, and lie at the sign of the Flying-horse in Thames-street neer Dowgate where I will (by the grace of God) be ready to attest the truth hereof with my life.</title>
         <author>Smith, Nicholas, d. 1680.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>8 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>s.n.,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1653">1653]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Imprint from Wing.</note>
         <note>In this edition line 6 ends "Ni-"; line 7 ends "Pet-"; line 16 ends "prophesie".</note>
         <note>Annotations on Thomason copy: "Aprill 1st 1653"; "I think formerly".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
