<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Gods unchangeableness: or Gods continued providence, in preserving, governing, ordering and disposing of all creatures, men, actions, counsels and things, as at the beginning of the world, so to the end of the world, for ever, according to the counsel of his own will. From whence is gatherd six necessary inferences very applicable to the changes, alterations and vicissitude of these our present times. Wherein is clearly demonstrated and proved, that Oliver Cromwell is by the providence of God, Lord Protector of England, Scotland and Ireland, &amp;c. to whom the people owe obedience, as to him whom God hath set over them. Unto which is added, the causes of discontent, repining and murmurings of men: also, some serious advertisements, and seasonable admonitions to the discontented, and reprehensions to all impetuous, arrogant murmurers. Together with answers to some cheif objections made against the Lord Protector and his present government, endeavouring (if possible) satisfaction to all men. / Therefore written and published for publicke good, by George Smith, Gent.</title>
      <author>Smith, George, 1602 or 3-1658.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[10], 55, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Tho. Underhill</persName> at <placeName>the Ancor</placeName> and Bible in <placeName>Pauls Churchyard</placeName>, and <persName type="publisher">Lawrence Chapman next to the Fountain Tavern</persName> in <placeName>the Strand.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1655">1655.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Jan 15:"; the final '5' in the imprint has been crossed out and replaced with a "4".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Lawrence Chapman next to the Fountain Tavern</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Tho. Underhill</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Pauls Churchyard</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Ancor</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Strand.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
