<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The second part of the duply to M.S. alias Two brethren. Wherein are maintained the Kings, Parliaments, and all civil magistrates authority about the Church. Subordination of ecclesiasticall judicatories. Refuted the independency of particular congregations. Licentiousnesse of wicked conscience, and toleration of all sorts of most detestable schismes, heresies and religions; as, idolatry, paganisme, turcisme, Judaisme, Arrianisme, Brownisme, anabaptisme, &amp;c. which M.S. maintain in their book. With a brief epitome and refutation of all the whole independent-government. Most humbly submitted to the Kings most excellent Majestie. To the most Honorable Houses of Parliament. The most Reverend and learned Divines of the Assembly. And all the Protestant churches in this island and abroad. By Adam Steuart. Octob. 3. 1644. Imprimatur Ja: Cranford.</title>
      <title>Duply to M.S. alias Two brethren. Part 2.</title>
      <author>Steuart, Adam.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8], 144, 147-194 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Iohn Field</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his house upon Addle-hill, neer Baynards-Castle</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1644">1644.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A reply to: M.S. to A.S.</note>
      <note>The words "Are maintained .. in their book." are enclosed in a complex system of brackets on the title page.</note>
      <note>Apparently published earlier than his "Zerubbabel to Sanballat and Tobiah: or, The first part of the duply to M.S. alias Two brethren", which is dated 17 March 1644 (Lady Day dating).</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Decemb: 4th".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Iohn Field</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his house upon Addle-hill, neer Baynards-Castle</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
