<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Natures explication and Helmont's vindication. Or A short and sure way to a long and sound life: being a necessary and full apology for chymical medicaments, and a vindication of their excellency against those unworthy reproaches cast on the art and its professors (such as were Paracelsus and Helmont) by Galenists, usually called Methodists. Whose method so adored, is examined, and their art weighed in the ballance of sound reason and true philosophy, and are found too light in reference to their promises, and their patients expectation. The remedy of which defects is taught, and effectual medicaments discovered for the effectual cure of all both acute and chronical diseases. / By George Starkey, a philosopher made by the fire, and a professor of that medicine which is real and not histrionical.</title>
      <author>Starkey, George, 1627-1665.</author>
      <author>Helmont, Franciscus Mercurius van, 1614-1699.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[64], 336 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">E. Cotes</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Alsop</persName> at <placeName>the two Sugar-loaves over against St. Antholins Church at the lower end of Watling-street</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1658">1657. [i.e. 1658]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Actual publication date from Wing.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Jan: 16"; the 7 in the imprint date has been crossed out and replaced with a "6".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Alsop</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>E. Cotes</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the two Sugar-loaves over against St. Antholins Church at the lower end of Watling-street</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
