<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>To the supreame authoritie the Parliament of the Common-vvealth of England. The humble petition of the officers of the army. Sheweth, that wee having had divers meetings to seeke the Lord, and to speake of the great things God hath done for this Common-Wealth, it hath been set upon our hearts as our duty to offer such things, on the behalf of this nation, as in our judgements and consciences might tend to the peace and well being thereof, and therefore in pursuance of the same, have with one consent thought it fit humbly to present to you the particulars following, which wee desire may be taken into serious consideration.</title>
      <author>Whalley, Edward, d. 1675?</author>
      <author>Hacker, Francis, d. 1660.</author>
      <author>Barkstead, John, d. 1662.</author>
      <author>Okey, John, d. 1662.</author>
      <author>Goffe, William, 1605?-1679?</author>
      <author>Worsley, Charles, 1622-1656.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>1 sheet ([1] p.)   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">M. Simmons</persName> for <persName type="publisher">L. Chapman</persName> in <placeName>Popes-head-Alley</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1652">1652.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Dated and signed at end: At the Councell of VVarre at White-Hall, the 12. of August. 1652. Ordered, that Commis: Gen: VVhalley, Col: Hacker, Col: Barkstead, Col: Okey, Col: Goffe, and Lieut. Col. Worsley doe present this petition to the Parliament tomorrow, on the behalfe of themselves, and the rest of the officers of the Army. Rich: Hatter, Secretary.</note>
      <note>Prays for reformation in the church, law, magistracy, excise, payment of public debt, arrears of pay, treatment of widows, public revenues, salaries, beggars, freedom of trades, &amp;c. (With) a resolution of the Council of War, Whitehall, 12 Aug., appointing Com.-Gen. Whalley, Cols. Hacker, Barkstead, Okey, Goffe, and Lieut.-Col. Worsley to present it -- Cf. Steele.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "August. 14th.".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>L. Chapman</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>M. Simmons</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Popes-head-Alley</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
