<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The snare broken: or light discovering darknesse. Being an answer to a book intituled, Foot yet in the snare; published by James Naylor. Wherein his treachery and back-sliding from the true faith is brought to light, and his untrodden paths discovered. With some of his divided language and deceitful lyes in short laid open, and his spirit proved to be the same which appeared in all the false prophets, who say the Lord saith, when he spake not unto them; plainly to be seen by the impartial eye, in all those whose eyes are in their head, least the wolfe should devoure the lamb, under a shadow of love to the truth. / By a lover of truth and peace, called, John Toldervy.</title>
      <author>Toldervy, John.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 28, [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">N. Brooks</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>the Angel in Cornhil</placeName>, and at <placeName>the three Bibles neer the West end of Pauls.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1656">1656.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A reply to: Naylor, James.  Foot yet in the snare.</note>
      <note>With a blank final leaf.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "January. 31 1655"; also the last number of the imprint date has been marked through and replaced with a 5.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>N. Brooks</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Angel in Cornhil</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the three Bibles neer the West end of Pauls.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
