<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The whirl-wind of the Lord gone forth as a fiery flying roule, with an alarm sounded against the inhabitants of the north-countrey. Being a fore-warning to all the rulers in England, of the mighty and terrible day of the Lord, which shall overtake the wicked; but especially and in particular, to the persecuting rulers, priests, and people, in the county of Westmerland. Who by their fruits are made manifest to all, to be open enemies to Sions converts, and a generation of evil doers, with whom the Lord Jehovah is coming to plead the cause of the oppressed, and to redeem Zion with judgement, and her converts with righteousness. G.T.</title>
      <author>Taylor, Christopher, ca. 1615-1686.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 17, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">Giles Calvert</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop, at the Black-spread-Eagle neer the west end of Pauls</placeName>, <placeName>London</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1655" cert="low">165[5]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>G.T. = Christopher Taylor, whose name appears on C1v.</note>
      <note>The last digit of the publication date has failed to print. Some copies have this filled in with a "5" in MS.</note>
      <note>Variant 1: pages 15, 16, and 17 are misnumbered 13, 12, and 9.</note>
      <note>Variant 2: pages 16 and 17 are misnumbered 12 and 9. Page 15 is numbered correctly.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Sept. 12".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Giles Calvert</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>London</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop, at the Black-spread-Eagle neer the west end of Pauls</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
