<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A true copie of the master-piece of all those petitions which have formerly beene presented by the major, aldermen, and the rest of the Common Counsell of the Citie of London. Being, two petitions; the first whereof was presented to the honourable House of Peeres now assembled in Parliament; with a certificate of the major, aldermen, and the rest of the Common Counsell of the Citie of London. The other petition, was likewise presented to the honourable House of Commons now assembled in Parliament; with their humble answer, and reasons thereof to the message which the honourable House sent to them upon Saturday, being the 22. of this instant Ianuary. These two petitions were presented the 25. of this instant January 1642. to the honourable assembly of both Houses, by the committee of aldermen and common counsell-men, selected for martiall affaires.</title>
      <author>City of London (England). Court of Common Council.</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 8 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>by <persName type="printer">R. Olton.</persName> and <persName type="printer">G. Dext er.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">J.B.</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Printed at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1642">An. Dom. 1641 [i.e. 1642]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Petition is concerned with the means of suppressing the rebellion in Ireland, the disarming of papists, etc.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>J.B.</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>G. Dext er.</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>R. Olton.</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
