<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The ansvver of the Corporation of Moniers in the mint, at the Tower of London, to two false and scandalous libells printed at London, and lately come forth without date. The first intituled, The humble representation of Peter Blondeau, as a warning touching severall disorders hapning by money ill-favouredly coyned, and the only means to prevent them. The second intituled, A most humble memorandum from Peter Blondeau. Which not only intends maliciously to sandall [sic] us the Corporation of Moniers, of the Common-wealth of England : but also most falsly to imprint in the hearts and mindes of all people in Christendome, and more especially the good people under the obedience of the Parliament of England; that ... the moneys of the of this Common-Wealth ... are not justly made ... Set forth to undeceive all the good people that have seen or read the said Peter Blondeau's false and scandalous libells.</title>
      <author>Corporation of Moniers in the Mint (London, England)</author>
      <author>Violet, Thomas, fl. 1634-1662.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 41, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">the Corporation of Moniers</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1653">1653.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Written by Thomas Violet. Cf. Wing.</note>
      <note>A response to two pamphlets by Peter Blondeau.</note>
      <note>Includes the names of all the moniers and their laborers.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the British Library (Thomason Tracts) and in the University of London (Goldsmiths'-Kress library of economic literature).</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>the Corporation of Moniers</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
