<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A true narrative of som [sic] remarkable-proceedings concerning the ships Samson, Salvador, and George, and several other prize-ships depending in the High Court of Admiralty; humbly presented to the Parliament of the Common-wealth of England, and the  Councell of State, and the Councell of Officers of his excellency the Lord Generall. / By Tho. Violet of London, gold-smith.</title>
      <author>Violet, Thomas, fl. 1634-1662.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 50, 53-106, [2], 107-114, [4] p., plates   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">William Du-Gard</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1653">an. Dom. 1653.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>The title page and epistle dedicatory exist in two settings (bound together in filmed copies, called [3] and [4]  in Thomason copies; second title page lacks vignette and has imprint: London, printed in the yeere of our Lord God. 1653.</note>
      <note>There is a plate which is bound in as frontispiece and before page 107; it reads: A list of such ships as the fleet of the Parlament of England have brought into this Common-wealth as Dutch-prizes, (which ships have all been discharged by the High Court of Admiraltie, the daies here-under written).</note>
      <note>On final leaf is postscript by the author: I desire you to take notice, that I beeing surprised in time for the sorting of my papers, and using several printers for the expedition, som of my papers have been misplaced and twice printed, through neglect of those I intrusted in this business, which I hope will bee no trouble to the judicious that read's them.</note>
      <note>Signatures: pi&#185; a-d&#178;  [A]-Z&#178;  2A-2D&#178;  2e-2f&#178;  2E&#178; .</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the British Library (Thomason Tracts), and the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery (Early English books, 1641-1700).</note>
      <note>Thomason copy bound after title page of: Mysteries and secrets of trade and mint-affairs (V583).</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>William Du-Gard</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
