<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Regimen sanitatis Salerni: or, The schoole of Salernes regiment of health. Containing, most learned and judicious directions and instructions, for the preservation, guide, and government of mans life. Dedicated, unto the late high and mighty King of England, from that university, and published (by consent of learned physicians) for a generall good. Reviewed, corrected, and inlarged with a commentary, for the more plain and easie understanding thereof. / By P.H. Dr. in Physicke, deceased. Whereunto is annexed, a necessary discourse of all sorts of fish, in use among us, with their effects appertaining to the health of man. As also, now, and never before, is added certain precious and approved experiments for health, by a right honorable, and noble personage.</title>
         <title>Regimen sanitatis Salernitatum. English and Latin.</title>
         <author>Joannes, de Mediolano.</author>
         <author>Holland, Philemon, 1552-1637.</author>
         <author>Arnaldus, de Villanova, d. 1311.</author>
         <author>Holland, Henry, 1583-1650?</author>
         <author>Paynell, Thomas.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[4], 206, [12], 207-220, [4] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by B. Alsop, dwelling in Grub-street neer the Upper-Pump,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1649 [i.e. 1650]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Attributed to Joannes de Mediolano.</note>
         <note>The original Latin verse text, with an English translation by Philemon Holland, of: Regimen sanitatis Salernitatum.</note>
         <note>With a translation by Thomas Paynell of the commentary by Arnaldus de Villanova.</note>
         <note>Dedication signed: H.H., i.e. Henry Holland.</note>
         <note>Running title reads: The regiment of health.</note>
         <note>Includes indexes.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "ffebr. 8".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
