<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The constant man's character. Intended to be sent first as a letter from a gentleman in the country, to a gentlemen his esteemed friend and countryman, a Member of the House of Commons. Since inlarged into a discourse by way of humble advice to keep him from revolting, either directly or collaterally by the side-winde of being Presbyterially affected, through the mistaken and unhappy conceit, that those who have taken the Covenant, cannot without breach of the same, assent and submit unto the late proceedings of the Parliament, when as the parts of the Covenant seem to be inconsistent within themselves, as the author's observations here discoursed do manifest. The scope whereof is 1 Historically to set down the occasion and beginnings of the war. ... 4 To prove the fitness and necessity (as matters now stand) of complying with, and submitting unto this present government. For the powers that be are ordained of God, Rom. 13. Together with some animadversions incident hereunto on the same book, and on the two declarations, intituled The declarations of the Lords and Commons assembled in Parliament at Oxford. The one touching a treaty for peace, [the] other concerning their endeavors for peace. Printed there, 1643.</title>
         <author>S. W.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[4], 77, [3] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>for Giles Calvert at the Black Spread-Eagle, neer the west end of Pauls,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>Printed at London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1650.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Signed at end: S.W.</note>
         <note>The numbers 1-4 are enclosed in brackets on title page. The words "One touching .. endeavors for peace." are enclosed in brackets with the word "The" printed once to the left of the brackets.</note>
         <note>The last leaf is blank.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Mar. 18"; the imprint date has been altered to 1649.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
