<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Jacob found in a desert land: or, A recovery of the lost out of the loss (truly manifested;) wherein is discovered the work of the Lord in the creature, and how I travelled through the night of thick darkness, which hath over spread the whole world; and of my deliverance out of darkness into the true Light and truth: wherein is witness my heavenly call into the ministry of the everlasting truth. / Given forth for the everlasting name of the Lord sake, and for their sakes, who desire to know the truth, and how I came into the truth; that they that can believe it may receive some satisfaction, (out of which all despisers and unbelievers are excluded.) By a witness of the same in life and testimony, who am a sufferer for the pure seed sake, who am known to the sons of men by the name of George Whitehead; in contempt, by the generation of despisers, called, a Quaker. With a few words to them who have any desires left in them to know the truth, whether they be in forms of profession, or out of forms, that they may see themselves, and return from their evil. Also a voyce of the thunder of the Lord from his holy temple, uttered forth to the inhabitants of the earth, who are in the Army of the Dragon (whether rulers, teachers or people.).</title>
         <author>Whitehead, George, 1636?-1723.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 20 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for Giles Calvert, and are to be sold at the Black Spread-Eagle at the west-end of Pauls,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
         <date>1656.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Septem: 26".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
