<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Plain truth vvithout feare or flattery: or a true discovery of the unlawfulnes of the Presbyterian government, it being inconsistent with monarchy, and the peoples liberties; and contrary both to the Protestation and Covenant. The end of establishing the militia of London in such hands as it is now put into by the new ordinance. The betraying votes, and destructive practises, of a trayterous party in the House of Commons, concerning certain pettions [sic] for liberty and justice. Also a vindication of his Excellency Sir Thomas Fairfax concerning certain scurrulous words uttered by some of the said faction. VVith the meanes and wayes that must be used to obtain reliefe against the said tyrannous usurpers; and for reducing the Parliament to its due rights, power and priviledges, in the preservation of the kingdomes lawes and liberties / VVritten by Amon VVilbee.</title>
      <author>Wilbee, Amon.</author>
      <author>Lilburne, John, 1614?-1657.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>8, [16] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed and published for <persName type="publisher">the information, advice, and benefit, of the poor, oppressed, betrayed, and almost destroyed commons of England</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Oxford] :</pubPlace>
      <date>1647.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Editions/issues of this work appear with differing author statements: Written by I.L. (i.e. John Lilburne), or, Written by Amon Wilbee. NUC attributes the work to John Lilburne, Wing (CD-ROM, 1996) attributes to Amon WIlbee. The Lilburne entries for this title have be cancelled in Wing.</note>
      <note>Place of publication from Wing.</note>
      <note>The last leaf is blank.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "July 2d London".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>the information, advice, and benefit, of the poor, oppressed, betrayed, and almost destroyed commons of England</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
