<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The severall examinations and confessions of the treacherous conspiratours against the citie of Bristoll. Together with the judgement of death by the Councell of War upon Robert Yeomans, late sheriffe of the said city, chief actor in the said conspiracy. Also a message from the Earl of Forth, lord lieutenant generall of His Majesties forces, in the behalf of the said conspirators, to Colonell Fines, governour and commander in chief, and the rest of the Councell of War in Bristoll. With the answer of the said Col. Fines and the Councell of War in the said city to the said message. Die Lun&#230; 22&#8304; Maii 1643. It is this day ordered by the House of Commons, that the examination of Robert Yeomans, and the rest of the examinations sent up from the Governour of Bristoll, together with the sentence of the Councell of War, and the letters, be forthwith printed. H. Elsynge Cler. Parl. D. Com.</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament. House of Commons.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>15 [i.e. 16] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Edward Husbands, and to be</persName> sold at <placeName>his Shop in the Middle Temple</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1643">May 25. MDCXLIII. [1643]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>The text includes separate statements of Robert Yeomans, George Teage, Jeremy Bucks, Moses Longman and Robert Hawkesworth, George Bourcher, Edward Hunt, John Pestor, Nath. Street.</note>
      <note>Page 16 has been misnumbered 15.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Edward Husbands, and to be</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his Shop in the Middle Temple</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
