<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A full relation of the desperate design of the malignants, for the betraying of Monmouth towne and castle: with the particular manner of the discovery thereof by Sir Trevor Williams, and the meanes used to prevent it by Col. Morgan and Lieut. Col. Kerle. And divers malignant families thereupon by proclamation put out of the said town. Also, how Lieut. col. Kerle fell into the enemies quarters neere Hereford, and took divers prisoners, horse, and armes. Likewise, a copy of Col. Sandys letter of the manner of taking Shelford house, 140. of the enemy put to the sword, the governour wounded, and 30 officers and common prisoners taken. Published by speciall command.</title>
      <author>C. W.</author>
      <author>Sandys, Richard.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 6 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Bates</persName>, at <placeName>the signe of the Maiden-head on Snow-hill</placeName>, <placeName>Holborn conduit</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1645">1645.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Two letters, the first of which is signed: C.W.; the second of which is signed: Richard Sandys.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: ""Nouemb 7th" [?; MS. ink has bled, obscuring annotation; bound after an item dated November 7th. Listed in Thomason Catalogue under November 4th].</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Bates</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Holborn conduit</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the signe of the Maiden-head on Snow-hill</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
