<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Caleb's inheritance in Canaan: by grace, not works, an answer to a book entituled The doctrine of baptism, and distinction of the covenants, lately published by Tho. Patient: wherein a review is taken, I. Of his four essentials, and they fully answered; ergo II. Dipping proved no gospel practice, from cleer scripture. III. His ten arguments for dipping refuted. IV. The two covenants answered, and circumcision proved a covenant of grace. V. His seven arguments to prove it a covenant of works, answered. VI. His four arguments to prove it a seale onely to Abraham, answered: and the contrary proved. VII. The seven fundamentals that he pretends to be destroyed by taking infants into covenant, cleeered; and the aspersion proved false. VIII. A reply to his answer given to our usual scriptures. For infant-subjects of the kingdom, in all which infant-baptism is cleered, and that ordinance justifyed, / by E.W. a member of the army in Ireland.</title>
      <author>Warren, Edward, Member of the army in Ireland.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8], 126 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">George Sawbridge</persName>, at <placeName>the sign of the Bible upon Ludgate-hill.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1655">1656 [i.e. 1655]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>"The epistle" signed: Ed. Warren.</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Octob: 23 1655"; the 6 in imprint date has been crossed out and replaced with a "5".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>George Sawbridge</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the sign of the Bible upon Ludgate-hill.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
