<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The poores advocate in 8 parts. Shewing, what an incomparable favour it is to the rich: that there are poor to accept of their charity, had they the wit to know it. Wherein is also made plain, that bounty and frugality is the best and surest way to plenty: with many other rational, and strong inducements to make men liberal; were it but for their own ends. Being enough (with the blessing of God) to change even a Nabal into a Zaccheus. By R. Yonnge [sic], florilegus. Who most earnestly begs of all rich men especially, and that for the poors sake, for Christs and the Gospels sake, but most of all for their own (even if their bodies, names, estates, precious souls and posterities) sake; to lay to heart, what is herein propounded to them out of Gods word, touching the poor: and then certainly, they will neither spend so excessively, nor heap up wealth so unmeasurably as they do; when millions of their poor brethren (for whom God would become man and die to redeem) are in such want, that I want words to express it.</title>
         <author>Younge, Richard.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 18, [2], 36 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by R. &amp; W. Leybourn, and are to be sold by James Crump, in Little Bartholomews well-yard, and to be lent gratis at the Blue Pales over against the High Constables, short of Shore-ditch Church, leaving two pence untill they do return them,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1654">1654.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Place of publication from Wing; pagination from McAplin Catalogue.</note>
         <note>The second part has caption title; register and pagination are separate.</note>
         <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "february 11".</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
