<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The works of the judicious and learned divine Dr. Thomas Taylor, part 1. sometimes preacher of Aldermanbury, London. Published by himself in his life time, in several smaller volumes, now collected together into three volumes in fol. two of which are here bound together. The first volume containing, I. An exposition on the 32. Psalm ... The second volume containing, I. An exposition of the parable of the sower and seed, on Luk. 8. ... The third volume is in the press, and will containe in it, I. The progress of sts, to full holinesse ...</title>
      <author>Taylor, Thomas, 1576-1632.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[16], 417, [13], 439-491, [15], 189, [19], 217-258, 263-303, [23], 543, [9] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">Tho. Ratcliffe</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">John Bartlet the elder, sometimes</persName> living at <placeName>the Gilt Cup in the Goldsmiths Row in Cheapside, now in the New-buildings on the south-side of Pauls neer St. Austins Gate</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1659">1659.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Gathered in 6's.</note>
      <note>In two volumes, each with separate dated title page, register and pagination; each volume has internal title pages, vertical half-titles, and indexes.</note>
      <note>"A commentary upon the epistle of St. Paul written to Titus" (also published separately as Wing (2nd ed.) T563A) has separate dated title page, pagination and register.</note>
      <note>Quire 2O is not part of foliation of the first volume.</note>
      <note>Item at reel 2219:9 is vol. 1 only, -A1 &amp; vertical half-title at end of text.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library (reel 2136) and the Dr. Williams' Library, London (reel 2219).</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>John Bartlet the elder, sometimes</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Tho. Ratcliffe</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Gilt Cup in the Goldsmiths Row in Cheapside, now in the New-buildings on the south-side of Pauls neer St. Austins Gate</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
