<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The art of ringing. [etc. ; pt 2: Artificial fireworks; and The art of gardening] giving exact rules for ringing all sorts of plain changes and cross peals, with directions for pricking; also how to hang bells, with easie directions for every thing which necessarily belongs to that art. Also Artificial fireworks; being directions to order and make moulds, ... rockets, fisgigs, and other curiosities too tedious to mention likewise The art of gardening: giving an account of the tools, or instruments necessary therein; and also what is to be done every month in the year; as likewise how to order cattle, orchards and hop-gardens, &amp;c. To which is added, an excellent receipt to make a valuable liquor agreeable to all constitutions. By J. White, gent.</title>
         <author>White, John, d. 1671.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 34, [2], 34, 12 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed for G. Conyers, at the Ring in Little-Britain,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>[1687?]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Imprint date suggested by Wing: [1680?]; G. Conyers active in London, 1686-1713 (cf. Plomer).</note>
         <note>"Artificial fireworks" has separate general title page with the order of the first two titles reversed; "The art of gardening" has caption title. Each part has individual pagination and register.</note>
         <note>Caption title on p. 1 of "The art of ringing": Tintinalogia. Or, The art of ringing improv'd.</note>
         <note>A re-publication of some parts of: White, John.  A rich cabinet with variety of inventions.</note>
         <note>Copy stained affecting legibility.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
