<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Zions ioy in her King, comming in his glory. Wherein, the estate of the poore distressed Church of the Gentiles (travailing in the wildernesse towards the new Jerusalem of the Jewes) in her utmost extremities, and height of her joyes, is lively delineated; in some mediations upon that propheticall Psalme 102. wherein the sense is opened, and many difficult places of Scripture inlightned by a harmony, and consent of the Scriptures. Delightfull and profitable to be read in these times of the Churches troubles, and much longed for restauration and deliverance. / By Finiens Canus Vove. Compiled in exile, and lately now revised and somewhat augmented as the weight of the subject and the revolution of the times required. It is ordered this three and twentieth day of January, 1642 by the Committee of the Commons House of Parliament concerning printing, that this booke intituled Zions joy in her King, comming in his glory, be printed. John White.</title>
      <author>Fenwicke, John, d. 1658.</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament. aut</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8], 142 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>for <persName type="publisher">Benjamin Allen</persName>, in <placeName>Popes-head Alley</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Printed at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1643">1643.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Finiens Canus Vove is a near-anagram of John Fenwicke, who takes credit for having written this on p. 9 of "Christ ruling in midst of his enemies" (Wing F719).</note>
      <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Aprill. 6".</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Benjamin Allen</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Popes-head Alley</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
