<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The treasurie of health contayning many profitable medicines, gathered out of Hipocrates, Galen and Auicen / by one Petrus Hyspanus, and translated into English by Humfry Lloyd, who hath added thereunto the causes and signes of euery disease, with the Aphorismes of Hipocrates, and Iacobus de Partibus, redacted to a certaine order according to the members of mans bodie, and a compendious table containing the purging and confortative medicines, with the exposition of certaine names and weights in this booke contained, with an epistle of Diocles unto Kyng Antigonus..</title>
         <author>John XXI, Pope, d. 1277.</author>
         <author>Desparts, Jacques, ca. 1380-1458.</author>
         <author>Diocles, of Carystus.</author>
         <author>Hippocrates. Aphorisms. English.</author>
         <author>Llwyd, Humphrey, 1527-1568.</author>
         <author>Pseudo-Mesuë.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[462] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>William Copland,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[London,</pubPlace>
         <date>ca. 1560].</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Attributed to John XXI, writing under the name Petrus Hyspanus.</note>
         <note>Imprint information from STC (2nd ed.).</note>
         <note>Signatures: A-Y⁸ a-g⁸ h⁴ (last leaf blank? leaf h₃ lacking?).</note>
         <note>No leaf numbered h₃, but text appears to be continuous.</note>
         <note>"A booke conteining the names of the compound medicines ..." (sign. c5r-f1v) is an adaptation of the Summula super plurimis remediis ex Mesue libris of Jacobus de Partibus (i. e. Jacques Desparts) "The epistle of Diocles, unto king Antigonus ... " (sign. g4r-g8r) is a translation of Epistola de secunda valetudine tuenda attributed to Diocles Carystius.</note>
         <note>Imperfect: Q₁, Q₈ lacking, replaced by leaves from anr. ed.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in: National Library of Wales.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
