<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A further discovery of the mystery of Jesuitisme in a collection of severall pieces representing the humours, designs, and practises of those who call themselves the Society of Jesus.</title>
         <author>Jarrige, Pierre, 1605-1660.</author>
         <author>Schoppe, Kaspar, 1576-1649. Discourse of the reasons why the Jesuits are so generally hated.</author>
         <author>Well-wisher to the Jesuits. Discovery of the Society in relation to their politicks.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[35], 75, [10], 84, [12], 33, [7], 23, [4], 24 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed for T. Dring, and are to be sold at the George in Fleet-street ...,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1658">1648. [i.e. 1658]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>"The authors dedicatory" signed at end Peter Jarrigus.</note>
         <note>Each part has added t.p. and separate paging but signatures are continuous.</note>
         <note>Wing gives date of publication as 1658.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in: Trinty College (Dublin, Ireland) Library.</note>
         <note>I. The Jesuits upon the scaffold for severall capitall crimes by them committed in the province of Guienne / by Peter Jarrigius -- II. The calumnies of James Beaufes refuted / by the same author -- III. Secret instructions for the superiours of the Societie of Jesus / faithfully rendred out of the Latine -- IV. A discourse of the reasons why the Jesuits are so generally hated / originally written by Fortunius Galindus [i.e. Kaspar Schoppe. London] : Printed for Richard Royston and Thomas Dring, 1659 -- V.A. discovery of the Society in relation to their politicks / written originally by a well-wisher to the Jesuits.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
