<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Papers delivered in by the commissioners of the kingdom of Scotland at London, to the honorable Houses of the Parliament of England containing, 1. Their answer upon the whole propositions of peace, 2. Reasons touching the militia, 3. The citations of severall passages out of the declaration of the honourable Houses concerning the militia, and uniformity in religion, 4. Reasons why the result of the Committee of Both Kingdoms at Edinburgh, 28 Novem. 1643 is a treaty.</title>
      <author>Scotland. Parliament. Committee of Estates.</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 44, 18 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>by <persName type="printer">order of the Committee of Estates</persName> by <persName type="printer">Evan Tyler his Majesites printer</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Printed at Edinburgh :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1646">1646.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Headpieces; initial letters.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the National Library of Scotland.</note>
      <note>The first paper delivered in to the Houses of Parliament by the Commissioners of Scotland, containing their answer to the whole propositions of peace -- The second paper, delivered in to the Houses of Parliament by the Commissioners of Scotland, containing reasons touching the militia -- The third paper, delivered in to the Houses of Parliament by the Commissioners of Scotland, concerning the citations of severall declarations of the Houses, concerning the militia, and uniformity of religion -- The fourth paper delivered in to the Houses of Parliament by the Commissioners of Scotland, containing their reasons, why the result of the Committee of Both Kingdomes at Edinburgh 28. Novemb. 1643 is a treaty.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Evan Tyler his Majesites printer</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>order of the Committee of Estates</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
