<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Newes from Hereford, or, A wonderful and terrible earthquake: vvith a wonderful thunder-clap, that happened on Tuesday being the first of October, 1661.  Shewing how a church-steeple, and many gallant houses were thrown down to the ground, and people slain : with a terrible thunder-clap and violent storms of great hailstone, which were about the bigness of an egg, many cattel being utterly destroy'd as they were being utterly destroy'd as they were feeding in the field.  Also the wonderful apparitions which were seen in the air to the great amazement of the beholders, who beheld two perfect arms and hands; in the right hand being grasped a great broad sword, in the left a beul full of blood, from whence they heard a most strange noise, to the wonderful astonishment of al present, the fright caused divers women to fall in travail; among whom the clerks wife one Margaret Pellmore, fell in labour, and brought forth 3 children who had teeth and spoke as soon as ever they were born, as you shall hear in the following relation, the like not known in any age.  The tune is, Aim not too high.</title>
      <author>W. K.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>1 sheet ([1] p.) : ill.  </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">F. Coles</persName>, <persName type="publisher">T. Vere</persName>, and <persName type="publisher">W. Gilbertson</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1661">1661.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Caption title.</note>
      <note>Imprint from colophon.</note>
      <note>Place of publication suggested by Wing (2nd ed.).</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in: Bodleian Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>F. Coles</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>T. Vere</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>W. Gilbertson</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
