<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The country-mans counsellour, or, Every man made his own lawyer. Plainly shewing the nature, and offices of all courts as Kings bench, common pleas, chancery, exchequer, marshalsey, &amp;c. VVith the just feas for all vvrits &amp; proceedings in each court; allowed and established by act of Parliament.  As also how to sue a man to the out-lawry, or to reverse the same: to pass a fine'er recovery, to sue an attorney or clerk, to get an injunctionin chanciry to stop your advercsaries proceedings at law, to sue in forma pauperis, &amp;c. VVith approved presidents, and easie directions for all persons, how to make according to law, bonds, bills, acquittances, general releases, letters of attorney, bills of sale, vvills, &amp;c.  work most useful to all persons, the like not extant, and now published for a general good.  With allowance / by H. R.</title>
      <author>H. R.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 22 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">J. Clarke</persName> at <placeName>the Bible</placeName> and Harp near <placeName>the hospital gate in West-smith-Field</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1682">[1682]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Place and date of publication suggested by Wing (2nd ed.).</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in: Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>J. Clarke</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Bible</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the hospital gate in West-smith-Field</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
