<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>An epistle written (dated the 30th of the 11th month 1659,) and sent from London into the countrey. By a friend to the glorious (though at this day despised) cause of Christ, in answer to a letter sent up to him (dated the 16th of the same month) wherein the following things are treated of, (viz.) 1. The fifth kingdom it self, which the God of Heaven sets up in the latter dayes. 2. The kingdom of the beast which is to be destroyed. 3. The instruments that are to be used in destroying the one and erecting the other; with the way or manner how they are to be used. 4. The time of the beginning of this work. [bracket] First, before Christs personal comming. Secondly, before the call of the Jewes. Thirdly, that it is already begun, and hath taken place in this nation and that Cromwel with the army, hath apostatized from it, and that all the powers, or governments that have been set up since that time, have been, and still are upon the foundation of the apostacy. As also, severall of the particular evills which the army, and others abetting the apostacy are guilty of. Together with, some considerations tendered to the favourers of Christ's righteous cause, wherein is laid down, their duty of separation from Babylon, and from all the parts and branches (both in church and state) of the forementioned apostacy.</title>
      <author>N. S.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 48 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">the author</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1660">1660.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Signed: N.S.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the University of Toronto Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>the author</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
