<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Tvvo sermons preached before the Kings Maiestie at Whitehall. Of the birth of Christ The one on Christmas day anno 1609. The other on Christmas last anno 1610. By the Bishop of Elie his Maiesties almoner.</title>
      <author>Andrewes, Lancelot, 1555-1626.</author>
      <author>Andrewes, Lancelot, 1555-1626. Sermon preached before the Kings Majestie at White-hall, on Munday the 25. of December, being Christmas day, anno 1609. aut</author>
      <author>Andrewes, Lancelot, 1555-1626. Sermon preached before His Majestie at White-Hall, on Tuesday the 25. of December last, being Christmas day. aut</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 41, [3]; [4], 46, [2] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">Robert Barker</persName>, printer to <persName type="patron">the Kings most Excellent Maiestie</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1610">Anno 1610.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Bishop of Elie = Lancelot Andrewes.</note>
      <note>The last leaf in each register is blank.</note>
      <note>The first leaf (second series) contains a large signature-mark "A" with part of a woodcut frame.</note>
      <note>Signature E (second series) wrongly imposed.</note>
      <note>"A sermon preached before the Kings Maiestie at White-hall, on Munday the 25. of December, being Christmas day, anno 1609" and "A sermon preached before His Maiestie at White-Hall, on Tuesday the 25. of December last, being Christmas day" each has separate title page (the first bearing the imprint date 1610), pagination and register; each work was possibly issued separately (STC 618 and 613).</note>
      <note>Identified as STC 627 on UMI microfilm reel 613; part 1 identified as 618 on UMI microfilm reel 867.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the British Library, Cambridge University Library, and the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
      <note>Appears at reel 613 (Cambridge University Library copy), at reel 733 (British Library copy), and at reel 867 (Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery copy).</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Robert Barker</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="patron">
      <persName>the Kings most Excellent Maiestie</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
