<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A soveraigne antidote against sabbatarian errours. Or, A decision of the chiefe doubts and difficulties touching the Sabbath Wherein these three questions (beside others coincident) are clearly and succinctly determined, viz. I. Which is the fittest name whereby to call the day of Christian weekly rest, whether Sabbath day, Lords-day, or Sunday? II. What is the meaning of that prayer, appointed to be used by our Church: Lord have mercy upon us, and encline, &amp;c. as it is repeated and applyed to the words of the fourth Commandment. III. Whether it be lawfull to use any bodily recreation on the Lords-day? and if so, what kinde of recreation? By a reverend, religious, and judicious divine.</title>
      <author>Reverend, religious, and judicious divine.</author>
      <author>Sanderson, Robert, 1587-1663, attributed name.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[8], 27, [5] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Thomas Harper</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Benjamin Fisher</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his shop in Aldersgate-street at the signe of the Talbot</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1636">1636.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Sometimes attributed to Robert Sanderson.</note>
      <note>Cf. Folger catalog, which gives signatures: A-E&#8308;.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: A treatise concerning the Sabbath.</note>
      <note>The last two leaves bear (1) imprimatur and (2) colophon.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in Cambridge University Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Benjamin Fisher</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Thomas Harper</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop in Aldersgate-street at the signe of the Talbot</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
