<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The lamentations and holy mourninges of the prophet Ieremiah with a lamentable paraphrase and exhortation, meete euery way to be applyed vnto these our dayes: for the comforting of all the true faithfull children of God that are vnder the crosse and feele their miseries: and for the awaking of all those that haue no feeling of their miseries: not-with-standing the great calamities which haue fallen and still are like to fall vpon these our dayes. Published by Daniel Toussaine, and translated out of French into English, by Tho. Sto. gent.</title>
      <title>Les lamentations et saincts regretz du prophete Jeremie. English.</title>
      <author>Tossanus, Daniel, 1541-1602.</author>
      <author>Stocker, Thomas, fl. 1569-1592.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[46], 264 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Iohn Windet</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">Humfrey Bate</persName>, and are to be solde at <placeName>his shop in Paternoster rowe at the signe of the Blacke Horse</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1587" cert="low">[1587?]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A translation, by Thomas Stocker, of: Toussain, Daniel. Les lamentations et saincts regretz du prophete Jeremie, avec paraphrase et exposition appropri&#233;e &#224; ce temps en toutes sortes lamentable.</note>
      <note>Running title reads: The lamentations of Ieremiah.</note>
      <note>Identified as STC 24144a on UMI microfilm.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Folger Shakespeare Library.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the Cambridge University Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Humfrey Bate</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Iohn Windet</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>his shop in Paternoster rowe at the signe of the Blacke Horse</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
