<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The voluntarie conuersion and seuerall recantations, of foure great learned men, professed fryers in sundry monasteries of Fraunce, from the errours of idolatrie and poperie, to the true religion established in the Reformed Church. 1. Master Iohn Le Vager, a priest in the Romane Church, conuerted at Mauns, Ianuary 6. 2. Master Iohn Forent, a fryer Carmelite, in the Court of Morthemard, conuerted in the Reformed Church of Poictiers, Iune, 9. 3. Master Denis Boucher, a Franciscane fryer, in the couent of Noisy, neere Paris, conuerted in the Reformed Church of Paris, Iuly. 6. 4. Master Daniell Dusert,  Franciscan fryer at Mello, conuerted in the Church of Mello, December, 22. All conuerted this last yeare, 1603. as their seuerall discourses following at large doe testifie, vnder their owne hands. Truely translated, out of the French printed copies.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 44 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>By <persName type="printer">Richard Bradocke</persName>, for <persName type="publisher">W. Iones [2]</persName>, dwelling at <placeName>the signe of the Gun, neere Holborne Conduit:</placeName> and are to be solde by <persName type="bookseller">W. Aspley</persName>, in <placeName>Paules Church-yard</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>Imprinted at London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1604">1604.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Clarification regarding W. Jones from STC.</note>
      <note>Leaves F2-3 cropped at head, with some loss of print.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>W. Iones [2]</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Richard Bradocke</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>W. Aspley</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Paules Church-yard</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the signe of the Gun, neere Holborne Conduit:</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
