<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Six sermons upon severall occasions preached before the King, and elsewhere: by that late learned &amp; reverend divine John Donne, Doctour in divinitie, and Dean of S. Pauls, London.</title>
      <author>Donne, John, 1572-1631.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[6], 37, [3], 40, [2], 24, [2], 26, [2], 23, [3], 16 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">[Thomas Buck</persName> and <persName type="printer">Roger Daniel] the printers to the Vniversitie of Cambridge:</persName> and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Nicholas Fussell</persName> and <persName type="bookseller">Humphrey Mosley</persName>, at <placeName>their shop in Pauls Church-yard [</placeName>, <placeName>London]</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[Cambridge] :</pubPlace>
      <date>1634.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>The first leaf is blank except for an ornament.</note>
      <note>"Two sermons preached before King Charles, upon the xxvi verse of the first chapter of Genesis", "The second sermon preached before King Charles, upon the xxvi verse of the first chapter of Genesis", "A sermon upon the xix verse of the ii chapter of Hosea", "A sermon upon the xliiii verse of the xxi chapter of Matthew", "A sermon upon the xxii verse of the v chapter of John", and "A sermon upon the xv verse of the viii chapter of John" each has separate dated title page and pagination; register is continuous.</note>
      <note>"Two sermons preached before King Charles, upon the xxvi verse of the first chapter of Genesis" is separately listed as STC 7058 and may have been issued separately, but its title page is conjugate with the general title.</note>
      <note>"A sermon upon the xv verse of the viii chapter of John" identified as STC 7055 on UMI microfilm reel 1234.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the Bodleian Library and Harvard University. Library.</note>
      <note>Appears at reel 1234 (Bodleian Library copy) and at reel 1269 (Harvard University. Library copy, "A sermon upon the xv verse of the viii chapter of John" only).</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Humphrey Mosley</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="bookseller">
      <persName>Nicholas Fussell</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Roger Daniel] the printers to the Vniversitie of Cambridge:</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>[Thomas Buck</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>London]</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>their shop in Pauls Church-yard [</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
