<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Ianuary 12. Numb. 6. The continuation of our vveekely avisoes, since the 2. ditto to the 12. of the same Containing amongst divers other things these particulars following; the arrivall of the Queene of Sweden at the citie of Wittenburg, where a few houres after came a messenger from the King of Sweden, that presented her with these particulars following. An image of the child Iesus of pure gold ... and another image of S. Martin of pure gold; all which amongst other he had taken, being ornaments of popish churches. The present state of Tillyes armie ... The rendring of the citie of Mentz, and Oppenheym, with the taking of that castle by assault, with the articles of agreement vpon the former rendring. The cruell and barbarous behaviour of the Spanisp [sic] towards all the townes which they doe forsake before they depart away from them. The King of Sweden hath lately taken in the Palatinate these townes; Oppenheym, Crutznatk, Bagrag, Ladenburg, Slakenburg, and all the Bergstraight ...</title>
         <author>Butter, Nathaniel, d. 1664, publisher.</author>
         <author>Bourne, Nicholas, publisher.</author>
         <author>Dawson, John, printer.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 14 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed [by John Dawson?] for Nath: Butter and Nicolas Bourne,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1632.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Printer's name conjectured by STC.</note>
         <note>No. 6 in a series published between 29 Nov. 1631 and 12 Oct. 1632 by Nathaniel Butter and Nicholas Bourne (cf. Dahl).</note>
         <note>Identified as part of STC 11178 on UMI microfilm.</note>
         <note>Reproductions of the originals in the British Library.</note>
         <note>Bound and filmed with eight other issues of Foreign avisoes.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
