<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Cent. 3. Numb. 48. The continuation of the forraine occurents for 5. weekes last past, containing many very remarkable passages of Germanie, France, Spaine, Italy, Sweden, the Low-Countries, and other parts of the world Amongst which are these following particulars. 1. The rebellion and falling away of Catalonia confirmed, with their conjunction with the French. 2. The revolt and crowning of a new King of Portugall (the Duke of Briganza) by the name of Iohn the Fourth. 3. The proceedings of Bannier and the Swedish armies in Germany. 4. The taking of Carthagena and the plate fleet in the harbour there by the Hollanders. 5. What hath lately passed at the Dyet at Ratisbone. Examined and licenced by a better and more impartiall hand then heretofore.</title>
      <author>Butter, Nathaniel, d. 1664, publisher.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 419-464 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>for <persName type="publisher">Nath: Butter</persName>, dwelling at <placeName>St. Austins Gate</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, Printed Ianuary 11. 1640 :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1641">[1641]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Imprint date is given according to Lady Day dating.</note>
      <note>No. 48 in a series of newsbooks published between the beginning of March 1640, and the end of January or beginning of February 1641 by Nathaniel Butter and Nicholas Bourne (cf. Dahl).</note>
      <note>Identified as STC 11178 on microfilm.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      <note>Bound and filmed with eight other issues of Foreign avisoes.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Nath: Butter</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>St. Austins Gate</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
