<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The continuation of ovr weekely avisoes, since the 30. of the last moneth to this present Containing amongst the rest these particulars following. 1 The free exercise of the Protestant relgion in Ratisbone, or Reginspurgh. 2 Other letters written and sent by Henry Earle of Vandenberg; the one to the Infanta, manifesting his discontent, the other to the states, prelates, nobility, gentry, cities, and provinces of the Netherlands. 3 A letter from Norimberg concerning the King of Sweden his being at Furte with 20000. experienced souldiers, intending to meete with Walsteyn in Bohemia. 4 The passages of the Duke of Saxonie, and Walsteyn, or Freedland, before the King of Sweden came neere them. 5 The late accord betwixt the French King, and the D. of Lorraine. 6 Generall Pappenheym beaten by the Lands-graue of Hessen. 7 The great discontent amongst the subjects of the Arch-Dutches, vpon the revolt of the Lords.</title>
         <title>Continuation of our weekely avisoes, since the 30. of the last moneth to this present.</title>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 13, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by I. D[awson] for Nathaniel Butter and Nicholas Bourne,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1632.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>At head of title page: Iuly 6. Numb. 32.</note>
         <note>Printer's name from STC.</note>
         <note>Formerly STC 25198.</note>
         <note>Identified on UMI microfilm as STC 25198.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Cambridge University Library.</note>
         <note>With: The continvation of ovr weekely avisoes, since the 19. of this present. Iuly 25. Numb. 35. London : Printed by I.D. for Nathaniel Butter and Nicholas Bourne, 1632.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
