<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Iune 6. Numb. 26. The continuation of our forraine avisoes, since the 28. of the last moneth, to this present 1. The care of the old King and State of Poland, to provide for the defence of Lituania, and the confines, against the present invasion of the Muscovite. 2. The like care of the late King of Poland, for the governement of that kingdome in the interregnum, (being sicke) if in case he should die, and of his death on the 29. of Aprill following. 3. The names of some of the competitors which doe now labour to make a faction to be elected king. 4. The latest and best confirmed newes of the King of Sweden his proceeding in Bavaria, and of those cruelties vsed by the mutinous Boores against some of the Swedes, whereupon the King hath beene forced to punish that country, more then hee hath done any place, since he came into Germany [...]</title>
         <author>Butter, Nathaniel, d. 1664, publisher.</author>
         <author>Bourne, Nicholas, publisher.</author>
         <author>Dawson, John, printer.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 14 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>printed [by John Dawson] for Nathanaell Butter and Nicolas Bourne,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1632.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Printer's name from Dahl.</note>
         <note>No. 26 in a series published between 29 Nov. 1631 and 12 Oct. 1632 by Nathaniel Butter and Nicholas Bourne (Cf. Dahl).</note>
         <note>Formerly STC 11178 and 25201c.</note>
         <note>Identified as STC 11178 on UMI microfilm reel 1097 and as STC 25201c on UMI microfilm reel 1087.</note>
         <note>Imperfect; Cambridge University Library copy lacks title page; British Library copy stained and faded affecting print.</note>
         <note>Reproductions of the originals in the Cambridge University Library (reel 1087) and the British Library (reel 1097).</note>
         <note>Appears at reel 1087 (Cambridge University Library copy) and at reel 1097 (British Library copy).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
