<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>September 1. Numb. 42. The continuation of our weekely avisoes, since the 23. of the last, to the first of this present Conteining amonst the rest, these particulars following. A patheticall speech made by the King of Sweden to his commaunders and captaines, vpon occasion of some misdemeanors committed by the souldiers. The confirmation of the burning of the Walsteyn and Bavarian magazen at Fryenstadt, together with the defeat given vnto some imperiall regiments at the same time. The taking of great Glogaw and Breslaw, with other townes in Silesia, by the nixt forces of the Swedes, Saxons and Brandenburgers. The preparation of the King of Sweden by (command of a generall fast throughout the whole army, and in the city of Norimberg) to goe vpon some great designe, most of his forces being come to him. Something concerning France, and the troubles there.</title>
      <author>Butter, Nathaniel, d. 1664, publisher.</author>
      <author>Bourne, Nicholas, publisher.</author>
      <author>Dawson, John, printer.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 14 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">I[ohn]. D[awson].</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Nathaniel Butter</persName> and <persName type="publisher">Nicholas Bourne</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1632.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>A variant of STC 266, with title corrected (cf. STC).</note>
      <note>Printer's name from Dahl.</note>
      <note>No. 42 in a series of newsbooks published between 29 Nov. 1631 and 12 Oct. 1632 by Nathaniel Butter and Nicholas Bourne (cf. Dahl).</note>
      <note>Identified as STC 11178 on UMI microfilm reel 1097.</note>
      <note>Bound and filmed with eight other issues of Foreign avisoes.</note>
      <note>Reproductions of the originals in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Nathaniel Butter</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Nicholas Bourne</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>I[ohn]. D[awson].</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
