<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A continuation of the former newes Three great inuasions already attempted: the one by Bethlem Gabor, who with the Turkes is already come downe beyond the riuer Donaw: the other by the Count of Thurne, hauing the command of the Marquis of Iaggendorps forces, hath now entred into Selesia: the last by the Tartars vpon Polonia, which hath driuen them all to amazement. With the present estate of the siege of Breda, and in what manner Spinola hath beleager'd the towne. Likewise the resolution of the Colledge of Electors, concerning the succession of the Palatinate; as also the late commotion newly hapned in Rome; with the arrest of the Emperors Ambassador in Turkie, and diuers other occurrents.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 19, [1]   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Thomas Archer</persName>, and <persName type="publisher">Beniamin Fisher:</persName> and are to be sold in <placeName>Popes head Alley, ouer against the signe of the Horse-shoo</placeName>, and in <placeName>Pater-noster Row at the signe of the Talbot</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1624">[1624]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>At head of title page: Septemb. 9. Numb. 23 [i.e. 32--STC].</note>
      <note>Publication date from STC.</note>
      <note>Formerly STC 25200.</note>
      <note>Identified as STC 25200 on UMI microfilm.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Beniamin Fisher:</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>Thomas Archer</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Pater-noster Row at the signe of the Talbot</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Popes head Alley, ouer against the signe of the Horse-shoo</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
