<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>An oration or speech appropriated vnto the most mightie and illustrious princes of Christendom Wherein the right and lavvfulnesse of the Netherlandish warre, against Philip King of Spain is approved and demonstrated. Composed by a Netherlandish gentleman, and faithfully translated out of divers languages into Dutch, and now Englished by Thomas Wood. According to the printed copie at Amsterdam, by Michael Collyne stationer, dwelling upon the water at the corner of the old Bridge street, anno 1608.</title>
         <title>De jure belli Belgici. English</title>
         <author>Verheiden, Jacob, fl. 1590.</author>
         <author>Verheiden, Willem, 1568-1596, attributed name.</author>
         <author>Ofwod, Stephen.</author>
         <author>Wood, Thomas, fl. 1615-1624.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[2], 70, [2], 14 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed [by the successors of Giles Thorp],</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[Amsterdam] :</pubPlace>
         <date>anno 1624.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A Netherlandish gentleman = Jacob Verheiden. Sometimes also attributed to Willem Verheiden.</note>
         <note>A translation of: De jure belli Belgici.</note>
         <note>Identification of printer from STC.</note>
         <note>"An adioyner of sundry other particular wicked plots and cruel, inhumane, perfidious; yea, unnaturall practises of the Spaniards .. Gathered and translated .. by S.O. [i.e. Stephen Ofwod]" has separate dated title page and pagination; register is continuous.</note>
         <note>"An adjoynder" identified as STC 18757 on UMI microfilm reel 1212.</note>
         <note>Reproductions of the originals in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery and the British Library.</note>
         <note>Appears at reel 1180 (Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery copy) and at reel 1212 (British Library copy).</note>
         <note>Reel 1180: page 19 faded. Beginning-page 25 from Harvard University. Library spliced at end.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
