<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>De adiaphoris Theological and scholastical positions, concerning the nature and vse of things indifferent. Where also is methodically and briefely handled, of ciuill and ecclesiasticall magistrates, of humane lawes, of Christian libertie, of scandall, and of the worship of God. A vowed worke, destinated (by the grace of God) to appease the dissentions of the Church of England. Written in Latine by M. Gabriel Powel, and translated into English by T.I.</title>
         <title>De adiaphoris. English</title>
         <author>Powel, Gabriel, 1576-1611.</author>
         <author>Jackson, Thomas, 1579-1640, attributed name.</author>
         <author>T. I., fl. 1607.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[12], 191, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Imprinted by Felix Kyngston, for Edvvard White, and are to be sold at the little North-doore of Pauls, at the signe of the Gun,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1607.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A translation, sometimes attributed to Thomas Jackson, Dean of Peterborough, of: Powel, Gabriel.  De adiaphoris.</note>
         <note>Half-title reads: Two profitable and necessarie treatises. The I. Analyticall. Concerning the nature and use of things indifferent .. The II. Apologeticall. Containing a defence of the proceedings against the refractarie ministers ..</note>
         <note>Part 2, "A reioynder unto the Mild defence", is an answer to William Bradshaw's "A myld and just defence of certeyne arguments, at the last session of Parliament directed to that most Honorable High Court, in behalfe of the ministers suspended and deprived &amp;c: for not subscribing and conforming themselves etc.". It has a divisional title page; pagination and register are continuous.</note>
         <note>Part 2 was formerly STC 20143.</note>
         <note>Part 2 identified as STC 20143 on UMI microfilm.</note>
         <note>Reproductions of the originals in the Bodleian Library and Emmanuel College (University of Cambridge). Library (Part 2 only).</note>
         <note>Appears at reel 1001 (Bodleian Library copy) and at reel 1285 (Emmanuel College (University of Cambridge). Library (Part 2 only).</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
