<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>An explication of the iudiciall lawes of Moses. Plainely discovering divers of their ancient rites and customes. As in their governours, government, synedrion, punishments, civill accompts, contracts, marriages, warres, and burialls. Also their oeconomicks, (vizt.) their dwellings, feasting, clothing, and husbandrie. Together with two treatises, the one shewing the different estate of the godly and wicked in this life, and in the life to come. The other, declaring how the wicked may be inlightned by the preaching of the gospel, and yet become worse after they be illuminated. All which are cleered out of the originall languages, and doe serue as a speciall helpe for the true understanding of divers difficult texts of scriptures. ... / By Iohn Weemse, of Lathocker in Scotland, preacher of Gods word.</title>
         <author>Weemes, John, 1579?-1636.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[30], 221, [2] p. : ill. (woodcuts)  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by Iohn Dawson for Iohn Bellamie, and are to be sold at his shoppe at the signe of the three Golden Lyons in Cornehill, neere the Royall Exchange,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1632">1632.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>General title page for Volume 3 of the "Workes", included following index.</note>
         <note>Signatures: A4, )(4, ][4, *4. B-Ff4.</note>
         <note>Includes indexes.</note>
         <note>With a final addendum leaf.</note>
         <note>Usually bound with: Exercitations divine: London, 1632.</note>
         <note>This item also appears as part of STC 25207.5 at reels 1297:1 and 2019:2.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in Yale University Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
