<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>His Maiesties ansvver, to the petition; concerning the disbanding of his gaurd [sic]: as also, his proclamation forbiding all his Majesties subjects belonging to the trained bands, or militia of this kingdom, to rise, march, muster, or exercise by vertue of any order or ordinance of one or both Houses of Parliament, without consent or warrant from His Majestie, upon paine of punishment according to the law. VVhereunto are annexed, two orders of both Houses of Parliament: the one to all high sheriffs, and other officers within a hundred and fiftie miles of the citie of York. The other, in particular to the high sheriffs, and other officers, within the countie of Lancaster: in generall, to all the counties of England, and Dominion of Wales. VVith votes of both Houses of Parliament, and sundery articles, or acts of Parliament, to confirme the same. Taken out of the records of the Tower. / Die Sabbathi 28. May. 1642. Ordered by the Lords in Parliament, that these votes with the articles, be forthwith printed, and published. Jo. Browne Cleric. Parliamentorum.</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Sovereign (1625-1649 : Charles I)</author>
      <author>Charles I, King of England, 1600-1649.</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>8 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed the first of Iune, for <persName type="publisher">W. Gaye</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London: :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1642">1642..</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Imperfect: stained, and with print bleeding and show-through, with loss of print.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>W. Gaye</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
