<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Rome exactly describ'd, as to the present state of it, under Pope Alexandre the Seventh in two curious discourses / written originally in Italian, and translated into English.</title>
         <title>Relazione della corte romana fatta l'anno 1661. English</title>
         <author>Ferrare du Tot, Charles de, d. 1694.</author>
         <author>Correr, Angelo, 1605-1678.</author>
         <author>Chantry, John, d. 1662?</author>
         <author>Bulteel, John, fl. 1683.</author>
         <author>Torriano, Giovanni.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>2 pts. ([19], 109; [16], 64 p.) : port.  </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by T. Mabb, for Mich. Young ..., and J. Starkey ..., and J. Playfere ...,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date>1664.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Part 1 is a translation of Relazione della corte romana fatta l'anno 1661, previously attributed to Angelo Correr, but now recognized to be by Charles Du Tot. Translation is by John Bulteel (J.B).  Cf. Diz. biog. degli Italiani, v. 29, p. 483. Part 2 is a translation of Relatione di Roma del Almaden;  cf. BM, v. 206, col. 202.</note>
         <note>Part 2 (A new relation of Rome) appears on reels 430, 487, and 704; part 1 on reel 487 only.</note>
         <note>Port. of Pope Alexander VII engraved by John Chantry.</note>
         <note>Pages 19 and 35 of pt. 1 are tightly bound with some loss of text in filmed copy.  Pages 10-45 photographed from Bodleian Library copy and inserted at end.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in: Bodleian Library; Cambridge University Library.</note>
         <note>Entries for N739 and T1927 (both called A new relation of Rome) cancelled in Wing (2nd ed.).</note>
         <note>A relation of the state of the court of Rome made in the year 1661 at the Council of Pregadi / by ... Angelo Corraro ... ; translated out of Italian by J.B. Gent. -- A new relation of Rome ... / taken out of one of the choicest cabinets of Rome, and Englished by Gio. Torriano ...</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
