<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A catalogue of books, of the several libraries of the Honorable Sir William Coventry, and the Honorable Mr. Henry Coventry, sometime Secretary of State to King Charles II. Containing a very good collection of most excellent books in divinity, history, philology, matters of state, &amp;c. in Greek, Latin, Italian, French, Spanish and English, to be sold by auction, at the late dwelling-house of Mr. Secretary Coventry, at the upper end of the Hay-market, Peccadilly, on Monday the ninth of May, 1687..</title>
      <author>Coventry, Henry, 1619-1686.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[4], 44 p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Catalogues are to be had gratis at <placeName>Mr. William Cooper's at the Pelican in Little-Britain</placeName>, <placeName>Mr. George Wells's at the Sun in St. Pauls Church-yard</placeName>, <placeName>Mr. Tho. Dring's at the Harrow at Chancery-Lane end</placeName>, <placeName>Fleet-street</placeName>, <placeName>Mr. Sam. Carr's at the Adam</placeName> and Eve near <placeName>Hungerford-Market</placeName>, <placeName>Strand</placeName>, <placeName>Mr. William Nott at the Queens Arms in the Pall-mall</placeName>, <placeName>Mr. Man's, at the Royal Coffee-House</placeName>, <placeName>Charing-Cross</placeName>, and at <placeName>Finches Coffee-House in Birchin-lane</placeName>, <placeName>London</placeName>, and at <placeName>the Coffee-Houses in Oxford</placeName> and Cambridge.,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1687">1687..</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Charing-Cross</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Finches Coffee-House in Birchin-lane</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Fleet-street</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Hungerford-Market</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>London</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Mr. George Wells's at the Sun in St. Pauls Church-yard</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Mr. Man's, at the Royal Coffee-House</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Mr. Sam. Carr's at the Adam</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Mr. Tho. Dring's at the Harrow at Chancery-Lane end</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Mr. William Cooper's at the Pelican in Little-Britain</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Mr. William Nott at the Queens Arms in the Pall-mall</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Strand</placeName>
    </place>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>the Coffee-Houses in Oxford</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
