<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_sourceDesc.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>At the court at Whitehall, the 28th of October, 1664 Present the kings most excellent Majesty. His royal highness the Duke of York. Lord Chancellor. Lord Treasurer. Duke of Albemarle. Duke of Ormond. Lord Chamberlain. Earl of Anglesey. Earl of Lauderdail. Earl of Middleton. Lord Bishop of London. Lord Ashely. Mr. Vice-Chamberlain. Mr. Secretary Morice. Mr. Secretary Bennet. Mr. Chancellor of the Dutchy. Sir Edward Nicholas. It was this day ordered (His Majestie present in Council) that his Majesties declaration, for incouragement of sea-men and mariners imployed in the present service, be forthwith printed by his Majesties printer, &amp;c. Richard Browne. His Majesties declaration for encouragement of seamen and mariners employed in the present service.</title>
      <title>Orders in Council. 1664-10-28.</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Sovereign (1660-1685 : Charles II)</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Privy Council. aut</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>1 sheet ([1] p.)   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">John Bill</persName> and <persName type="printer">Christopher Barker</persName>, printers to <persName type="patron">the Kings most Excellent Majesty</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date when="1664">1664.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Cf. edition at Wing E811B, title of which begins: His Majesties declaration for encouragement of sea-men &amp; mariners employed in the present service.</note>
      <note>Identified on reel as C2964 (entry cancelled in Wing 2nd ed.).</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the Society of Antiquities Library, London.</note>
      <note>Allowance instead of prize money 10s. per tun for every piece of ordnance; goods or merchandise above the gun-deck to be lawful pillage. The charges of sick and wounded will be provided.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Christopher Barker</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>John Bill</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="patron">
      <persName>the Kings most Excellent Majesty</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
