<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>By the Lords Justices, a proclamation. Tho. Cantuar. J. Sommers C.S. Pembroke C.P.S. Shrewsbury. Whereas by an Act made the last session of Parliament, intituled, An Act for the encrease and encouragement of seamen. It was, amongst other things, enacted, that all and every able mariner, seaman, waterman, fisherman, ...</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Lords Justices.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>1 sheet ([1] p.).   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Charles Bill, and the executrix of Thomas Newcomb, deceas'd;</persName> printers to <persName type="patron">the King's most excellent Majesty</persName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
      <date>1696.</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>At end of text: Given at our court at Whitehall, the tenth day of August, 1696. In the eighth year of His Majesties reign.</note>
      <note>Recites provisions of Act for the encrease and encouragement of seamen. The office for registering subjects capable of sea-service and willing to enter is on Tower-Hill in London, and the collectors of the customs at the ports are appointed 'Registers' for the purpose. -- Steele.</note>
      <note>Steele notation: Arms 124  and for or.</note>
      <note>Filmed copy at UMI Tracts Supplement reel C15 followed by docket title in mss.</note>
      <note>Filmed copy at UMI Tract Supplement reel C18 followed by 6 sheets of miscellaneous mss.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="patron">
      <persName>the King's most excellent Majesty</persName>
    </person>
    <person type="printer">
      <persName>Charles Bill, and the executrix of Thomas Newcomb, deceas'd;</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
</sourceDesc>
