<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Anno Regni Caroli II Regis Angliæ, Scotiæ, Franciæ &amp; Hiberniæ, vicesimo secundo &amp; vicesimo tertio. At the Parliament begun at Westminster the eighth day of May, anno. Dom. 1661 ... And there continued by several prorogations to the fourteenth day of February 1669/70 ... An act to prevent malicious maiming and wounding.</title>
         <title>Public General Acts. 1670-1671. 22 &amp; 23 Car.II</title>
         <author>England and Wales.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[8], 3-104, [2], 109-173, [3], 175-176, 183-250, 249-292 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by the assigns of John Bill and Christopher Barker, printers to the Kings most Excellent Majesty,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>In the Savoy, :</pubPlace>
         <date>1670/1 [i.e. 1671]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Although the title page states that it is for 22 &amp; 23 Charles II, the dates given and the imprint date are for the session of 22 Charles II. The contents are for the session of 22 &amp; 23 Charles II, which began 29 Dec. 1670 and ended 22 April 1671.</note>
         <note>With a table of the acts on the three leaves following the general title page.</note>
         <note>Text is continuous despite pagination.</note>
         <note>Identified on film as part of Wing E1250 (number cancelled).</note>
         <note>Item at 1776:17 imperfect: partial copy, item ends at p. 104.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
         <note>With: Anno Regni Caroli II. Regis Angliæ, Scotiæ, Franciæ &amp; Hiberniæ, vicesimo secundo. At the Parliament begun at Westminster the eighth day of May, anno. Dom. 1661. ... And there continued by several prorogations to the 14th day of February 1669/70. From whence it is continued by adjournment made the 11th of April 1670. to the 24th day of October following. In the Savoy, : Printed by the assigns of John Bill and Christopher Barker ..., 1670 -- Anno Regni Caroli II Regis Angliæ, Scotiæ, Franciæ &amp; Hiberniæ, vicesimo quinto. At the Parliament begun at Westminster the eighth day of May, anno. Dom. 1661. ... And there continued by several prorogations to the fourth day of February 1672/73. London, : Printed by the assigns of John Bill and Christopher Barker ..., 1673.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
