<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>A Reply of two of the brethren to A. S. wherein you have observations on his considerations, annotations, &amp;c. upon the apologeticall narration : with a plea for libertie of conscience for the apologists church way, against the cavils of the said A. S., formerly called M. S. to A. S. : humbly submitted to the judgements of all rationall and moderate men in the world : with a short survey of W. R. his Grave confutation of the separation, and some modest and innocent touches on the letter from Zeland and Mr. Parker's from New-England.</title>
         <author>Goodwin, John, 1594?-1665.</author>
         <author>Steuart, Adam. Some observations and annotations upon the Apologetical narration. Selections.</author>
         <author>Parker, Thomas, 1595-1677.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <editionStmt>
         <edition>The second edition, corrected, and inlarged.</edition>
      </editionStmt>
      <extent>[4], 112 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by M. Simmons, for H. Overton,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1644">1644.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Attributed to Goodwin by T. Jackson, A life of John Goodwin, 1882, p. 57, on the basis of a passage in Goodwin's Innocencies Triumph, 1644, p.4.  The passage, however, seems to suggest that someone other than Goodwin is actually the author.</note>
         <note>Written in defense of the Apologeticall narration by Thomas Goodwin and the other dissenting brethren of the Westminster Assembly in answer to A. S.'s [i.e. Adam Steuart] attack on it.</note>
         <note>"W. R." is William Rathband.</note>
         <note>Contains some excerpts from Steuarts "Some observations and annotation upon the Apologetical narration."</note>
         <note>"Some observations and annotations vpon the Apologeticall narration" caption title on page A3.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of original in Thomason Collection, British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
