<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>Troposchēmalogia: Tropes and figures; or, A treatise of the metaphors, allegories, and express similitudes, &amp;c. contained in the Bible of the Old and New Testament To which is prefixed, divers arguments to prove the divine authority of the Holy Scriptures wherein also 'tis largely evinced, that by the great whore, mystery Babylon is meant the Papal hierarchy, or present state and church of Rome. Philologia sacra, the second part. Wherein the schemes, or figures in Scripture, are reduced under their proper heads, with a brief explication of each. Together with a treatise of types, parables, &amp;c. with an improvement of them parallel-wise. By B. K</title>
         <title>Tropologia. Book 4.</title>
         <author>Keach, Benjamin, 1640-1704.</author>
         <author>De Laune, Thomas, d. 1685. Tropologia. aut</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[12], xvi, 436, 48, 437-444 p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>Printed by John Darby, for the author,</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
         <date>M DC LXXXII. [1682]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A continuation of: De Laune, Thomas and Keach, Benjamin. Tropologia.</note>
         <note>"The epistle to the reader" signed: Benj. Keach.</note>
         <note>First word of title is in Greek characters.</note>
         <note>The words "Mystery Babylon" are enclosed in square brackets on title page.</note>
         <note>"Philologia sacra. The second part" has caption title and separate pagination; register begins anew with B1.</note>
         <note>Text is continuous despite pagination.</note>
         <note>Includes index.</note>
         <note>Incorrectly identified at reels 320:4 and 866:1b as Wing K101.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of originals in: the Union Theological Seminary Library, New York ("Early English books, 1641-1700" reel 866), New College (University of Edinburgh). Library (reel 320), and Dr. Williams's Library, London (reel 1951).</note>
         <note>Item at reel 866:1b with: Tropologia, a key to open scripture metaphors / by B.K. [Benjamin Keach]. London : Printed by J.R. and J.D. for Enoch Prosser ..., 1682.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
