<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The London-ministers legacy to their several congregations being a collection of farewel-sermons preached by 1 preached by Mr. Calamy, 2 Mr. Watson, 3 Mr. Sclater, 4 Mr. Watson, 5 Dr. Jacomb, 6 Mr. Case, 7 Dr. Jacomb, 8 Mr. Baxter, 9 Mr. Jenkins 10 Mr. Jenkins, 11 Mr. Lye, 11 [sic] Mr. Lye, 13 Dr. Manton. To which is annexed, a sermon preached at the funeral of Mr. Simeon Ash, late minister of the Gospel at St. Austins in London. By Edmund Calamy, B.D.</title>
         <author>Calamy, Edmund, 1600-1666. aut</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <editionStmt>
         <edition>The second edition; to which is added Mr. Jenkins forenoon sermon.</edition>
      </editionStmt>
      <extent>[6], 207, p. 206, [2], 221-266, [2], 37, [1], 1, 34-39, [1], 22, [2], 31, [1] p.   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>s.n.],</publisher>
         <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
         <date when="1662">Printed in the year 1662.</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>Sermon numbers and ministers' names are printed in two columns on title page; in each column the sermon number and name are joined by the words "Preached by" (printed vertically); everything is connected by a complex series of brackets.</note>
         <note>Place of publication from Wing.</note>
         <note>Each sermon has caption title; register is continuous.</note>
         <note>Text is continuous despite pagination.</note>
         <note>Vertical title reading "London ministers legacy." precedes Sermon XII.</note>
         <note>Register and pagination begin anew with Sermon XII.</note>
         <note>"The righteous man's death lamented" (also published separately as Wing (2nd ed.) C262A) has separate dated title page and pagination; register is continuous.</note>
         <note>Various collections of the "farewell sermons" of the dissenting ministers were published in 1662 and 1663 under several different titles. See Wing C242, C243, C5638, E3632, and S2257.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
