<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <biblFull>
      <titleStmt>
         <title>The answer to William Penn Quaker, his book, entituled, The new witnesses proved old hereticks Wherein he is proved to be an ignotant [sic] spater-brain'd Quaker, who knows no more what the true God is, nor his secret decrees, then one of his coach-horses doth, nor so much; for the oxe knoweth his owner, and the ass his masters scrip, but Penn doth not know his maker, as is manifest by the Scriptures, which may inform the reader, if he mind the interpretation of Scripture in the discourse following. I. That God was in the forme, image and likeness of mans bodily shape, as well as his soul from eternity. ... VIII. What is meant by the armour of God, the wilderness, and the wilde beasts I fought with in the wilderness. / By Lodowick Muggleton.</title>
         <author>Muggleton, Lodowick, 1609-1698.</author>
      </titleStmt>
      <extent>[4], 40, 90, 22 p., [1] leaf of plate   </extent>
      <publicationStmt>
         <publisher>[s.n.],</publisher>
         <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
         <date>priuted [sic] in the year 1673 [i.e. 1698?]</date>
      </publicationStmt>
      <notesStmt>
         <note>A reply to: Penn, William.  The new witnesses proved old hereticks.</note>
         <note>With an engraved frontispiece portrait of Lodowick Muggleton, with caption: Lodowick Muggleton dyed the 14th of March 1697/8 then aged 88 years 7 months: &amp; 14 dayes.</note>
         <note>This edition contains the title page and apparently at least part of the sheets of the first edition, with an additional 40 pages inserted preceding chapter 1 of the first edition.</note>
         <note>Signatures: A²  B-F⁴ ² B-Z²  a¹ ³B²  ⁴B-E²  F¹.</note>
         <note>Reproduction of the original in the Cambridge University Library.</note>
      </notesStmt>
   </biblFull>
</sourceDesc>
