<?xml-model href="../schema/sourceDesc_fragment.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<sourceDesc xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <biblFull>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The Popish damnable plot against our religion and liberties fairly laid open and discover'd in the breviats of threescore and four letters and papers of intelligence past betwixt the Pope, Duke of York, Cardinal Norfolk, Cardinal Cibo, Cardinal Barbarina, nuntio and internuncio for the Pope in Italy, France and Flanders, and the Lord Arundel, Mr. Coleman, Mr. Cooke, Mr. Conne. And also the said Mr. Coleman, Albany, Sr. German, Lybourn, Sheldon, Throgmorton, and several others. As they were drawn up by the Secret Committee of the House of Commons, for the satisfaction of the House of Lords, in the bill against the Duke of York, and expected tryals of the Lords. / Now published for the vindication of the House of Commons upon the said bill, and for satisfaction of all the faithful subjects of His Majesties kingdoms, with several animadversions and remarks made upon the said letters.</title>
      <author>Tonge, Ezerel, 1621-1680, attributed name.</author>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament. House of Commons.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <extent>[2], 31, [1] p.   </extent>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">R. Janeway</persName> in <placeName>Queens-Head Alley in Pater-Noster-Row.</placeName>,</publisher>
      <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
      <date>MDCLXXX. [1680]</date>
    </publicationStmt>
    <notesStmt>
      <note>Sometimes attributed to Ezerel Tonge.</note>
      <note>"Animadversions on the foregoing breviats"--p. 13-31.</note>
      <note>Reproduction of original in the British Library.</note>
    </notesStmt>
  </biblFull>
  <listPerson>
    <person type="publisher">
      <persName>R. Janeway</persName>
    </person>
  </listPerson>
  <listPlace>
    <place type="location">
      <placeName>Queens-Head Alley in Pater-Noster-Row.</placeName>
    </place>
  </listPlace>
</sourceDesc>
