<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A paradox Prooving that the inhabitants of the isle called Madagascar, or St. Laurence, (in temporall things) are the happiest people in the world. Whereunto is prefixed, a briefe and true description of that island: the nature of the climate, and condition of the inhabitants, and their speciall affection to the English above other nations. With most probable arguments of a hopefull and fit plantation of a colony there, in respect of the fruitfulnesse of the soyle, the benignity of the ayre, and the relieving of our English ships, both to and from the East-Indies. By Wa: Hamond.</title>
      <author>Hamond, Walter, fl. 1643.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A02605</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">S103773</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>A paradox Prooving  that the inhabitants of the isle called Madagascar, or St. Laurence, (in temporall things) are the happiest people in the world. Whereunto is prefixed, a briefe and true description of that island: the nature of the climate, and condition of the inhabitants, and their speciall affection to the English above other nations. With most probable arguments of a hopefull and fit plantation of a colony there, in respect of the fruitfulnesse of the soyle, the benignity of the ayre, and the relieving of our English ships, both to and from the East-Indies. By Wa: Hamond.</title>
          <author gender="M">Hamond, Walter, fl. 1643.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[38] p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed [by <persName type="printer">J. Raworth</persName>, <persName type="printer">B. Alsop</persName>, <persName type="printer">T. Fawcet</persName>, and <persName type="printer">M. Parsons]</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Nathaniell Butter</persName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1640">1640.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>"Raworth pr[inted]. A-B, Alsop &amp; Fawcet D-E, Parsons F"--STC.</note>
          <note>"A paradoxe. Prouing that the inhabitants of the island called Madagascar, or St. Lawrence, (in temporall things) are the happiest people in the world" has separate divisional title on D1r.</note>
          <note>Signatures: A-B⁴ D-F⁴ (-A1).</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>Nathaniell Butter</persName>
        </person>
        <person type="printer">
          <persName>B. Alsop</persName>
        </person>
        <person type="printer">
          <persName><choice><orig>J. Raworth</orig><reg>Raworth, John</reg></choice></persName>
        </person>
        <person type="printer">
          <persName>M. Parsons]</persName>
        </person>
        <person type="printer">
          <persName>T. Fawcet</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>Hamond, Walter,</persName>
          <floruit>active 1643.</floruit>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="651x">Description and travel</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="651a">Madagascar</item>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>