<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A declaration of egregious popish impostures to with-draw the harts of her Maiesties subiects from their allegeance, and from the truth of Christian religion professed in England, vnder the pretence of casting out deuils. Practised by Edmunds, alias Weston a Iesuit, and diuers Romish priestes his wicked associates. Where-vnto are annexed the copies of the confessions, and examinations of the parties themselues, which were pretended to be possessed, and dispossessed, taken vpon oath before her Maiesties commissioners, for causes ecclesiasticall.</title>
      <author>Harsnett, Samuel, 1561-1631.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A02750</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">S120922</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>A declaration of egregious popish impostures to with-draw the harts of her Maiesties subiects from their allegeance, and from the truth of Christian religion professed in England, vnder the pretence of casting out  deuils. Practised by Edmunds, alias Weston a Iesuit, and diuers Romish priestes his wicked associates. Where-vnto are annexed the copies of the confessions, and examinations of the parties themselues, which were pretended to be possessed, and dispossessed, taken vpon oath before her Maiesties commissioners, for causes ecclesiasticall.</title>
          <author gender="M">Harsnett, Samuel, 1561-1631.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[8], 284 p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Iames Roberts</persName>, dwelling in <placeName>Barbican</placeName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>At London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1603">1603.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Preface signed: S.H., i.e. Samuel Harsnett.</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="printer">
          <persName>Iames Roberts</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>Harsnett, Samuel,</persName>
          <birth>1561</birth>
          <death>1631.</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
        <person role="subject">
          <persName>Weston, William,</persName>
          <birth>1550</birth>
          <death>1615.</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listOrg type="estc_ep">
        <org>
          <orgName>
            <name>Catholic Church</name>
          </orgName>
        </org>
      </listOrg>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Exorcism</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="form">
        <list>
          <item n="610v">Controversial literature</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>