<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Captaine Humes poeticall musicke Principally made for two basse-viols, yet so contriued, that it may be plaied 8. seuerall waies vpon sundry instruments with much facilitie. 1 The first way or musicke is for one bass-viole to play alone in pares, which standeth alwaies on the right side of this booke. 2 The second musicke is for two basse-viols to play toghether. 3 The third musicke, for three basse-viols to play together. 4 The fourth musicke, for two tenor viols and a basse-viole. 5 The fift musicke, for two lutes and a basse-viole. 6 The sixt musicke, for two orpherions and a basse-viole. 7 The seuenth musicke, to vse the voyce to some of these musicks, but especially to the three basse-viols, or to the two orpherions with one basse-viole to play the ground. 8 The eight and last musicke, in conforting all these instruments together with the virginals, or rather with a winde instrument and the voice Composed by Tobias Hume gentleman.</title>
      <author>Hume, Tobias, d. 1645.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A03842</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">S119142</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>Captaine Humes poeticall musicke Principally made for two basse-viols, yet so contriued, that it may be plaied 8. seuerall waies vpon sundry instruments with much facilitie. 1 The first way or musicke is for one bass-viole to play alone in pares, which standeth alwaies on the right side of this booke. 2 The second musicke is for two basse-viols to play toghether. 3 The third musicke, for three basse-viols to play together. 4 The fourth musicke, for two tenor viols and a basse-viole. 5 The fift musicke, for two lutes and a basse-viole. 6 The sixt musicke, for two orpherions and a basse-viole. 7 The seuenth musicke, to vse the voyce to some of these musicks, but especially to the three basse-viols, or to the two orpherions with one basse-viole to play the ground. 8 The eight and last musicke, in conforting all these instruments together with the virginals, or rather with a winde instrument and the voice  Composed by Tobias Hume gentleman.</title>
          <author gender="M">Hume, Tobias, d. 1645.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[28] p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Iohn VVindet</persName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1607">1607.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>G2 recto varies: it is blank or has dedication: to Sir C. Hatton or to Philip [i.e. Thomas? Howard] Earl of Arundel--STC.</note>
          <note>Signatures: G-N² .</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the Folger Shakespeare Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="printer">
          <persName>Iohn VVindet</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>Hume, Tobias,</persName>
          <death>-1645.</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Instrumental music</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>