<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>hEre begynneth the volume intituled and named the recuyell of the historyes of Troye,
          composed and drawen out of dyuerce bookes of latyn in to frensshe by the ryght venerable
          persone and worshipfull man. Raoul le ffeure. preest and chapelayn vnto the ryght noble
          gloryous and myghty prynce in his tyme Phelip duc of Bourgoyne of Braband [et]c in the
          yere of the incarnacion of our lord god a thousand foure honderd sixty and foure, and
          translated and drawen out of frenshe in to englisshe by Willyam Caxton mercer of ye cyte
          of London, at the comau[n]deme[n]t of the right hye myghty and vertuouse pryncesse hys
          redoubtyd lady. Margarete by the grace of god. Duchesse of Bourgoyne of Lotryk of Braband
          [et]c., whiche sayd translacion and werke was ... fynysshid in the holy cyte of Colen the.
          xix. day of septembre the yere of our sayd lord god a thousand foure honderd sixty and
          enleuen [sic] [et]c ...</title>
      <title>Recueil des histoires de Troie. English</title>
      <author>Lefèvre, Raoul, fl. 1460.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A05232</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">S109298</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>hEre begynneth the volume intituled and named the recuyell of the historyes of Troye, composed and drawen out of dyuerce bookes of latyn in to frensshe by the ryght venerable persone and worshipfull man. Raoul le ffeure. preest and chapelayn vnto the ryght noble gloryous and myghty prynce in his tyme Phelip duc of Bourgoyne of Braband [et]c in the yere of the incarnacion of our lord god a thousand foure honderd sixty and foure, and translated and drawen out of frenshe in to englisshe by Willyam Caxton mercer of ye cyte of London, at the comau[n]deme[n]t of the right hye myghty and vertuouse pryncesse hys redoubtyd lady. Margarete by the grace of god. Duchesse of Bourgoyne of Lotryk of Braband [et]c., whiche sayd translacion and werke was ... fynysshid in the holy cyte of Colen the. xix. day of septembre the yere of our sayd lord god a thousand foure honderd sixty and enleuen [sic] [et]c  ...</title>
          <title>Recueil des histoires de Troie. English</title>
          <author gender="M">Lefèvre, Raoul, fl. 1460.</author>
          <author gender="M">Caxton, William, ca. 1422-1491.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[704] p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">William Caxton and, probably</persName>, <persName type="printer">Colard Mansion</persName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>[Bruges :</pubPlace>
          <date notBefore="1473" notAfter="1474">1473 or 1474]</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>A translation of: Recueil des histoires de Troye.</note>
          <note>Title from ¹[A]2r, which is printed in red.</note>
          <note>Imprint from STC and Needham; see also Lotte Hellinga, "Caxton in focus", p. 38-9, 48.</note>
          <note>Signatures: [A-O¹⁰ P; A-I¹⁰ K L⁶; A-K¹⁰].</note>
          <note>In three books.</note>
          <note>The first leaf is blank.</note>
          <note>[A]3r text begins: and zeland and thus whan alle thyse thynges cam ..</note>
          <note>The last leaf contains 14 lines of Latin verse beginning: Pergama flere volo. fata danais data solo ..</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person n="printer">
          <persName>Colard Mansion</persName>
        </person>
        <person n="printer">
          <persName>William Caxton and, probably</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>Lefèvre, Raoul,</persName>
          <floruit>active 1460.</floruit>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
        <person role="added" n="translator, printer.">
          <persName>Caxton, William,</persName>
          <floruit>approximately 1422-1491 or 1492,</floruit>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
        <person role="added" n="printer.">
          <persName>Mansion, Colard,</persName>
          <floruit>active 15th century,</floruit>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="651x">Romances</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="651a">Troy (Extinct city)</item>
          <item n="752a">Belgium</item>
          <item n="752d">Bruges.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>