<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Newes from Bohemia. An apologie made by the states of the Kingdome of Bohemia, shewing the reasons why those of the reformed religion were moued to take armes, for the defence of the king and themselues, especially against the dangerous sect of Iesuites. With a plaine declaration, that those who belong unto the monasteries and ecclesiasticall iurisdiction (according unto his Maiesties letters, and agreements made betweene that states of the reformed religion and the Papists) haue good right, as being subjects of the Imperiall Maiestie, to the peaceable exercise of their diuine seruice, and building of churches. / Translated out of Dutch into Latine, and thence into English by Will. Philip..</title>
      <title>Stavové evangelicti. English</title>
      <author>Bohemia (Kingdom).</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A16300</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">S116504</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>Newes from Bohemia. An apologie made by the states of the Kingdome of Bohemia, shewing the reasons why those of the reformed religion were moued to take armes, for the defence of the king and themselues, especially against the dangerous sect of Iesuites.  With a plaine declaration, that those who belong unto the monasteries and ecclesiasticall iurisdiction (according unto his Maiesties letters, and agreements made betweene that states of the reformed religion and the Papists) haue good right, as being subjects of the Imperiall Maiestie, to the peaceable exercise of their diuine seruice, and building of churches. / Translated out of Dutch into Latine, and thence into English by Will. Philip..</title>
          <title>Stavové evangelicti. English</title>
          <author>Bohemia (Kingdom).</author>
          <author gender="M">Phillip, William.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[33] p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">George Purslow</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Ralph Rounthwaite</persName>, and are to bee sold at <placeName>his Shop, at the Signe of the Flower de luce</placeName> and Crowne, in <placeName>Pauls Chruch-yard.</placeName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1619">1619..</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>initials, headpiece.</note>
          <note>Signatures: A-D⁴.</note>
          <note>Copy at reel 1540:2 imperfect: some print show-through; some leaves cropped at head, affecting running title.</note>
          <note>Reproduction of originals in: British Library (1540:2); Folger Shakespeare Library (2291:6a).</note>
          <note>Copy at reel 2291:6a bound and filmed with STC 3211.5: Newes from Bohemia.  A true relation of the now present warres in Bohemia, their manner of proceeding in the same, fortifying and besieging of certaine townes, with such supplies and aide as they haue already receiued, and further expect from other countries.  With the troubles and disagreements, betweene them, the Emperor, and King Ferdinando.  And a description of the death both of the Emperor and Empresse.  Translated out of the Dutch copie printed at Newinberg, the 4. of May 1619.  London, : Printed by Edward Griffin for Ralph Rounthwaite at the signe of the Golden Lyon in Paules Church-yard., 1619.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>Ralph Rounthwaite</persName>
        </person>
        <person type="printer">
          <persName>George Purslow</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="added" type="tr.">
          <persName>Phillip, William, <roleName>l. 1600,</roleName></persName>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listOrg type="estc_ep">
        <org>
          <orgName>
            <name>Jesuits</name>
          </orgName>
        </org>
      </listOrg>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Counter-Reformation</item>
          <item n="650a">Thirty Years' War, 1618-1648</item>
          <item n="650x">Sources</item>
          <item n="651x">History</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="temporal">
        <list>
          <item n="651y">1618-1848</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="651a">Bohemia (Czech Republic)</item>
          <item n="650z">Bohemia</item>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>