<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Baron and feme a treatise of the common law concerning husbands and wives.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A31029</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R6177</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>Baron and feme a treatise of the common law concerning husbands and wives.</title>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[30], 380, [35] p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed by the assigns of <persName type="assigns">Richard</persName> and <persName type="assigns">Edward Atkyns</persName> ..., for <persName type="publisher">John Walthoe</persName> ...,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1700">1700.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>"Precedents": p. 353-380.</note>
          <note>"Books printed for and sold by John Walthoe at his shop in Vinecourt, Middle-Temple": [2] p. following contents.</note>
          <note>"Wherein is contained The Nature of a Feme Covert, and of Marriages, Bastardy, the Privileges of Feme Coverts: What Alterations are made by Marriage as to Estates, Leases, Goods and Actions.  What Things of the Wife accrue to the Husband by the Intermarriage, or not.  What Acts, Charges, Forfeitures by the Husband shall bind the Wife after his Death or not.  Of Jointures and Pleadings, Fines, and Recovery, Conveyances, and other Law Titles relating to Baron and Feme.  Of Wills and Feme Covert being Executrix.  Of the Wief's [sic] Separate Disposition and Maintenance.  What amounts to the Disposition of the Wife's Term by the Husband.  Of Actions brought by or against Baron and Feme.  What Actions done, or Contracts made by the Wife, shall bind her Husband.  Of Indictments and Informations against them.  Of Baron and Feme's Joinder in Action.  Of a Feme Sole Merchant.  Declarations and Pleas, etc. of Divorces, etc. with many other Matters relating to the said Subject and some useful Precedents."</note>
          <note>Reproduction of original in Bodleian Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>John Walthoe</persName>
        </person>
        <person type="assigns">
          <persName>Edward Atkyns</persName>
        </person>
        <person type="assigns">
          <persName>Richard</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Husband and wife</item>
          <item n="650a">Marriage law</item>
          <item n="650a">Forms (Law)</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="650z 752b">England</item>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>