<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A Fourth collection of papers relating to the present juncture of affairs in England</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A40066</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R12180</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>A Fourth collection of papers relating to the present juncture of affairs in England</title>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[2], 34 p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Rich. Janeway</persName> ...,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1688">1688.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Fourth in a series of twelve collections issued in 1688-1689 under the general title: A collection of papers relating to the present juncture of affairs in England; and reissued in 1689 under title: A compleat collection of papers, in twelve parts, relating to the great revolutions in England and Scotland.</note>
          <note>Reproduction of original in the Huntington Library.</note>
          <note>(from t.p.) I. The Prince of Orange's first declaration from the Hague, Octob. 10, 1688 ... -- II. The Bishop of Rochester's letter to the Ecclesiastical Commissioners -- III.  The Prince of Orange's speech to the gentlemen of Somersetshire and Dorsetshire, coming to joyn His Highness at Exeter, Nov. 15, 1688 -- IV. A true copy of a paper delivered by the Earl of Devonshire to the Mayor of Darby ... -- V. An address of the Mayor &amp;c. of Lyn-Regis in Norfolk to the Duke of Norfolk ... -- VI. A declaration of the Lords Spriritual and Temporal in and about the city ... -- VII. A paper delivered to the Prince of Orange by the commissioners sent by His Majesty -- VIII. The King's letter to the Earl of Feversham on His Majesties leaving Whitehall ... -- IX. A declaration of the Prince of Orange to the commanders in chief of the dispersed regiments, troops and companies to keep them together in order -- X. An address of the Lieutenancy of London to the Pr. of Orange -- XI. An address of the Lord Mayor, aldermen and Common Council of London to the Prince of Orange -- XII. A speech of Sir G. Treby on delivery of the city address.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="bookseller">
          <persName>Rich. Janeway</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="651x">History</item>
          <item n="651x">Sources</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="temporal">
        <list>
          <item n="651y">William and Mary, 1689-1702</item>
          <item n="651y">Revolution of 1688</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="651a 752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>