<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Historical collections, or, A brief account of the most remarkable transactions of the two last Parliaments consisting of I. The speeches, votes, accusations, addresses, and article of impeachment, &amp;c., II. The bills of association, exclusion, and repeal of 35 Eliz. &amp;c., III. The several informations, messages, narratives, orders, petitions, protestation of the Lords, and resolves of both Houses, etc., IV. The tryal and sentence of William Howard Lord Viscount of Stafford in Westminster Hall, his speech and execution on the scaffold at Tower Hill with many other memorable passages and proceedings of the two last Parliaments, held and dissolved at Westminster and Oxford, V. A perfect list of each Paraliament, VI. His Majesty's declaration, shewing the causes and reasons that moved him to dissolve the two last Parliaments.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A43880</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R32032</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>Historical collections, or, A brief account of the most remarkable transactions of the two last Parliaments consisting of I. The speeches, votes, accusations, addresses, and article of impeachment, &amp;c., II. The bills of association, exclusion, and repeal of 35 Eliz. &amp;c., III. The several informations, messages, narratives, orders, petitions, protestation of the Lords, and resolves of both Houses, etc., IV. The tryal and sentence of William Howard Lord Viscount of Stafford in Westminster Hall, his speech and execution on the scaffold at Tower Hill with many other memorable passages and proceedings of the two last Parliaments, held and dissolved at Westminster and Oxford, V. A perfect list of each Paraliament,  VI. His Majesty's declaration, shewing the causes and reasons that moved him to dissolve the two last Parliaments.</title>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[7], 228, [2], 229-302 p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Simon Neal</persName> ...,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1682">1682.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>"Historical collections, or, The continuation of the proceedings of the Parliament, begun and dissolved at Oxford" has special t.p.</note>
          <note>Includes index.</note>
          <note>Numerous errors in paging.</note>
          <note>Reproduction of original in the Harvard Law School Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>Simon Neal</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="subject">
          <persName>Stafford, William Howard, <roleName>Viscount,</roleName></persName>
          <birth>1614</birth>
          <death>1680</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listOrg type="estc_ep">
        <org>
          <orgName>
            <name>England and Wales.</name>
            <name>Parliament</name>
          </orgName>
        </org>
      </listOrg>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="651x">History</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="temporal">
        <list>
          <item n="651y">Charles II, 1660-1685</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="651a 752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>