<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A Ninth collection of papers relating to the present juncture of affairs in England ...</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A52353</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R24409</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>A Ninth collection of papers relating to the present juncture of affairs in England ...</title>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[2], 34 p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed and are to be sold by <persName type="printer"><persName type="bookseller">Richard Janeway</persName></persName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1689">1689.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Ninth in a series of 12 collections issued in 1688-1689 under title: A collection of papers relating to the present juncture of affairs in England; and reissued in 1689 under title: A compleat collection of papers, in twelve parts, relating to the great revolutions in England and Scotland.</note>
          <note>Advertisement: p. 34.</note>
          <note>This item can be found at reels 1235:19 and 1447:9.</note>
          <note>Reproduction of original in the Huntington Library.</note>
          <note>(from t.p.) I. A dialogue beween two friends, wherein the Church of England is vindicated in joyning with the Prince of Orange in his descent into England -- II. His late Majesty's letter to the Lords and others of his Privy Council -- III. Some remarks on the late king's pretended letter to the Lords and others of his Privy Council -- IV. Reasons for crowning the Prince and Princess of Orange King and Queen jointly and for placing the executive power in the prince alone -- V. A lord's speech without doors to the Lords upon the present condition of the government -- VI. Reflections on a paper, called, A lord's speech without doors -- VII. The bishops reasons to Queen Elizabeth for taking off the Queen of Scots, offer'd to the consideration of the present sect of Grumbletonians.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="printer">
          <persName><choice><orig>Richard Janeway</orig><reg>Janeway, Richard, active 1680-1703</reg></choice></persName>
        </person>
        <person type="bookseller">
          <persName><choice><orig>Richard Janeway</orig><reg>Janeway, Richard, active 1680-1703</reg></choice></persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="651x">History</item>
          <item n="651x">Politics and government</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="temporal">
        <list>
          <item n="651y">Revolution of 1688.</item>
          <item n="651y">1660-1714.</item>
          <item n="651y">William and Mary, 1689-1702.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="651a 752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>