<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A short demurrer to the Jewes long discontinued barred remitter into England Comprising an exact chronological relation of their first admission into, their ill deportment, misdemeanors, condition, sufferings, oppressions, slaughters, plunders, by popular insurrections, and regal exactions in; and their total, final banishment by judgment and edict of Parliament, out of England, never to return again: collected out of the best historians and records. With a brief collection of such English laws, Scriptures, reasons as seem strongly to plead, and conclude against their readmission into England, especially at this season, and against the general calling of the Jewish nation. With an answer to the chief allegations for their introduction. / By William Prynne Esq; a bencher of Lincolnes-Inne.</title>
      <title>Short demurrer to the Jewes long discontinued remitter into England. Part 1.</title>
      <author>Prynne, William, 1600-1669.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A56206</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R205682</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>A short demurrer to the Jewes long discontinued barred remitter into England Comprising an exact chronological relation of their first admission into, their ill deportment, misdemeanors, condition, sufferings, oppressions, slaughters, plunders, by popular insurrections, and regal exactions in; and their total, final banishment by judgment and edict of Parliament, out of England, never to return again: collected out of the best historians and records.  With a brief collection of such English laws, Scriptures, reasons as seem strongly to plead, and conclude against their readmission into England, especially at this season, and against the general calling of the Jewish nation. With an answer to the chief allegations for their introduction. / By William Prynne Esq; a bencher of Lincolnes-Inne.</title>
          <title>Short demurrer to the Jewes long discontinued remitter into England. Part 1.</title>
          <author gender="M">Prynne, William, 1600-1669.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <editionStmt>
          <edition>The second edition, enlarged.</edition>
        </editionStmt>
        <extent>[12], 182 [i.e. 128] p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>for <persName type="publisher">Edward Thomas</persName> dwelling in <placeName>Green-Arbor</placeName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>Printed at London, :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1656">1656.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>A second part was published in the same year.</note>
          <note>Reproduction of original in British Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>Edward Thomas</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>Prynne, William,</persName>
          <birth>1600</birth>
          <death>1669.</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Jews</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="form">
        <list>
          <item n="650v">Controversial literature</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="650z 752b">England</item>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>