<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Jerubbaal justified: or, A plain rebuke of the high (pretended humble) remonstrance and plea against Mr. Crofton his reformation not separation or, a plea for communion with the church under those corruptions, and by that disorderly ministration, to which he cannot conform, nor by it administer. Demonstrating, T.P. (alias D.) his grosse mistakes of Mr. Crofton his principle and argument: as also the fallacie and vanity of his pleaded necessity for his (confessed) separation from publique assemblies, which is found insufficient to acquit him of schisme. To which is added a position, disputing the lawfulnesse of ministers receiving an imposed liturgy.</title>
      <author>R. S.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A58653</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R33967</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>Jerubbaal justified: or, A plain rebuke of the high (pretended humble) remonstrance and plea against Mr. Crofton his reformation not separation or, a plea for communion with the church under those corruptions, and by that disorderly ministration, to which he cannot conform, nor by it administer.  Demonstrating, T.P. (alias D.) his grosse mistakes of Mr. Crofton his principle and argument: as also the fallacie and vanity of his pleaded necessity for his (confessed) separation from publique assemblies, which is found insufficient to acquit him of schisme.  To which is added a position, disputing the lawfulnesse of ministers receiving an imposed liturgy.</title>
          <author>R. S.</author>
          <author>Crofton, Zachary, 1625 or 6-1672. Reformation not separation.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[10], 43, [1] p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>[s.n.],</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1663">printed in the year, 1663.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>A reply to Crofton's Reformation not separation.</note>
          <note>This is a replacement for incomplete S130 on reel 1046.  Cf.  Wing (2nd ed.).</note>
          <note>Reproductions of originals in: Union Theological Seminary (New York, N.Y.). Library (reel 1046:5) and Folger Shakespeare Library (reel 2925:1).</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>R. S.</persName>
          <sex value=""/>
    </person>
        <person role="subject">
          <persName>Crofton, Zachary,</persName>
          <floruit>1625 or 1626-1672.</floruit>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listOrg type="estc_ep">
        <org>
          <orgName>
            <name>Church of England</name>
          </orgName>
        </org>
      </listOrg>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Dissenters, Religious</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="form">
        <list>
          <item n="610v">Apologetic works</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="650z 752b">England</item>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>