<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Sad and deplorable news from Oxford-sheir &amp; Bark-sheir Being a lamentable and true relation of the drowning of about sixty persons, men, women and children, in the lock, near Goring in Oxford sheir; as they were passing by water, from Goring Feast, to Stately in Barksheir. Readers, this story is both strange and true, and for your good (presented unto you:) be careful of your life, all sins to fly, lest you by death be taken suddenly. When he is sent, on you arrest to make, no fees nor bail, can purchase your escape.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A58994</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R219824</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>Sad and deplorable news from Oxford-sheir &amp; Bark-sheir Being a lamentable and true relation of the drowning of about sixty persons, men, women and children, in the lock, near Goring in Oxford sheir; as they were passing by water, from Goring Feast, to Stately in Barksheir.  Readers, this story is both strange and true, and for your good (presented unto you:) be careful of your life, all sins to fly, lest you by death be taken suddenly. When he is sent, on you arrest to make, no fees nor bail, can purchase your escape.</title>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[2], 6 p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>printed for <persName type="publisher">R. Vaughan</persName>, in <placeName>the Little-old-Baily</placeName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1674">1674.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Caption title on p. 1 reads: Sad news from Oxford shier, and Berke-shier, &amp;c.</note>
          <note>Some print show-through.</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>R. Vaughan</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Drowning</item>
          <item n="650a">Drowning victims</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="650z 752b">England</item>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>