<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Two treatises The first, of the venereal pocks: Wherein is shewed, I. The name and original of this disease. II. Histories thereof. III. The nature thereof. IV. Its causes. V. Its differences. VI. Several sorts of signs thereof. VII. Several waies of the cure thereof. VIII. How to cure such diseases, as are wont to accompany the whores pocks. The second treatise of the gout, 1. Of the nature of the gout. 2. Of the causes thereof. 3. Of the signs thereof. 4. Of the cure thereof. 5. Of the hip gout or sciatica. 6. The way to prevent the gout written in Latin and English. By Daniel Sennert, Doctor of Physick. Nicholas Culpeper, physitian and astrologer. Abdiah Cole, Doctor of Physick, and the liberal arts.</title>
      <title>De lue venerea. English</title>
      <author>Sennert, Daniel, 1572-1637.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A59205</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R221594</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>Two treatises The first, of the venereal pocks:  Wherein is shewed, I. The name and original of this disease. II. Histories thereof. III. The nature thereof. IV. Its causes. V. Its differences. VI. Several sorts of signs thereof. VII. Several waies of the cure thereof. VIII. How to cure such diseases, as are wont to accompany the whores pocks. The second treatise of the gout, 1. Of the nature of the gout. 2. Of the causes thereof. 3. Of the signs thereof. 4. Of the cure thereof. 5. Of the hip gout or sciatica. 6. The way to prevent the gout written in Latin and English. By Daniel Sennert, Doctor of Physick. Nicholas Culpeper, physitian and astrologer. Abdiah Cole, Doctor of Physick, and the liberal arts.</title>
          <title>De lue venerea. English</title>
          <author gender="M">Sennert, Daniel, 1572-1637.</author>
          <author gender="M">Culpeper, Nicholas, 1616-1654.</author>
          <author gender="M">Sennert, Daniel, 1572-1637.</author>
          <author gender="M">Cole, Abdiah, ca. 1610-ca. 1670.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[4], 75, [1], 87, [1] p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">Peter Cole, printer and</persName> book-seller, at <placeName>the sign of the Printing-press in Cornhil, neer the Royal Exchange</placeName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1660">1660.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>A translation of "De lue venerea" and "De arthritide tractatus".</note>
          <note>"A treatise of the gout" begins new pagination, and new register beginning with C1.</note>
          <note>With a final advertisement page.</note>
          <note>Some print faded.</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the Royal College of Surgeons of England Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="printer">
          <persName>Peter Cole, printer and</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>Sennert, Daniel,</persName>
          <birth>1572</birth>
          <death>1637.</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
        <person role="added">
          <persName>Cole, Abdiah,</persName>
          <floruit>approximately 1610-approximately 1670.</floruit>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
        <person role="added">
          <persName>Culpeper, Nicholas,</persName>
          <birth>1616</birth>
          <death>1654.</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
        <person role="added">
          <persName>Sennert, Daniel,</persName>
          <birth>1572</birth>
          <death>1637.</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Gout</item>
          <item n="650a">Sexually transmitted diseases</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>