<?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The dead-man's testament: or, A letter written, to all the saints of God in Scotland fellow-heirs of the blessing with those in England: for a view of the present work of God against the mystery of iniquity and for unity and love amonst themselves, in this day of the Lord's mercifull dispensation, and of the judgement of the whore. By Thomas Wood, sometimes inhabitant of Leith, lately departed this present life. And supplied by one of his own countrey-men, a lover of the true spirituall Beautie of Zion. Published by authoritie.</title>
      <author>Wood, Thomas, of Leith.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A66947</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R221198</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>The dead-man's testament: or, A letter written, to all the saints of God in Scotland fellow-heirs of the blessing with those in England: for a view of the present work of God against the mystery of iniquity and for unity and love amonst themselves, in this day of the Lord's mercifull dispensation, and of the judgement of the whore. By Thomas Wood, sometimes inhabitant of Leith, lately departed this present life. And supplied by one of his own countrey-men, a lover of the true spirituall Beautie of Zion.  Published by authoritie.</title>
          <author gender="M">Wood, Thomas, of Leith.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>16 p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>by <persName type="printer">Evan Tyler</persName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>Printed at Leith :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1651">1651</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>With imprimatur dated: Novemb. 25. 1651.</note>
          <note>Copy imperfect; title page stained with print show-through.</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="printer">
          <persName>Evan Tyler</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>Wood, Thomas, <roleName>of Leith.</roleName></persName>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listOrg type="estc_ep">
        <org>
          <orgName>
            <name>Church of Scotland</name>
          </orgName>
        </org>
        <org>
          <orgName>
            <name>Church of Scotland</name>
          </orgName>
        </org>
      </listOrg>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Presbyterianism</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">Scotland</item>
          <item n="752d">Edinburgh</item>
        <item n="752f">Leith.</item></list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>