<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The interpretacyon, and sygnyfycacyon of the Masse Here begynneth a good deuoute boke to the honoure of god, of our lady his mother, [and] of all sayntes, and ryght profytable to all good Catholyke persones, to knowe howe they shall deuoutly here masse. And how salutaryly they shal confesse them. And how reuerently and honourably they shall go to the holy sacrament or table of our sauyour Ihesu chryste, with dyuerse other profytable documents and oraysons or prayers here conteyned, composed and ordeyned by frere Gararde, frere mynoure, of the ordre of the Obseruauntes.</title>
      <author>Gherit, van der Goude, fl. 1507.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A68080</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">S110806</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>The interpretacyon, and sygnyfycacyon of the Masse Here begynneth a good deuoute boke to the honoure of god, of our lady his mother, [and] of all sayntes, and ryght profytable to all good Catholyke persones, to knowe howe they shall deuoutly here masse. And how salutaryly they shal confesse them.  And how reuerently and honourably they shall go to the holy sacrament or table of our sauyour Ihesu chryste, with dyuerse other profytable documents and oraysons or prayers here conteyned, composed and ordeyned by frere Gararde, frere mynoure, of the ordre of the Obseruauntes.</title>
          <author>Gherit, van der Goude, fl. 1507.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[240] p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Imprynted by <persName type="printer">me Robert Wyer</persName>, dwellynge at <placeName>the sygne of saynt Iohn Eua[n]gelyste, in saynt Martyns parysshe in the felde, in the bysshop of Norwytche rentes, besyde Charynge crosse</placeName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1532">In the yere of our Lorde God a. M. CCCCC. xxxii. The .xiiii. daye of the moneth of Octobre] [1532]</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>A translation of Gherit van der Goude: Boexken van der missen.</note>
          <note>Formerly also STC 11809.</note>
          <note>Identified as STC 11809 at reel 1660:11.</note>
          <note>Imprint from colophon.</note>
          <note>Signatures: pi⁴ a-z⁴ [et]⁴ A-E⁴ .</note>
          <note>Reproductions of the original in the British Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="printer">
          <persName>me Robert Wyer</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>Gherit, <roleName>van der Goude,</roleName></persName>
          <floruit>active 1507.</floruit>
          <sex value=""/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Lord's Supper</item>
          <item n="650a">Mass</item>
          <item n="650x">Catholic Church</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>