<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The Art of courtship; or, The School of delight. Containing amorous dialogues, complemental expressions, poems, letters and discourses upon sundry occasions, relating to love and business: Pleasant new songs, and directions for courtship and behaviour: And rules for carving flesh, fish, fowl; and cutting up pastry: Also to distinguish the best pieces, and decently to serve a table after the most modish and courtly manner. : With other delightful and profitable things, necessary for the accomplishment of all persons. : To which is added, the significance of moles, in any part of the body, in relation to good and bad fortunes. : As likewise, the interpretation of dreams, as they presage happiness or unhappiness to men and women, in all stations and conditions. : Very profitable and advantageous to all persons.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A75623</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R175477</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>The Art of courtship; or, The School of delight. Containing amorous dialogues, complemental expressions, poems, letters and discourses upon sundry occasions, relating to love and business: Pleasant new songs, and directions for courtship and behaviour:   And rules for carving flesh, fish, fowl; and cutting up pastry: Also to distinguish the best pieces, and decently to serve a table after the most modish and courtly manner. : With other delightful and profitable things, necessary for the accomplishment of all persons. : To which is added, the significance of moles, in any part of the body, in relation to good and bad fortunes. : As likewise, the interpretation of dreams, as they presage happiness or unhappiness to men and women, in all stations and conditions. : Very profitable and advantageous to all persons.</title>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[24] p. : ill.  </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">J.M.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">J. Back</persName>, at <placeName>the Black Boy on London-Bridge</placeName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1688">1688.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Includes illustrated added t.p.</note>
          <note>Reproduction of original in the Bodleian Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>J. Back</persName>
        </person>
        <person type="printer">
          <persName>J.M.</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Courtship.</item>
          <item n="650a">Etiquette.</item>
          <item n="650a">Dreams</item>
          <item n="650a">Fortune-telling by moles.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>