<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Shrewsbury taken. A copie of Sir VVilliam Breretons letter to the Parliament: and the copie of a letter from the Committee of Shropshire: with a full relation of the manner of the taking of Shrewsbury, by Colonell Mitton and Colonell Bowyer, with Sir William Breretons and Colonell Mittons forces, on Saturday last, February 22. And the particulars of that great victory against P. Maurice's forces there: also a list of the chiefe prisoners names; and what was taken in the said garrison. Published according to order.</title>
      <author>Brereton, William, Sir, 1604-1661.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A77325</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R212285</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>Shrewsbury taken. A copie of Sir VVilliam Breretons letter to the Parliament: and the copie of a letter from the Committee of Shropshire: with a full relation of the manner of the taking of Shrewsbury, by Colonell Mitton and Colonell Bowyer, with Sir William Breretons and Colonell Mittons forces, on Saturday last, February 22. And the particulars of that great victory against P. Maurice's forces there: also a list  of the chiefe prisoners names; and what was taken in the said garrison. Published according to order.</title>
          <author gender="M">Brereton, William, Sir, 1604-1661.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[2], 13, [1] p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Robert Austin</persName>, in <placeName>the Old-Baily.</placeName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1645">1645.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "feb. 27".</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="printer">
          <persName>Robert Austin</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>Brereton, William, <roleName>Sir,</roleName></persName>
          <birth>1604</birth>
          <death>1661.</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="651x">History</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="temporal">
        <list>
          <item n="651y">Civil War, 1642-1649</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="651a 752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="651a">Shrewsbury (England)</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>