<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The declaration of the Hollanders concerning, the English fleet now under the command of General Blake; with the rising of the people against their magistrates, and declaring for a war with England: and the States proclamation, prohibiting all merchants and sea-men to touch upon the English coasts. Also, Vantrumps putting forth to sea with one hundred and seven men of war, and his orders and instructions given to the captains of his fleet. Likewise, the state of affairs in France, and declaring of the citizens of Paris rebels and traytors, by the King and councel. Together with the proceedings of the Parliaments forces in Ireland: sent in several letters from divers personages of honour to certain member of the Councel of State.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A82166</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R207032</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>The declaration of the Hollanders concerning, the English fleet now under the command of General Blake; with the rising of the people against their magistrates, and declaring for a war with England: and the States proclamation, prohibiting all merchants and sea-men to touch upon the English coasts. Also, Vantrumps putting forth to sea with one  hundred and seven men of war, and his orders and instructions given to the captains of his fleet. Likewise, the state of affairs in France, and declaring of the citizens of Paris rebels and traytors, by the King and councel. Together with the proceedings of the Parliaments forces in Ireland: sent in several letters from divers personages of honour to certain member of the Councel of State.</title>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>8 p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">B.A.</persName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1652">1652.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "July. 9th.".</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="printer">
          <persName>B.A.</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="subject">
          <persName>Blake, Robert,</persName>
          <birth>1599</birth>
          <death>1657</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
        <person role="subject">
          <persName>Tromp, Maarten Harpertsz,</persName>
          <birth>1598</birth>
          <death>1653</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Anglo-Dutch War, 1652-1654</item>
          <item n="650a">Fronde</item>
          <item n="651x">History</item>
          <item n="651x">1648-1714</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="temporal">
        <list>
          <item n="651y">Louis XIV, 1643-1715</item>
          <item n="651y">1649-1660</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="651a">Netherlands</item>
          <item n="651a">France</item>
          <item n="651a">Ireland</item>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>