<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The Parliaments vindication of Iohn Pym Esquire from His Majesties exception against him. Occasioned from his speech delivered at a conference with both Houses Jan. 25. 1641 concerning licenses granted by His Majesties immediate warrant, to many of the chiefe commanders now in the head of the rebells in Ireland, for their transporting thither, since the ports were stopt by both Houses of Parliament, against all Irish papists. In which vindication are, 1. Mr. Pym his speech. 2. His Majesties message concerning his speech. 3. The Commons answer to the message. 4. His Majesties reply to the Commons answer. 5. The Commons answer to the reply. 6. His Majesties second reply. Ordered by the Commons House of Parliament, that Mr. Pym his speech, His Majesties message concerning his speech, the commons answer to the message, His Majesties reply to the Commons answer, the Commons answer to that reply, and His Majesties second reply, be forthwith printed together and published. H. Elsynge Cler. Parl. D. Com.</title>
      <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A83365</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R22746</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>The Parliaments vindication of Iohn Pym Esquire from His Majesties exception against him. Occasioned from his speech delivered at a conference with both Houses Jan. 25. 1641 concerning licenses granted by His Majesties immediate warrant, to many of the chiefe commanders now in the head of the rebells in Ireland, for their transporting thither, since the ports were stopt by both Houses of Parliament, against all Irish papists. In which vindication are, 1. Mr. Pym his speech.  2. His Majesties message concerning his speech.  3. The Commons answer to the message.  4. His Majesties reply to the Commons answer.  5. The Commons answer to the reply. 6. His Majesties second reply. Ordered by the Commons House of Parliament, that Mr. Pym his speech, His Majesties message concerning his speech, the commons answer to the message, His Majesties reply to the Commons answer, the Commons answer to that reply, and His Majesties second reply, be forthwith printed together and published. H. Elsynge Cler. Parl. D. Com.</title>
          <author>England and Wales. Parliament.</author>
          <author gender="M">Pym, John, 1584-1643.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[2], 14 p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">John Bull</persName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1643">1643.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "June 17th".</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>John Bull</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="subject">
          <persName>Pym, John,</persName>
          <birth>1584</birth>
          <death>1643</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
        <person role="added">
          <persName>Pym, John,</persName>
          <birth>1584</birth>
          <death>1643.</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listOrg type="estc_ep">
        <org>
          <orgName>
            <name>England and Wales.</name>
            <name>Parliament.</name>
          </orgName>
        </org>
      </listOrg>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="651x">History</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="temporal">
        <list>
          <item n="651y">Rebellion of 1641</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="651a">Ireland</item>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>