<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A collection of certaine statutes in force, vvith full and ready notes in the margent, containing their effect in briefe. As also the ordinances for the better observation of the Lords day, and the fast dayes. Published for the better caution of such as are inclinable to delinquency against the severall effects of those statutes and ordinances. And also for the better information of all such officers and ministers as are by late speciall warrants authorised and commanded to put the same statutes and ordinances in execution. For the better suppressing 1. Of unlawfull pastimes and abuses on the Lords day. 2. Of prophane swearing and cursing. 3. Of the loathsome sin of drunkennesse. 4. Of the severall offences committed by inne-keepers, ale-house-keepers, and unlicensed ale-house-keepers. 5. Of unlawful games. And severall other abuses. Being appointed by the Lord Mayor of the City of London to be published in all congregations within his jurisdiction.</title>
      <author>England and Wales.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A84520</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R8377</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>A collection of certaine statutes in force, vvith full and ready notes in the margent, containing their effect in briefe. As also the ordinances for the better observation of the Lords day, and the fast dayes. Published for the better caution of such as are inclinable to delinquency against the severall effects of those statutes and ordinances. And also for the better information of all such officers and ministers as are by late speciall warrants authorised and commanded to put the same statutes and ordinances in execution. For the better suppressing 1. Of unlawfull pastimes and abuses on the Lords day.  2. Of prophane swearing and cursing.  3. Of the loathsome sin of drunkennesse.  4. Of the severall offences committed by inne-keepers, ale-house-keepers, and unlicensed ale-house-keepers.  5. Of unlawful games.  And severall other abuses. Being appointed by the Lord Mayor of the City of London to be published in all congregations within his jurisdiction.</title>
          <author>England and Wales.</author>
          <author gender="M">W. B., co-author.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[8], 40 p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">Robert White</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>his house on Adling-Hill</placeName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1644">MDCXLIV. [1644]</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>"The epistle to the reader" signed: W.B.</note>
          <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Nouemb: 11th".</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="printer">
          <persName>Robert White</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="added">
          <persName>W. B.</persName>
          <sex value=""/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listOrg type="estc_ep">
        <org>
          <orgName>
            <name>England and Wales.</name>
          </orgName>
        </org>
      </listOrg>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Sunday legislation</item>
          <item n="650a">Swearing</item>
          <item n="650a">Liquor laws</item>
          <item n="650a">Taverns (Inns)</item>
          <item n="650a">Gambling</item>
          <item n="650x">Law and legislation</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="form">
        <list>
          <item n="655a">Laws.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="650z 752b">England</item>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>