<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A true and perfect relation of the surrender of the strong and impregnable garrison the island of Scillie, to Captain Batten Vice-Admirall of the Parliaments navie at sea. VVith the discoverie of a bloody designe of Pendennis, for the blowing up of the castle, and poysoning of foure-score pieces of ordnance. Also a perfect account of the ammunition provision, and other necessaries that were left in the castle, at the surrender thereof. Together wit a list of the names of all the colonels, majors, captaines, lievtenants and other officers that were therein. VVhereunto is annexed an excellent copy of verses, made in Pendennis castle, when it was besieged by sea and land. Certified by two severall letters from Mr. Iohn Hoselock, chyrurgion to the Vice-Admirall Captain Batten in the St. Andrew. And now ptinted [sic] and published by the originall copies, according to order of Parliament.</title>
      <author>Haslock, John.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A86090</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R201078</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>A true and perfect relation of the surrender of the strong and impregnable garrison the island of Scillie, to Captain Batten Vice-Admirall of the Parliaments navie at sea. VVith the discoverie of a bloody designe of Pendennis, for the blowing up of the castle, and poysoning of foure-score pieces of ordnance. Also a perfect account of the ammunition provision, and other necessaries that were left in the castle, at the surrender thereof. Together wit  a list of the names of all the colonels, majors, captaines, lievtenants and other officers that were therein. VVhereunto is annexed an excellent copy of verses, made in Pendennis castle, when it was besieged by sea and land. Certified by two severall letters from Mr. Iohn Hoselock, chyrurgion to the Vice-Admirall Captain Batten in the St. Andrew. And now ptinted [sic] and published by the originall copies, according to order of Parliament.</title>
          <author gender="M">Haslock, John.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[8] p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">B.I.</persName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1646">1646.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Signatures: A⁴.</note>
          <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Sept: 1st".</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="printer">
          <persName>B.I.</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>Haslock, John.</persName>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listOrg type="estc_ep">
        <org>
          <orgName>
            <name>Pendennis Castle (Falmouth, England)</name>
          </orgName>
        </org>
      </listOrg>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="651x">History</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="temporal">
        <list>
          <item n="651y">Civil War, 1642-1649.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="651a 752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="651a">Scilly, Isles of</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>