<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The last bloudy fight at sea, between the English and the Dutch, on Tuesday last, upon the coast of Denmark: the manner of the engagement; the particulars of the fight; the taking of one hundred and seven ships, and above two thousand prisoners; with the pursuing of three hundred sayl to the coast of Scotland, and besieging of them in Bressie-Iland; the resolution of the Dutch-men to fight it out to the last man, and their preparation and proceedings thereupon. The concluding of a league between the States of Holland, the King of Denmark; the Queen of Sweden; and a declaration of four score of the Swedish men of war.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A88719</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R207089</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>The last bloudy fight at sea, between the English and the Dutch, on Tuesday last, upon the coast of Denmark: the manner of the engagement; the  particulars of the fight; the taking of one hundred and seven ships, and above two thousand prisoners; with the pursuing of three hundred sayl to the coast of Scotland, and besieging of them in Bressie-Iland; the resolution of the Dutch-men to fight it out to the last man, and their preparation and proceedings thereupon. The concluding of a league between the States of Holland, the King of Denmark; the Queen of Sweden; and a declaration of four score of the Swedish men of war.</title>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>8 p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">George Horton</persName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1652">1652.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "July 27".</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>George Horton</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="subject">
          <persName>Ayscue, George, <roleName>Sir,</roleName></persName>
          <floruit>active 1646-1671</floruit>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
        <person role="subject">
          <persName>Tromp, Maarten Harpertsz.,</persName>
          <birth>1598</birth>
          <death>1653</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Anglo-Dutch War, 1652-1654</item>
          <item n="651x">History, Naval</item>
          <item n="651x">History</item>
          <item n="651x">1648-1714</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="temporal">
        <list>
          <item n="651y">Stuarts, 1603-1714</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="651a 752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="651a">Netherlands</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>