<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A true relation of the proceedings of the Scots and English forces in the north of Ireland: sent in a letter to Mr. Tobias Siedgwicke, living in London; relating these particulars: viz. 1. Their meeting at Drumboe in the county of Antrem. 2. The manner of their march towards the Nury, with the taking of a fort neere Kilwarlin Woods. 3. The taking of the towne and castle of the Nury, and the releasing of divers prisoners of note. 4. The great spoile they tooke in those parts, with great terrour to the rebels, and their flight from those parts. 5. Divers skirmishes with the rebels in Mr. Cartons woods. 6. The desires of the earle of Antrem to be received into the English Army. VVith divers other things worthy your observation.</title>
      <author>Pike, Roger, 17th cent.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A90704</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R152</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>A true relation of the proceedings of the Scots and English forces in the north of Ireland: sent in a letter to Mr. Tobias Siedgwicke, living in London; relating these particulars: viz. 1. Their meeting at Drumboe in the county of Antrem. 2. The manner of their march towards the Nury, with the taking of a fort neere Kilwarlin Woods. 3. The taking of the towne and castle of the Nury, and the releasing of divers prisoners of note. 4. The great spoile they tooke in those parts, with great  terrour to the rebels, and their flight from those parts. 5. Divers skirmishes with the rebels in Mr. Cartons woods. 6. The desires of the earle of Antrem to be received into the English Army. VVith divers other things worthy your observation.</title>
          <author gender="M">Pike, Roger, 17th cent.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[1], 7 p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">F. Coules</persName> and <persName type="publisher">T. Bates</persName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1642">1642.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Signed: Roger Pike.</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
          <note>At head of title: June 8th. 1642.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>F. Coules</persName>
        </person>
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName><choice><orig>T. Bates</orig><reg>Bates, Thomas</reg></choice></persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>Pike, Roger,</persName>
          <floruit>active 17th century.</floruit>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="651x">History</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="temporal">
        <list>
          <item n="651y">1625-1649</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="651a">Ireland</item>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>