<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Questions propounded, or Quæres, concerning remedies, and taking away of the extreame and unnecessary charges, expences, troubles, and long delayes in just causes and suits in courts of equity and others called English-Courts, and abating those that may be for contention and trouble only, and the preservation of many honest men from great losses, and others from undoing therby, without hindrance or prejudice to any but unnecessary and upstart officers. And how many hundred thousand pounds may be saved to the common-wealth yearly, by reducing proceedings in law to the old and legall proceedings, and taking away those that be unlawfull and contrived by exacting officers for their own only gaine. Authorized to be printed and published for the good of the common-wealth.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A91599</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R201398</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>Questions propounded, or Quæres, concerning remedies, and taking away of the extreame and unnecessary charges, expences, troubles, and long delayes in just causes and suits in courts of equity and others called English-Courts, and abating those that may be for contention and trouble only, and the preservation of many honest men from great losses, and others from undoing therby, without hindrance or prejudice to any but unnecessary and upstart officers.  And how many hundred thousand pounds may be saved to the common-wealth yearly, by reducing proceedings in law to the old and legall proceedings, and taking away those that be unlawfull and contrived by exacting officers for their own only gaine. Authorized to be printed and published for the good of the common-wealth.</title>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>8 p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">F. Leach</persName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1647">1647.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "March 11th 1646"; the 7 in imprint date crossed out.</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="printer">
          <persName><choice><orig>F. Leach</orig><reg>Leach, Francis, -1658</reg></choice></persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Law</item>
          <item n="650a">Courts</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="650z 752b">England</item>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>