<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The three Kingdomes healing-plaister. Or, The solemne covenant of reformation and defence explained. Wherein is shewed the authority, antiquity, and use of an holy covenant: the occasions moving to it, and the ends in doing it, the necessity of it at this time, for diverse reasons herein expressed. Also a full explanation of each article of the Covenant, to the satisfaction of all: shewing the benefit that may redound by it, viz. Gods protection and blessing to heale our miseries, and establish truth in religion, peace and lasting happinesse to the three kingdomes. Likewise shewing the danger of refusing it, and Gods curse upon us, if we enter into it deceitfully. Imprimatur, Ia. Cranford. By G.S., Gent.</title>
      <author>Smith, George, 1602 or 3-1658.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A93351</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R460</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>The three Kingdomes healing-plaister. Or, The solemne covenant of reformation and defence explained. Wherein is shewed the authority, antiquity, and use of an holy covenant: the occasions moving to it, and the ends in doing it, the necessity of it at this time, for diverse reasons herein expressed. Also a full explanation of each article of the Covenant, to the satisfaction of all: shewing the benefit that may redound by it, viz. Gods protection and blessing to heale our miseries, and establish truth in religion, peace and lasting happinesse to the three kingdomes. Likewise shewing the danger of refusing it, and Gods curse upon us, if we enter into it deceitfully. Imprimatur, Ia. Cranford.  By G.S., Gent.</title>
          <author gender="M">Smith, George, 1602 or 3-1658.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[2], 14 p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Francis Coles</persName> in <placeName>the Old-Bailey</placeName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1643">1643.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Octob: 17th".</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>Francis Coles</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>Smith, George,</persName>
          <floruit>1602 or 1603-1658.</floruit>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Covenants</item>
          <item n="651x">History</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="temporal">
        <list>
          <item n="651y">Civil War, 1642-1649</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="651a 752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="650z 752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>