<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>To Sions virgins: or, A short forme of catechisme of the doctrine of baptisme, in use in these times that are so full of questions. By an antient member, of that long agoe gathered congregation, whereof Mr. Henry Jacob was an instrument of gathering it, and the pastour worthy of double honour, Mr. John Lathroppe succeeding him, now pastor in New England; and the beloved congregation, through Gods mercies sees her teachers, waiting when God shall give more liberty and pastours according to his own heart, praying the Lord of the harvest to thrust forth labourers into his harvest.</title>
      <author>Antient member of that long agoe gathered congregation.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A94435</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R4276</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>To Sions virgins: or, A short forme of catechisme of the doctrine of baptisme, in use in these times that are so full of questions. By an antient member, of that long agoe gathered congregation, whereof Mr. Henry Jacob was an instrument of gathering it, and the pastour worthy of double honour, Mr. John Lathroppe succeeding him, now pastor in New England; and the beloved congregation, through  Gods mercies sees her teachers, waiting when God shall give more liberty and pastours according to his own heart, praying the Lord of the harvest to thrust forth labourers into his harvest.</title>
          <author>Antient member of that long agoe gathered congregation.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[12] p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>s.n.],</publisher>
          <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1644">Printed in the yeare 1644.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Annotation on Thomason copy: "Nou: 4th"; "London".</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>Antient member of that long agoe gathered congregation.</persName>
          <sex value=""/>
    </person>
        <person role="added" n="attributed name.">
          <persName>Jones, Sarah,</persName>
          <sex value="F"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Baptism</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>