<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The copie of a letter sent from Pope Urban the 8. unto the King of France, Jan. 28. 1641. Brought unto the said king, by the Bishop of Salerno the Popes nuntio. Wherein he informes the king, that he understands by his nuntio lately returned out of England. What and how great persecutions and pressures the catholiques suffer, since the sitting of the Parliament there. Whence he taketh occasion to exhort and incite the king to the same measure towards his Hugonets in France. Also strongly perswading him to an inclination unto peace with the crowne of Spaine. And for the assisting of the Catholiques in Ireland. Translated out of the Latine copie by J.S.</title>
      <author>Urban VIII, Pope, 1568-1644.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A95747</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R17612</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>The copie of a letter sent from Pope Urban the 8. unto the King of France, Jan. 28. 1641. Brought unto the said king, by the Bishop of Salerno the Popes nuntio. Wherein he informes the king, that he understands by his nuntio lately returned out of England. What and how great persecutions and pressures the catholiques suffer, since the sitting  of the Parliament there. Whence he taketh occasion to exhort and incite the king to the same measure towards his Hugonets in France. Also strongly perswading him to an inclination unto peace with the crowne of Spaine. And for the assisting of the Catholiques in Ireland. Translated out of the Latine copie by J.S.</title>
          <author gender="M">Urban VIII, Pope, 1568-1644.</author>
          <author>J. S.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[2], 6 p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Iohn Thomas</persName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1642">1641. [i.e. 1642]</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>Iohn Thomas</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>Urban <roleName>Pope,</roleName> <genName>VIII,</genName></persName>
          <birth>1568</birth>
          <death>1644.</death>
        </person>
        <person role="added">
          <persName>J. S.</persName>
          <sex value=""/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Catholics</item>
          <item n="651x">Religion</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="temporal">
        <list>
          <item n="650y 651y">17th century.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="651a 752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="650z 752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>