<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Bloudy nevves from the Lord Byron, in Wales; declaring the proceedings of the royall party, against the Parliaments forces, and the rising of the Welch-men with long hookes, and the bloudy execution done thereby. Also, a great fight neer the Isle of Anglesea, between the forces commanded by the Lord Byron, and Col. Horton, with the particulars thereof, and the number killed and taken. And a dangerous fight at Scarbrough Castle in Yorkes, between a party of the Princes forces, and Col. Bethels. Likewise, the resolution of the Levellers of England. And the remonstrance and declaration of Lieut. Gen. Cromwell, concerning the enemies of religion, King, and kingdome. Commanded to be printed and published. O. Crumwell.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A96528</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R205099</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>Bloudy nevves from the Lord Byron, in Wales; declaring the proceedings of the royall party, against the Parliaments forces, and the rising of the Welch-men with long hookes, and the bloudy execution done thereby. Also, a great fight neer the Isle of Anglesea, between the forces commanded  by the Lord Byron, and Col. Horton, with the particulars thereof, and the number killed and taken. And a dangerous fight at Scarbrough Castle in Yorkes, between a party of the Princes forces, and Col. Bethels. Likewise, the resolution of the Levellers of England. And the remonstrance and declaration of Lieut. Gen. Cromwell, concerning the enemies of religion, King, and kingdome. Commanded to be printed and published. O. Crumwell.</title>
          <author gender="M">Wilkinson, Thomas.</author>
          <author gender="M">Cromwell, Oliver, 1599-1658.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[2], 6 p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Septemb. 14. Imprinted at <placeName>London</placeName>, for <persName type="publisher">G.H.</persName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>[London] :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1648">1648.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Includes a letter signed: Thomas Wilkinson; and "The remonstrance &amp; resolution of the Right Honorable, and truly valiant, Lieut. Gen. Cromwell".</note>
          <note>Reproduction of the original in the British Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>G.H.</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="added">
          <persName>Wilkinson, Thomas.</persName>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
        <person role="added">
          <persName>Cromwell, Oliver,</persName>
          <birth>1599</birth>
          <death>1658.</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Levellers</item>
          <item n="651x">History</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="temporal">
        <list>
          <item n="651y">Civil War, 1642-1649</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="651a 752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>