<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>A chronological account of the age of the world at the birth of every one of the Ancient Fathers, from Adam to the Flood of Noah, the kings of Judah, the captivity of Babilon, and the end thereof, till the death of the Messiah to which are added several remarks concerning the end of the first six thousand years of this world's-age, and what may be expected for a thousand years thence next following, and some thoughts concerning the end of the world. As also a brief exposition of the thirteenth of the Revelations: much differing from all that ever was before it. Wherein is sett forth; first, who the two beasts therein mentioned are. Secondly, when they began. Thirdly, how long they are to continue. Fourthly, when their end shall be. Wherein that [my]stical number of 666, is fully explained. By William Wright of Colledge-Green, Dublin.</title>
      <author>Wright, William, 18th cent.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">A96980</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R217352</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>A chronological account of the age of the world at the birth of every one of the Ancient Fathers, from Adam to the Flood of Noah, the kings of Judah, the captivity of Babilon, and the end thereof, till the death of the Messiah to which are added several remarks concerning the end of the first six thousand years of this world's-age, and what may be expected for a thousand years thence next following, and some thoughts concerning the end of the world. As also a brief exposition of the thirteenth of the Revelations: much differing from all that ever was before it. Wherein is sett forth; first, who the two beasts therein mentioned are. Secondly, when they began. Thirdly, how long they are to continue. Fourthly, when their end shall be. Wherein that [my]stical number of 666, is fully explained. By William Wright of Colledge-Green, Dublin.</title>
          <author>Wright, William, 18th cent.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[2], 15, [1] p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>printed by <persName type="printer">J. Whalley, next door to the Flee[ce]</persName> in <placeName>St. Nicholas-street</placeName>, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">the book-sellers of Dublin</persName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>Dublin :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1700">1700</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>The titlepage is a cancellans. The cancellandum, which reads: 'A chronological account of the world: in which is shewed, the age of the world ..', is dated 1700.</note>
          <note>With a postscript, in which the author declares that: "In the printing of this small chronicle, I found that it did not fill two sheets of paper; therefore (with the advice of the printer,) I added something which I thought convenient to be known, to fill up the second sheet; .. when I had so done, I thought these two sheets too little to be published alone; and therefore I have added to them, .. A brief exposition of the thirteenth chapter of the Revelation; ..".</note>
          <note>Marginal notes.</note>
          <note>Copy filmed at UMI microfilm Early English Books 1641-1700 reel 2320 appears to be misbound with leaf C2 and C3 following title page and lacks all after p. [20]; title page is dated 1700.</note>
          <note>Reproduction of original in the William Andrews Clark Memorial Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="printer">
          <persName>J. Whalley, next door to the Flee[ce]</persName>
        </person>
        <person type="bookseller">
          <persName>the book-sellers of Dublin</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>Wright, William,</persName>
          <floruit>active 18th century.</floruit>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
        <person role="added" type="printer.">
          <persName>Whalley, John,</persName>
          <birth>1653</birth>
          <death>1724,</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="form">
        <list>
          <item n="630v">Chronology</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="752a">Ireland</item>
          <item n="752d">Dublin.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>