<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The 25. of September. Nevves from most parts of christendome. Especially from Rome, Italy, Spaine, France, the Palatinate, the Low Countries, and diuers other places. VVherein is contained a full and certaine relation, of the last battle fought at Bergen vp-Zome, and the great ouerthrow which Spinolaes forces receiued from those of the towne. With the lamentable losse of the city of Heidlebergh, after many braue repulses given to the enemie: and the names of some principall leaders, as were slaine in defence of the towne. And diuers other speciall matters, coninued from the last printed newes of the twentieth, to this present..</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">B07967</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">S94469</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>The 25. of September. Nevves from most parts of christendome. Especially from Rome, Italy, Spaine, France, the Palatinate, the Low Countries, and diuers other places.  VVherein is contained a full and certaine relation, of the last battle fought at Bergen vp-Zome, and the great ouerthrow which Spinolaes forces receiued from those of the towne.  With the lamentable losse of the city of Heidlebergh, after many braue repulses given to the enemie: and the names of some principall leaders, as were slaine in defence of the towne.  And diuers other speciall matters, coninued from the last printed newes of the twentieth, to this present..</title>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>17 p. : Coat of arms.  </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Nathaniel Butter</persName>, and <persName type="publisher">William Sheffard.</persName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London, :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1622">1622..</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Printer's ornament on t.p., coat of arms, headpieces, initials.</note>
          <note>Signatures: A-B⁴ C³.</note>
          <note>Imperfect: pages cropped with some loss of text.</note>
          <note>Reproduction of original in: Harvard University. Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>Nathaniel Butter</persName>
        </person>
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>William Sheffard.</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Thirty Years' War, 1618-1648</item>
          <item n="651x">History</item>
          <item n="651x">Newspapers</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="form">
        <list>
          <item n="655a">Newsbooks</item>
          <item n="655a">Newsbooks.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="temporal">
        <list>
          <item n="651y">17th century</item>
          <item n="655y">17th century.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="651a">Europe</item>
          <item n="655z 752b">England</item>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>