<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>The 27. of August. Mansfeilds arrivall in the dukedome of Brabant, and is alreadie come on this side Bruxelles, burning, spoyling, and ransoming the countrey. Also Gonzales comming towards him with great forces, with the rest of their proceedings. With the destruction of Spinola's forces before Berghen op Zoom; as also the marching of the English forces of the regiment of the Lord Vaus from Antwerpe to Bergen, with the number of them. Likewise, a true relation of the proceedings and circumstances, touching the royall coronation of the most illustrious, most mightie princesse, Lady Eleonora, Empresse of Rome, Queene of Hungaria, Arch-Dutches of Austria, and Dutches of Mantua. Moreover, the straite besieging of Mamora by the Hollanders, with the invasion made by the Protestant grisons vpon the countrey of Tyrolle, and the obtaining of great store of cattell. Lastly, the couragious Sally made by the garrisons in Glatts, vpon the emperialls; with the delivering vp of Hagenaw to Leopoldus; as also [Klin]genbergh to the Emperour.</title>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">B07966</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">S94222</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>The 27. of August. Mansfeilds arrivall in the dukedome of Brabant, and is alreadie come on this side Bruxelles, burning, spoyling, and ransoming the countrey. Also Gonzales comming towards him with great forces, with the rest of their proceedings.  With the destruction of Spinola's forces before Berghen op Zoom; as also the marching of the English forces of the regiment of the Lord Vaus from Antwerpe to Bergen, with the number of them.  Likewise, a true relation of the proceedings and circumstances, touching the royall coronation of the most illustrious, most mightie princesse, Lady Eleonora, Empresse of Rome, Queene of Hungaria, Arch-Dutches of Austria, and Dutches of Mantua.  Moreover, the straite besieging of Mamora by the Hollanders, with the invasion made by the Protestant grisons vpon the countrey of Tyrolle, and the obtaining of great store of cattell.  Lastly, the couragious Sally made by the garrisons in Glatts, vpon the emperialls; with the delivering vp of Hagenaw to Leopoldus; as also [Klin]genbergh to the Emperour.</title>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>17 p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">J. D.</persName> for <persName type="publisher">Nicholas Bourne</persName> and <persName type="publisher">Thomas Archer</persName>, and are to be sold at <placeName>their shops at the Exchange</placeName>, and in <placeName>Popes-head Pallace.</placeName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1622">1622..</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Headpieces, initials.</note>
          <note>Signatures: A-B⁴ C³.</note>
          <note>Imperfect: pages have faded print ; irregular pagination.</note>
          <note>Reproduction of original in: Bodleian Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>Nicholas Bourne</persName>
        </person>
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>Thomas Archer</persName>
        </person>
        <person type="printer">
          <persName>J. D.</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Thirty Years' War, 1618-1648</item>
          <item n="651x">History</item>
          <item n="651x">Newspapers</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="form">
        <list>
          <item n="655a">Newsbooks</item>
          <item n="655a">Newsbooks.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="temporal">
        <list>
          <item n="651y">17th century</item>
          <item n="655y">17th century.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="651a">Europe</item>
          <item n="655z 752b">England</item>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>