<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Several discourses concerning the actual Providence of God. Divided into three parts. The first, treating concerning the notion of it, establshing the doctrine of it, opening the principal acts of it, preservation and government of created beings. With the particular acts, by which it so preserveth and governeth them. The second, concerning the specialities of it, the unseachable things of it, and several observable things in its motions. The third, concerning the dysnoēta, or hard chapters of it, in which an attempt is made to solve several appearances of difficulty in the motions of Providence, and to vindicate the justice, wisdom, and holiness of God, with the reasonableness of his dealing in such motions. / By John Collinges ...</title>
      <author>Collinges, John, 1623-1690.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">B08803</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R233164</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>Several discourses concerning the actual Providence of God. Divided into three parts. The first, treating concerning the notion of it, establshing the doctrine of it, opening the principal acts of it, preservation and government of created beings. With the particular acts, by which it so preserveth and governeth them.  The second, concerning the specialities of it, the unseachable things of it, and several observable things in its motions.  The third, concerning the dysnoēta, or hard chapters of it, in which an attempt is made to solve several appearances of difficulty in the motions of Providence, and to vindicate the justice, wisdom, and holiness of God, with the reasonableness of his dealing in such motions. / By John Collinges ...</title>
          <author gender="M">Collinges, John, 1623-1690.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[27], 740, [15] p. :  port. </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Tho. Parkhurst</persName>, and are to be sold by <persName type="bookseller">Edward Giles</persName> ...,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London: :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1678">1678.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Includes index.</note>
          <note>Reproduction of original in the Haverford College Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName><choice><orig>Tho. Parkhurst</orig><reg>Parkhurst, Thomas</reg></choice></persName>
        </person>
        <person type="bookseller">
          <persName>Edward Giles</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>Collinges, John,</persName>
          <birth>1623</birth>
          <death>1690.</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
        <person role="added">
          <persName>White, Robert,</persName>
          <birth>1645</birth>
          <death>1703.</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Providence and government of God</item>
          <item n="650a">Theology, Doctrinal</item>
          <item n="650a">Sermons, English</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="form">
        <list>
          <item n="650v">Sermons</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="temporal">
        <list>
          <item n="650y">17th century.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>