<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Faith &amp; experience:, or, A short narration of the holy life and death of Mary Simpson, late of Gregories Parish in the city of Norvvich: who dyed, anno 1647 in or about the thirtieth yeare of her age after 3 yeares sicknesse and upwards. Containing a confession of her faith and relation of her experience, taken from her owne mouth. To which is added a sermon preached at her funerall, upon Rom. 14. 6,7. / by John Collings.</title>
      <author>Collinges, John, 1623-1690.</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">B08802</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R231574</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>Faith &amp; experience:, or, A short narration of the holy life and death of Mary Simpson, late of Gregories Parish in the city of Norvvich: who dyed, anno 1647 in or about the thirtieth yeare of her age after 3 yeares sicknesse and upwards.  Containing a confession of her faith and relation of her experience, taken from her owne mouth.  To which is added a sermon preached at her funerall, upon Rom. 14. 6,7. / by John Collings.</title>
          <author gender="M">Collinges, John, 1623-1690.</author>
          <author>Collinges, John, 1623-1690. Life &amp; death of a true Christian deciphered in a sermon.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>[22], 51, [3], 81 p.   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed for <persName type="publisher">Richard Tomlins</persName> and are to be sold at <placeName>his house at the Signe of the Sun</placeName> and Bible in <placeName>Pye-Corner</placeName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1649">1649.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Includes Collinges' work "The life &amp; death of a true Christian ..." not found in Wing (2nd ed.).</note>
          <note>Reproduction of original in: British Library.</note>
          <note>Bound and filmed with Wing A27B and Wing A27aA: The saints duty discoursed from 2 Pet 3, 18 and the saints dignity handled from Eph chap I, v. 7 with directions to both delivered from a chatecheticall dialogue by him that was and is ... London : Printed for William Franckling and are to be sold at his Shop Near the Signe of the George in Norwhich, 1649 -- A plaine and easie catechisme : wherein the grounds and principles of Christian religion are briefly taught and likewise proved by scripture published for the benefit of all / by R.A. London : Printed for William Franckling and are to be sold at his Shop near the Signe of the George in Norwich, 1649.</note>
          <note>Faith &amp; experience, or, A short narration of the holy life and death of Mary Simpson, late of Gregories Parish in the city of Norvvich : who dyed, anno 1647 in or about the thirtieth yeare of her age after 3 yeares sicknesse and upwards, containing a confession of her faith and relation of her experience taken from her owne mouth, to which is added a sermon preached at her funerall upon Rom. 14. 6,7 -- The life &amp; death of a true Christian : deciphered in a sermon preached upon the 14 Rom. 6,7 vers. at the buriall of Mary Simpson ; a religious young maid, lately living in the city of Norwich.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="publisher">
          <persName>Richard Tomlins</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="creator">
          <persName>Collinges, John,</persName>
          <birth>1623</birth>
          <death>1690.</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
        <person role="subject">
          <persName>Simpson, Mary,</persName>
          <death>-1647.</death>
          <sex value="F"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Funeral sermons</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="temporal">
        <list>
          <item n="650y">17th century.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752b">England</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>