<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>By His Excellency the governour. Whereas it hath been of absolute necessity, that a certain number of men should be impressed, for the service of Their Majesties, in defence of this their province, both a sea and Land, against the common enemy. And that some persons imployed therein, have passed the bounds of their duty, and my order, by putting the same in execution in a violent and disorderly manner, to the great grievance of Their Majesties good subjects.</title>
      <author>Massachusetts. Governor (1692-1695 : Phips)</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">B09500</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>By His Excellency the governour. Whereas it hath been of absolute necessity, that a certain number of men should be impressed, for the service of Their Majesties, in defence of this their province, both a sea and Land, against the common enemy.  And that some persons imployed therein, have passed the bounds of their duty, and my order, by putting the same in execution in a violent and disorderly manner, to the great grievance of Their Majesties good subjects.</title>
          <author>Massachusetts. Governor (1692-1695 : Phips)</author>
          <author gender="M">Phips, William, Sir, 1651-1695.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>1 sheet ([2] p.) : ill.  </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>Printed by <persName type="printer">Benjamin Harris</persName>, Printer to <persName type="patron">His Excellency, the Governour</persName> and <persName type="patron">Council</persName>,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>[Boston] :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1692">1692.</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Place of publication suggested by Wing (2nd ed.).</note>
          <note>Royal arms at head of title.</note>
          <note>Reproduction of original in: Massachusetts Historical Society Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="tcp_ep">
        <person type="printer">
          <persName>Benjamin Harris</persName>
        </person>
        <person type="patron">
          <persName>Council</persName>
        </person>
        <person type="patron">
          <persName>His Excellency, the Governour</persName>
        </person>
      </listPerson>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc><textClass/></profileDesc>
</teiHeader>