<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><?xml-model href="../schema/ep_teiHeader.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?><teiHeader xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <fileDesc>
    <titleStmt>
      <title>Whereas a commission under the Great Seal of England, bearing date at Westminster the three and twentieth day of August now last past, hath been directed unto me, and divers others in the said commission nominated, authorizing the said commissioners, or any four or more of them, by such ways and means as therein is directed, to enquire within the city and diocess of Canterbery in the county of Kent, as well within liberties as without, for the due execution of the statute made made in the three and fortieth year of the raign of our late soveraign Lady Queen Elizabeth ... Given under my hand this fourth day of September, in the year of our Lord 1683.</title>
      <author>Church of England. Province of Canterbury. Archbishop (1678-1690 : Sancroft)</author>
    </titleStmt>
    <publicationStmt>
      <publisher>EarlyPrint project</publisher>
      <idno type="tcpid">B09948</idno>
      <idno type="estcid">R186431</idno>
    </publicationStmt>
    <sourceDesc>
      <biblFull>
        <titleStmt>
          <title>Whereas a commission under the Great Seal of England, bearing date at Westminster the three and twentieth day of August now last past, hath been directed unto me, and divers others in the said commission nominated, authorizing the said commissioners, or any four or more of them, by such ways and means as therein is directed, to enquire within the city and diocess of Canterbery in the county of Kent, as well within liberties as without, for the due execution of the statute made made in the three and fortieth  year of the raign of our late soveraign Lady Queen Elizabeth ... Given under my hand this fourth day of September, in the year of our Lord 1683.</title>
          <author>Church of England. Province of Canterbury. Archbishop (1678-1690 : Sancroft)</author>
          <author gender="M">Sancroft, William, 1617-1693.</author>
        </titleStmt>
        <extent>1 sheet ([1] p.).   </extent>
        <publicationStmt>
          <publisher>s.n.,</publisher>
          <pubPlace>[London :</pubPlace>
          <date when="1683">1683]</date>
        </publicationStmt>
        <notesStmt>
          <note>Signed: "W. Cant."</note>
          <note>Place and date of publication suggested by Wing (2nd ed.).</note>
          <note>Reproduction of original in: Bodleian Library.</note>
        </notesStmt>
      </biblFull>
      <listPerson type="estc_ep">
        <person role="added">
          <persName>Sancroft, William,</persName>
          <birth>1617</birth>
          <death>1693.</death>
          <sex value="M"/>
    </person>
      </listPerson>
      <listOrg type="estc_ep">
        <org>
          <orgName>
            <name>Church of England.</name>
            <name>Province of Canterbury.</name>
            <name>Archbishop (1678-1690 : Sancroft).</name>
          </orgName>
        </org>
        <org>
          <orgName>
            <name>England and Wales.</name>
            <name>Commissioners for Charitable Uses</name>
          </orgName>
        </org>
      </listOrg>
    </sourceDesc>
  </fileDesc>
  <profileDesc>
    <textClass>
      <keywords n="general">
        <list>
          <item n="650a">Charities</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="form">
        <list>
          <item n="610v">Early works to</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
      <keywords n="geographic">
        <list>
          <item n="650z 752b">England</item>
          <item n="752a">Great Britain</item>
          <item n="752d">London.</item>
        </list>
      </keywords>
    </textClass>
  </profileDesc>
</teiHeader>